I got no leg room back here.
Move your seat forward.
That's as far as it goes.
There's a mechanism. You just pull it,
and throw your body weight.
I pulled it. It doesn't go.
If you want the leg room, say you want
the leg room! Don't blame the mechanism!
All right, Dad, we're five blocks
from the house.  Sit sideways.
Like an animal. Because of her,
I have to sit here like an animal!
Serenity now! Serenity now!
What is that?
Doctor gave me a relaxation cassette.
When my blood pressure
gets too high, the man
on the tape tells me
to say, 'Serenity now!'
Are you supposed to yell it?
The man on the tape wasn't specific.
What happened to the screen door?
It blew off again?
I told you to fix that thing.
Serenity nowww!
So I told Bobby and Lisa that  we'd try
the new Chinese Spanish  place
La Caridad on Saturday.
Oh, I thought we had tickets
for the Knicks home opener.
Well I thought this would be more fun
so I gave the tickets away.
What? All right, fine.
Are you mad at me?
No, I love a good Chinese Spanish
whatever it is.
You know... I've never seen you mad.
I get peeved.
Mad.
Miffed.
*Mad*.
Irked?
I'd like to see you get *really* mad.
Why does she want you to be mad?
She says I suppress my emotions.
So what do you care what she thinks.
Good body.
She probably gets that impression
because you're cool.
You're under control. Like me.
Nothing wrong with that.
But I get upset, I've yelled.
You've heard me yell.
Not really. Your voice kind of raises
to this comedic pitch.
Kramer, I am so sick of you comin' in here
and eatin' all my food.
Now shut that door and get
the hell out of here!
What is that, a new bit?
I told ya. Hey, any of you guys
want to come out
and help me fix  my father's screen
door in Queens?
Sorry, I'm fixing a screen door in the Bronx.
I'll do it.
Really? You wanna come?
Yeah, I love going to the country.
Where are they goin'?
Fix a screen door in Queens.
That's funny. Hey, listen, what are
you doin' Saturday night?
Not goin' to the Knick game.
I need someone to go with me
to Mr. Lippman's son's Bar Mitzvah.
You know, if you don't bring a guest
they save a catering.
You should be able to buy
a cheaper gift.
Oh, I don't think that's possible.
Get in a little closer.
I can't see the screen door. Perfect.
Dad, the hinges are all rusted here.
That's why the wind keeps
blowing the door off.
I hate that old door. Throw it out!
Serenity now!
It might be time to just let her go,
Frank. She's worked hard for ya.
Will you put her to rest for me?
Oh yeah, I'll take good care of her.
Get George to put those
boxes in the garage.
Dad, what's all this?
It's junk.
My computers. I've been selling them
for two months now. Shut up!
You're selling computers?
Two months ago,
I saw a provocative movie
on cable TV.
It was called The Net, with
that girl from the bus.
I did a little reading, and I realize,
it wasn't that farfetched.
Dad, you know what it takes
to compete with Microsoft and   IBM?
Yes, I do. That's why I got
a secret weapon... my son.
Damn it, they gave me cream!
I asked for nonfat milk!
I think they have 1% over there.
1%?! They can kiss 1% of my ass!
OK, Jerry, enough.
I'm not buying it.
You're damn right you're not buying it!
You shouldn't have to try.
It's just being open.
I'm open. There's just nothing
in there.
Oh, you think I'm lying about this?
I think you are.
Well, I'm not.
Yes, you are, liar.
Oh, stop it.
OK, liar.
That's enough!
Ooh, that was good.
Really? It felt good.
Congratulations, Mr. Lippman.
Oh, Elaine. My boy's a man today
Can you believe it? He's a man.
I'm a man!
Tongue?
Yeah.
Wow! I didn't try
that 'til I was 23.
Well this kid's not just a man.
He's a man's man.
And I think he's been
telling his friends.
I got invitations to
six more Bar Mitzvahs.
Hello? Yeah, this is Jerry Seinfeld.
No, no, no, I do not want to
stop over in Cincinnati.
Well, then you upgrade me.
That's right, you should thank me.
Hey, I'm flyin' first class.
Where did that come from?
Patty showed me how to get mad.
You gotta problem with that?
No.
Good.
All right, relax, tough guy.
I got to go out to my father's
garage, help him sell some computers.
What? The two of you workin' in that
garage is like a steel cage death match.
Kramer.
Yeah.
What-what are you doing?
Oh, I'm putting up Frank's screen door.
This beauty's got a
little life in her yet.
What do you need it for?
he cool evening breezes of Anytown, USA.
Let's see how this baby closes.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Morning, ma.
You're late!
Morning, dad.
I'm not 'dad' in the workplace.
My professional name is Mr. Costanza
and I will refer to you
as 'Costanza'. Morning, Braun.
Morning, George.
Two cream, no sugar.
What is Lloyd Braun doing here?
Your mother recommended him.
Yeah, of course she did.
That's all I ever heard growing up
is 'Why can't you be
more like Lloyd Braun?'
Did you know he was in a mental institution?
I didn't read his resume.
Another sale, Mr. Costanza.
Chalk me up on the big board.
What is this?
This is your lagging. Good work, Braun.
Good for you, Lloyd!
So Adam, I just talked to your father,
and, apology
accepted.
I'm not apologizing. It was great.
I told everyone.
Yeah, I know. Uh, by the way,
could you do me a favor
and tell Mitchell
Tanenbaum that I will be
unable to attend this Saturday.
Are you free Friday night?
I am, but that is not the point.
You are thirteen, and I am
in my early... 20s.
But I'm a man. The rabbi said so.
No. You are not a man.
It takes a *long* time to become
a man.
I mean, half my friends
aren't even there yet.
Well, if I'm not a man, then this
whole thing was a sham!
First,they said I was gonna get great
gifts, and then, somebody gives me
I renounce my religion!
Who wants cookies?
As of this moment, I am no
longer Jewish. I quit!
What?
Walnuts, mmmmmm.
You're late again, Costanza,
so listen up.
Starting tonight, we're
having a little sales contest.
The loser gets fired, the winner
gets a Waterpik.
You're not giving away our Waterpik!
Serenity now!
You know what?
It doesn't matter, because I quit!
I guess your mother was right
You never could compete
with Lloyd Braun!
You wanna sell computers?
I will show *you* how to sell computers!
Hello, Mr. Farneman. You wanna buy
a computer? No? Why not?
All right, I see! Good answer!
Thank you!
Serenity now!
Adam, you don't become a man
overnight. Look at your father.
It takes time. Patience, experience.
Uh, several careers of varying success.
And these are things
I look for in a man.
Well, that does me a lot of
good. 'Early 20s'!
Well, I'm sorry, sir, I tried.
So, that's the type of guy
you're looking for?
Uhh. I guess so. Why?
What is this?
Anytown, U.S.A. Hello?
Is Kramer home? Oh, hey.
Hello, neighbor.
Boy, those azaleas are really
coming in nicely.
Oh, you gotta mulch. You've got to.
You barbecuing tonight?
Right after the fireworks.
So, where do you want to eat tonight?
How about La Caridad again?
Again!? How much flan
can a person eat!?
Jerry, you've been yelling
at me all afternoon.
Well, I don't think more flan
is the answer!
Maybe I should just leave.
'Maybe'!?
Good-bye!
Double good-bye!
Hey, buddy!
Hey. Happy New Year!
Y'all come back reeeaall...
Did you and Patty just break up?
Yeah! In fact, she broke up with me!
And I don't want to talk about it!
Well, then you're free tonight.
You know what, I heard about
this great place called La Caridad.
That's the last thing she said to me.
She wanted to go there also,
but I wasn't in the mood.
Whoa. What is the matter?
It's Patty.
Jerry, you break up with
a girl every week.
What-what is this salty discharge?
Oh my God. You're crying.
This is horrible! I care!
Patty won't call me back.
I don't know if I can live without her.
She's really gotten to you,
hasn't she?
I don't know what's happening to me.
Simple. You let out one emotion,
all the rest will come  with it.
It's like Endora's box.
That was the mother on
Bewitched. You mean Pandora.
Yeah, well, she... had one, too.
Jerry, can I talk to you for a second?
That's it, that's it!
I warned you kids. I told you not
to play in front of my house.
This time, I'm keepin' it. And you're not
getting back your rock either!
Are you still down in
the dumps? Come on.
It's just a chick.
You ever heard of a little thing
called feelings?
Well, I got just the thing
to cheer you up. A computer!
Huh? We can check porn,
and stock quotes.
Porn quotes... I'm so lucky to have
a friend like you, George.
Ever  tell you how much I love you?
What?
I love you, George. Come here.
I-I'm already here.
I'm here. I'm here.
Uh, you know what?
If you want a computer,
call me. I-I gotta go.
Go wherever you want.
I'm still gonna love you.
Look what they did. Look what
they did to my house!
I turn my back for two seconds,
and they put shaving
cream all over my door.
You, I see
you! I'll teach these kids a lesson.
Where's that house I put
under your sink?
Hose under my sink.
I love *you*, Kramer!
I love you, too, buddy, and George
I don't want to hear it, Kramer!
Listen, when I give you the signal,
I want you to turn this
water on full blast.
What signal? What-what signal?
I'll yell, uh, 'Hoochie mama!'
If I do it, will you buy a computer?
On the signal, George. On the signal.
Only if you buy. I gotta make a sale.
I love you, Costanza.
Will you shut up?!
Now! Now, George!
Turn on the faucet!
George, turn on the faucet!
Hoochie mama! Hoochie mama!
So now the *other* Lippman kissed me.
Well, sure.
Well, sure. They're Jewish, and you're
a shiksa.  What?
It means a non-Jewish woman.
I know what it means,
but what does being a shiksa
have to do with it?
You've got 'shiksappeal'.
Jewish men love the idea of meeting
a woman that's not like their mother.
Oh, that's insane.
I'll tell you what's insane:
the price that I could get you
on a new desktop computer.
I am not buying a computer from you.
There's porn.
Even so.
Damn it!
Don't get me wrong, Mr. Lippman.
I-I'm very flattered that
you found me attractive enough to...
lunge at me. Huh. But the only reason
you like me is because I'm a shiksa.
That's simply not true.
If you weren't Jewish, you
wouldn't be interested in me.
You are wrong. I'll prove it.
Oh, no. Don't!
I renounce Judaism!
Oy vey!
What happened to you, pal?
Joey Zanfino and some
of the neighborhood kids.
They ambushed me
with a box of 'Grade A's.
Are you all right?
Oh, no. I'm fine.
Serenity now. Serenity now.
Serenity now.
So, you're using Frank's
relaxation method?
Jerry, the anger, it just melts
right off. Serenity now.
Look at this. Serenity now!
Hey, what happened to you?
Serenity!
Well. You are not gonna believe this.
Now Lippman is renounced.
This shiksa thing is *totally* out of control.
What is  *with* you people?
What are you looking at?
Sit down, Elaine.
Oh, no. Jerry, I can't take
any more gentle sobbing.
I've been thinking about what
it means to be complete.
Do you have an apple or anything?
Look at us, hurtling through
space on this big, blue marble.
Or a nectarine? I would absolutely
love a nectarine.
Looking everywhere for
some kind of meaning...
Why am I in such a fruit mood?
Ahh, banana!
When all the while, the real secret
to happiness has been
right in  front of us!
What?
Elaine...
Jerry, I've found a way
to beat Lloyd Braun!
I buy the computers myself, I
store 'em in your apartment.
Then, after I win the
contest, I bring 'em
all back and get my money back.
Ha ha! It's brilliant. What? What's
wrong with your leg?
I'm asking Elaine to marry me.
I'll store these over
at Kramer's apartment.
Elaine?
Uhh, Jerry,
I've got a lot goin' on with, uh,
Lippman  right now.
Lippman?
Yeah, and him too. What?!
Oh, yeah! I think George is calling me,
so I'm gonna go give him a hand
Come on! Come on!
Can I help you?
No. Stay! Stay. Stay.
Hey, Braun, Costanza's kicking your butt!
Watch how it's done. Oh, hello,
Mr. Vandelay?
Would you like to buy a computer?
Oh, really? Two dozen?
Costanza, you're white hot!
If you'd like to make a call,
please hang up and--
Hey, Braun, I got good news
and bad news.
And they're both the same: you're fired.
Costanza, you've won the water pik!
You're not gonna give away
that water pik!
You wanna bet? Serenity now,
serenity now!
You know, you should tell your dad
that 'serenity now' thing doesn't work.
It just bottles up the anger,
and eventually, you blow.
What do you know?
You were in the nut house.
What do you think put me there?
I heard they found a family
in your freezer
Serenity now. Insanity later.
What happened here,
Kramer?
Serenity now, serenity now...
Kramer!
Geez! Jerry, I didn't here you come in.
Yeah, the children,  they've
done sum redecorating.
Serenity now, serenity now.
You don't look well.
Well, that's odd, 'cause I feel perfectly
at peace with the world- uh!
eggs! you! Serenity now, serenity now,
serenity now.
Oh, I'm sorry. Look at me, I stepped
on your last rose.
Jerry, come on. Don't get upset about
it.There's always next spring.
Now will you excuse me for a moment.
Serenity nooooooooww!
Jerry! I did it! Haha! I beat Braun!
Serenity now!
Come on, wanna give me a hand
with the computers?
Serenity nooooowwwww!
Why couldn't you squeeze
one of those stupid
rubber balls to get your stress out?
Why did you have to destroy
*twenty-five* computers?
George, you listen to me. I owe ya one.
He's incorrigible.
You want to talk about it?
Oh, please don't tell me you love me again,
Jerry, I can't handle it.
George, letting my emotions out was
the best thing I've ever done.
Sure I'm not funny anymore, but there's
more to life than making shallow,
fairly-obvious observations. How about you?
All right... here goes...
Rabbi, is there anything I can do
to combat this Shiks-appeal?
Ha! Elaine, shiks-appeal is a myth,
like the Yeti,
or his North
American cousin, the Sasquatch.
Well, something's goin' on here,
'cause every able-bodied
Israelite in the county
is driving pretty strong to the hoop.
Elaine, there's much you don't understand
about the Jewish religion.
For example, did you know that rabbis
are allowed to date?
Well, what does that have to do...?
You know, a member of my congregation
has a timeshare in Myrtle  Beach.
Perhaps, if you're
not too busy, we could
wing on down after  the High Holidays?
Elaine? 'Lainie?
So, that's it. All of my darkest fears,
and... everything I'm
capable of. That's me.
Yikes. Well, good look with all that.
Where you going? I-I thought I could count
on you for a little compassion.
I think you scared me straight
All right, Jerome, I'm in.
What?
Maybe we should get married.
Maybe everything we need is
right here in front of us.
Jer... let's do it.
I tell ya, I don't see it happening.
What? What happened to the new Jerry?
He doesn't work here anymore.
Oh, well that's just *great!*
I love you, Jerry.
Right back at ya, Slick.
You know, all these years,
I've always wanted to see the
two of you get back together.
Well, that's because you're an idiot.
You single-handedly
brought Costanza and Son
to the brink of bankruptcy.
Well what about all the Lloyd Braun sales?
He's crazy.
His phone wasn't even hooked up.
He just liked ringing
that bell.
I told you to clean out this garage.
I have to put my car in!
This is a place of business.
I told you never to come in here.
Serenity now!
All right...
Dad, you really should lay off
the 'serenity now' stuff.
So, what am I supposed to say?
'Hoochie mama'?
Move your crap,
I'm comin' in!
No you're not! Hoochie mama!
Hoochie mama!