Yeah. Yeah. All right. Uh-huh.
Chinese food!
Oh! There's my Chinese food, I gotta run.
All you.
Who was it?
I did a show for a car dealership
and they're getting me a new SAAB.
What about your old car?
They couldn't get Kramer's blood out of it?
No, the engine clotted. You know
who set this whole thing up for me?
Frank Merman.
Fragile Frankie Merman?
I never liked that guy.
Why? He's harmless.
Every summer you guys
went to camp together.
I was jealous. Felt like
he was the summer me.
He was not the summer you.
Besides, you had a summer me.
Whitey Fisk, the guy who snuck
you into Last Tango in Paris.
I made him up.
So you never saw Last Tango in Paris?
No.
Too bad. It was erotic.
Well... I've had it with these
jackbooted thugs!
"Pottery Barn"?
I got three "Pottery Barn"
catalogs in one day.
That makes eight this month.
Mira Sorvino. Think she'd go out with me?
Why don't you just throw 'em out?
Oh, no. I've been saving them up
here in your apartment. And now,
it's payback time. "Pottery
Barn" is in for a world of hurt.
Can I have one? I need
one of those old-looking
phones. So you wanna grab a bite?
I can't. I gotta make the weekly call to the folks.
So call now.
I gotta prep. I need a
couple of anecdotes, a few
you-were-right-abouts.
It's a whole procedure
Wasn't Fragile Frankie the one
that used to run into the
woods every time he got upset?
That's him.
Is he still nuts?
What do you think?
They gave me a new car
for thirty minutes of "So,
who's from out of town?"
Seriously, is this the best
okra you've ever had, or what?
Mmm. De-lish.
Delish?
Delish. You know, short for delicious.
Oh, like scrump.
Yeah.
I'm gonna be late. See ya later.
Excuse me, can I borrow your ketchup?
Oh, sure.
Hello?
Hey, it's Georgie.
Let me put your father on the phone.
Ma!
Who is this?
Dad, it's me.
Hey, listen, I was at
Fortunoff's the other day, and,
you know what, you were right.
Chinese food.
Sorry, George, our Chinese food
just came. Talk to you later.
Chinese food?
Hey, you like sending out catalogs!?
How do you like gettin' 'em back!?
So, maybe they had Chinese food?
After dark?
Please. At their age, that's like swallowing stun
grenades.
Well, there's one way to check.
Where there's Chinese
food, there's leftovers.
Well, gentlemen. Lainie is... in love.
That's dynamite. Yeah, I'll look
for the Chinese food leftovers.
I met this guy! And it was like this, totally unreal,
fairy tale moment.
It wasn't Whitey Fisk, was it?
Oh, George's friend.
Whatever happened to him?
Nothing. Uh, I don't know. I gotta go.
So, this is beautiful. You, and Puddy,
and this new guy, in a
big pot of love stew.
Oh, yeah... Puddy.
Well, I won't fire him
until I see if this new
guy can... handle the workload.
Will you look at this?
More catalogs! "Omaha Steaks",
"Mac Warehouse", "Newsweek"?!
I can't stop all these
companies, so, I'm gonna attack
this problem at the choke point.
Stop the mail?
That's... even better!
So, where's the car?
This is it.
Inside the van?
It is the van!
Don't you remember, we
always talked about how cool
it would be to have
a van and just drive?
We were ten.
Come on. Let's take it for a spin.
I don't want a van.
Well, just tell him you want the SAAB.
You don't understand.
This is Fragile Frankie Merman.
When we were incamp, if you
upset him, he'd run out to the
woods, dig a hole, and sit in it.
Well, I have an idea.
Keep the van, and get
a bumper sticker that
says, "If this vans a-rockin',
don't come a-knockin'."
Always helpful.
Oh, Georgie, what are you doing here?
Just dropped in for a visit.
You, uh, you never called me back.
Uh... the phone broke.
Well, we got to get moving.
What? Where are you going?
We have a catered affair.
It's creative black tie. Move, woman.
No Chinese leftovers. George is gettin'
suspicious.
Elaine, I'm sorry I'm late.
I'm gonna be in the can.
Okay, Jack.
Can I use your phone?
Sure.
Puddy? It's Elaine. We're through.
Yeah, that's right. Again.
Nice captain's chairs, huh?
Aye, aye.
Oh, there's a spot. Just back up.
Hold on. There must be a truck backing up.
No, that's us.
Great. You know, Frankie,
I was wondering.  What if
I decided that it's silly
to drive a van, because, you know,
I live in New York City.
Is there maybe some way
I could exchange it?
You don't like the van?
No, no, no. Just hypothetically.
I gotta go to the park.
No! No, you don't! No woods.
I love the van. I'm a van guy.
Check it out.
Rain and sleet may not stop
them, but let's see them
get by... these bricks.
Where'd you get the bricks?
Jerry, the whole building is brick.
So you want to take a
ride with me out to Jersey?
I'm gonna try to sell the van to a lot.
A dealer? Are you insane?
No, take out an ad. Sell it privately.
I don't think I want to meet the people
that are in the market for a used van.
Come on, Jerry, just let me help you.
OK.
All right! OK!
Right, here we go.
Yeah. OK, so... "For sale.
For Sale A big,
juicy van."
And, ooh, you gotta put down,
"interesting trades considered."
I don't want to trade.
No, you don't have to.
It's all about tickling their buying bone.
Hey, you know what? This is all your mail.
They're puttin' it in my box now.
Oh, that's it. They have gone too far.
They keep pushing me, and pushing me.
Now I got no choice but to go
down there... and talk to them.
Hey, Jerry. I'd like you to meet someone.
This is Jack.
May I help you?
Yeah, I'd like to cancel my mail.
Certainly. How long would
you like us to hold it?
Oh, no, no. I don't think you
get me. I want out, permanently.
I'll handle this, Violet. Why don't you take
your three hour break?
Oh, calm down, everyone.
No one's cancelling any mail.
Oh, yes, I am.
What about your bills?
The bank can pay 'em.
The bank.
What about your cards and letters?
E-mail, telephones,
fax machines. Fedex, telex,
telegrams, holograms.
All right, it's true! Of
course nobody needs mail.
What do you think, you're so
clever for figuring that out?
But you don't know the
half ofwhat goes on here.
So just walk away,
Kramer. I beg of you.
Is everything all right here,
Postal Employee Newman?
Yes, sir, I believe everything is all squared away.
Isn't it, Mr. Kramer?
Oh, yeah. As long as I stop getting mail!
Welcome back.
Oh!
Quick for a... catered affair.
I don't know what you mean.
You ditched me. That's twice.
Now I demand to know what's going on!
George, we've had it with you.
Understand? We love you like a son,
but even parents have limits.
The breakups, the firings.
And every Sunday with the calls.
What my wife is trying to say
is that this is supposed to be our time.
I'm not following.
We're cuttin' you lose.
You're cuttin' me loose?
Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm
going to make love to your mother.
They don't want to see me anymore!
But this is what you've always wanted.
It is. I'm just not ready yet.
Aw, that's kind of sweet.
Ah, shut up, Jerry.
My parents think they can ignore me.
Heh heh.  Well, they
better think again.
Oh, no. George, please.
What are you going to do?
You remember my cousin
Rhisa? I'm gonna date her.
Mother of God.
One little wink. She'll
freak out, tell my parents.
They'll be all over
me. Who is this guy?
That guy Elaine's dating
seems really familiar to me.
I think he may have been a
comedian I worked with one time.
Wait a minute, what is this?
Nobody beats me, because I'm the Wiz!
I'm the Wiz!
That is the guy!
Elaine's in love with the Wiz guy?
No, she thinks she's in
love with him. But she's
just remembering this old commercial.
That's pretty pathetic.
I know. They're not even related.
I'm gonna get going.
Hey, have fun at the... family reunion.
So, what do you know
about this Jack fellow?
Isn't he the best?
Yeah, nobody beats him.
What kind of work does he do?
Oh, right now he's a fact
checker for New York Magazine.
It's not much, but it has
a certain type of quiet dignity.
Right, quiet dignity. As opposed to, say,
this?
Nobody beats me, because I'm the Wiz! I'm the Wiz!
Oh no!
Hello? Yeah, the van is still for sale. Sure,
come on buy.
Yeah, I called about the van.
Some more merlot?
Yeah, thanks.
Sure. You know, Rhisa.
I've always found you... very attractive.
What?
I know it may sound shocking.
But, I just can't stop myself from...
wanting you.
You want to borrow money, right?
No, no. I-I just want us to be... together.
All right.
All right?
Let's go for it.
Well... we could dance around it a little first.
Nah. Let's be bad, George.
Let's be really... bad.
So, how come you're selling it?
You know why I'm
selling it. I hate it.
How many miles?
Two.
City or highway?
Look, do you really want
to buy this thing, or what?
Hey, hey. Take it
easy. I'm not gonna be
pressured. I'll walk away right now.
Is this thing bent?
I'm not paying for that.
All right, just get out of here.
All right, look. I'm going to be honest.
I'm very interested in the
van.
OK, fine. "What do I have to do to put you
in this van today?"
Well, I don't really have any money.
But it says right here,
"interesting trades considered".
You put that in!
And I'm glad I did. Here.
You want to trade me an undershirt?
No, I want to trade you screen
legend Anthony Quinn's undershirt.
He took this off to do sit-ups
in the park and I nabbed it.
That's disgusting.
Well, it's my final offer.
You dumped me for some
idiotic TV pitchman.
Look, I'm sorry, Puddy.
It-it was a mistake.
So, let's just put it behind us,
and we can continue like
this never happened.
Gee, I don't know. What
if we're out somewhere
and you see the Maytag  repairman.
You're not taking me back?
That's right.
He's not idiotic. He's the Wiz.
And nobody beats him. Nobody...
Here you go. Mail is evil. Pass it
on. Hey, mail blows.
Fax it to a friend.
Why does this dummy have
a bucket on its head?
Because we're blind to their tyranny.
Then shouldn't you
be wearing the bucket?
Yeah. Move along, Betty.
Is this, uh, Jerry Seinfeld's van?
Well, not anymore. He traded it
to me for some Hollywood memorabilia.
I'm, uh, I'm so stupid.
What?
I'm so stupid. Uh, excuse me. I'm sorry.
Yeah, nice to meet you.
She's into it?
She's leaving me dirty messages
on my answering machine.
So have your parents
found out about it?
She wants to keep it quiet.
She wants to keep it
quiet. She... thinks we have
a real future  together.
Brave new world, alright.
Hey, you guys.
Hey, how's the anti-mail campaign going?
Oh, it's fantastic. We were out in front
of the post office today,
and not one person went in.
It's Sunday.
Why is the mailman wearing a bucket?
Huh?
Well, it symbolizes our persecution.
Then... shouldn't you
be wearing the bucket.
Hey, I want my van keys back.
Oh, well. I, uh, thought we made
a deal for Quinn's t-shirt.
Are you insane? Give 'em to me.
No, I can't, I can't. See, I
told Frank he could borrow it.
Yeah, he wants to move some of
George's stuff into storage.
Wait a minute? He's picking up the van tonight?
This is perfect.
I'll drive Rhisa to someplace
romantic. Then when my father slides
the door open, I'm in the van
kissing his brother's daughter.
Oh, listen, Jerry. One
of your friends came by
and he was very upset
that I had your wheels.
Oh, no, not Frankie.
Well, I didn't catch his name, but then
he went running into the park.
Oh, no, the woods! The hole!
Kramer, what the hell are you doing?
I know, I'm gonna switch
the bucket to something else.
Not that!
What?
You're in trouble, Kramer.
I shouldn't even be talking to you, but
I'm telling you as a friend.
Here's how it's going
to happen: you may be
walking. Maybe on a crisp,
autumn day just like today.
When a mail truck will slow
beside you, and a door will open,
and a mailman you
know, maybe even trust,
will offer to give you a lift.
Are you through?
No! And no one will ever see you again!
Yes. No, wait! OK, yes.
Quick! Get in!
Oh, no, no, no. That's exactly how you said it
was going down.
There's another way it can go down,
and it's going down right now!
No. You said a mailman I know,
and you're a mailman I know!
I know you know, but
you don't know what I know.
Frankie, is that you?
My name is Edgar.
Have a nice night.
Thank you.
Stupid... so stupid! Jerry?
All right, George. I'm ready.
Yeah, hold on. I'm,
uh, I'm just trying to get
a reading on my dashboard compass.
Where are my parents?
Is this Seinfeld's van? Seinfeld's van?
Seinfeld's van?!
Wait. What's he saying?
I think he's saying "Son
of Sam"! Oh, my God!
No, they caught him.
I knew it wasn't Berkowitz!
So I told him, "Hit the road.
I'm going back with Jack."
Elaine, that's the second
piece of good news today.
Really, what was the first?
They're bringing me back. Yeah. I'm the Wiz
again.
I'm the Wiz! I'm the Wiz!
Well what, what about
your fact-checking job?
Oh... here's a fact. Uh,
I'm... the Wiz! I'm the Wiz
and noooobody beats me!
Frankie... come on out of
there.
You hate the van.
But I'm keeping it.
As much as I hate the idea
of being a van guy,it's much
better than hanging out here
with the nocturnal dirt people.
So, can we go for a ride?
Yeah, let's just get out of here.
Are you done
with that?
Good. He left the door unlocked.
Why did Kramer have to
park the van in the woods?
Isn't it obvious?
There are no parking meters out here.
Hey, look at this. Hoochie
mama!
Oh, my goodness.
What have they done to you here?
Huh? Who are you?
Well, you can just call me Henry.
Henry Atkins? The postmaster general?
Last time I checked.
Henry... can I get out of here now?
Oh, oh. Sit a bit. Sit a bit.
I mean, after all, I drove
all the way up here from D.C. just to talk to you.
I even had to cancel a round
of golf with the secretary
of state. Do you like golf, Mr. Kramer?
Kramer, I've been, uh, reading some
of your material  here.
I gotta be honest with you: you make
a pretty strong case.
I mean, just imagine. An army
of men in wool pants running
through the neighborhood handing
out pottery catalogs, door to door.
Well, it's my job. And I'm pretty damn serious
about it.
In addition to being a postmaster,
I'm a general.
And we both know, it's the
job of a general to, by God, get things done.
So maybe you can understand why I get
a little irritated when someone
calls me away from my golf.
I'm sorry.
I'm very very sorry.
I think we got a stack of mail out
at the desk that belongs to you.
Now, you want that mail,
don't you Mr. Kramer?
Sure do!
Now, that's better.
Geez. Newman?
Tell the world my story.
Hey, George!
Jerry! Hey, that's the guy!
What? George Costanza, Frankie Merman.
Oh. The summer me.
The winter me.
You must be George's cousin.
Girlfriend.
What is that? That van's a-rockin'.
Don't go a-knockin'.
Oh, my god!
Now you gotta sell this van.
Oh, yeah.
What you saw in that van
was a natural expression
of a man's love for his lady.
Your father's right. It's beautiful.
And it was safe.
Oh, God...
Now if you'll excuse me. Once again, your mother and I...
Oh... make it stop.