When are they gonna have the flying cars, already?
Yeah, they have been promising that for a while...
Years.
When we were kids, they made it seem like
it was right around the corner.
I think Ed Begley Jr has one.
No.
That's just electric.
What about Harrison Ford?
He had one in the Blade Runner.
That was a cool one.
What's the competition,
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang?
What do you think the big holdup is?
The government is very touchy
about us being in the air.
Let us run around on the ground
as much as we want.
Anything in the air is a big production.
Yeah, right.
And what about the floating cities?
And the underwater bubble cities?
It's like we're living in the '50s here.
It's good suspension!
Would you stop it?
You'll have plenty of time to destroy it
after I get it.
Hey, George, I'm buyin' this car.
What is wrong with you?
You never tell 'em you like the car.
You're not sure what you want.
You don't even know why you're here.
That vein again.
I'm starving.
We should have had lunch first...
It'll be twenty minutes.
I told ya, Puddy's getting me an insider deal.
Since when is Elaine's boyfriend selling cars?
I thought he was a mechanic.
I guess he graduated.
That's an easy move.
Go from screwing you behind your back
to screwing you right to your face.
Thank you.
Puddy's just gonna give you the car, huh?
Youll see.
First they stick you with the undercoating,
rust-proofing, dealer prep.
Suddenly you're on your back like a turnip.
Alright.
Calm down.
My father had a car salesman buddy.
He was gonna fix him up real nice.
Next thing I know, I'm getting dropped off
in a Le Car with a fabric sunroof.
All the kids are shoutin at me:
"Hey, Le George!
Bonjour, Le George!
"Lets stuff Le George in Le Locker!"
Jerry, I don't think
this thing is hooked up right.
Alright, were goin in.
You've got a good eye, there.
I see you've noticed
the uni-body construction.
I'm Rick.
Are you looking to buy or lease?
Uh, borrow.
It's for my friend.
Yeah, hell be buying...
Maybe I should talk to him.
Oh, I don't think so.
No, he's an entertainer.
You know, all over the place.
That's where I come in.
I see. So, youre his manag-
- Yeah, neighbor. That's right.
Why don't we take this boiler out
for a shakedown?
Look at these salesmen.
The only thing these guys fear is the walk-out.
No matter what they say,
you say, "I'll walk out of here right now!"
Can I help you with something?
Hold it!
One more step and were walking!
George.
Sorry, we're just waiting for David Puddy.
He is.
You don't know what I'm doing here.
Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
My new salesman boyfriend took me out
to celebrate his promotion.
Ah.
Where'd you go?
Uh, to a restaurant.
- Arby's.
I had the roast beef...
So, Puddy, I decided
I'm gonna go with another 900 convertible.
Alright.
Classic.
High-five.
David, can you tell me
where the Xerox machine is?
Oh, sure, babe.
Salesman-only copy room right there.
Oh.
Hey, come on, guys.
Ill show you the 900.
Yeah, you show us the 900.
And look at these features, Mr Kramer:
Anti-lock breaks,
automatic climate control.
Uh, make a right at this corner, please.
An adjustable steering wheel and...
Oh, Mr.
Kramer, you missed the turn...
No.
No, I didn't.
Well, that's okay.
We'll make this next right
and swing around to get back to the dealership.
Well, it's a test drive, right?
I never drive around here.
If I'm gonna recommend this car,
I need to see that it'll handle my daily routine.
So where are we going?
Just a little place
I like to call "You'll see".
I'm starving. You got any of those
free donuts you use to soften people up?
By the service department.
Alright, remember:
no rust-proofing.
Commit to nothing.
If you have to speak - mumble.
Au revoir, Le George.
Don't think it can't happen!
So, Puddy,
this is a pretty good move for you, huh?
No more grease monkey.
I don't care for that term.
Oh.
Sorry, I didn't know...
No, I don't know too many monkeys
who could take apart a fuel injector.
I saw one once that could do sign language.
Yeah, I saw that one.
Uh...
Koko.
Yeah, Koko.
Right, Koko.
That chimp's alright.
High-five.
Hey, hey, hey!
What's goin on here?
You didn't agree to anything, did ya?
No.
We both just saw the same monkey.
Well, I got screwed on the donuts.
There were none left.
Well, there's a vending machine.
I can show you where it is.
Hey, gimme a dollar.
Where's your money?
I'm here helpin' you.
Hey. Where's Puddy?
The copy machine is broken.
He-he-heh.
That's what they want you to think.
Hey, Elaine, have you noticed your boyfriend
has developed an annoying little habit?
The squinting?
No.
The staring?
He keeps asking me
to give him a high-five.
I thought all guys do that.
Slapping hands is the lowest form
of male primate ritual.
In fact, even some of them have moved on.
They're doing sign language now.
It's that bad?
What do you think the Nazis were doing?
That was the heil-five.
Isn't that from your act,
like ten years ago?
It was a good bit in the 80s,
and it's still relatable today.
Good news.
We got a 900 in black.
That's the hot color.
High-five.
Um, David, you know what?
Can you come help me fix the copy machine?
You owe me five.
Twix...
B-5.
Ah, come on!
Ah, excuse me.
Do you have change of a dollar?
No.
Could I trade you for another dollar?
Don't have one.
Excuse me.
When your wallet was open,
I glanced inside,
and I couldn't help but notice
that you had several crisp dollar bills.
You're incorrect.
Perhaps you could look again, please?
I'm very hungry.
We had donuts earlier.
I guess everyone here
enjoys giving the old scroogie, huh?
Youre all doing a hell of a job!
What I would do with you...
Mr Kramer, we're really not allowed
to use the cars to run errands.
No, look, Rick.
I'm very close to giving this car, that my
celebrity friend is considering, my full endorsement.
Let's see if I can get a smile from these femininas...
Hey ladies!
It's a Saab 900!
What do you think?
Can I interest you in a little
supplemental restraint?
Geez!
I think the candy comes out over there.
People drop change down here, Jerry.
And they're too lazy to pick it up.
Either that, or they've got a weird little hang-up
about lying face-down in filth.
Why don't you just go to the cashier?
The cashier is at lunch -
which is where I'd like to be.
How much was under there?
I think something bit me.
I just need another nickel.
Hey, Puddy thinks I should go for the CD player.
What do you think?
He's got a live one.
Hes just reeling his big fish in!
Hey, can I have my dollar back?
It's wrinkled.
It's worthless.
Come on!
Jump!
They just put out some more donuts.
They did?
Last one.
Well, just one more errand
and we can head back.
Actually, it looks like
we're gonna need some gas.
Oh? Well, how much gas do you think
is in there right now?
Well, its on "E".
You know, uh, oftentimes, Jerry -
he lend me his car,
and I find myself in a situation
where the car is almost out of gas.
But, for a variety of reasons,
I don't want to be the one responsible
for purchasing costly gasoline.
So, you want to know how far
you can drive your friend's car for free.
Well, I make it up to him in other ways.
As you will see, the candy bar is paid for
and yet remains dangling in the machine.
Hey, it's gone.
Where is my Twix?
What?
That guy's eating it!
Well, how do you know that one's yours?
It was dangling!
There were only two left in the machine!
He must've bought one, and gotten both.
Sir, are you gonna buy a car?
No!
Hey!
I can see you!
That is my Twix!
Paper jam...
Got it!
- Hey!
On the flip side.
David, um, I...
Don't leave me hanging.
You're a salesman now -
and the high-five is...
It's very grease monkey.
What did I tell you about that?
I'm sorry, but
the high-five is just so stupid.
Oh yeah?
I'll tell you what's stupid.
You, stupid.
Well, that is really mature.
Yeah?
So are you.
You're the grease monkey.
That doesn't make any sense.
I am leaving.
Yeah, if you leave, we're through.
Fine!
We're through!
Oh, so you're leaving?
That's right.
High-five!
On the flip side!
Taking me to Arby's...
Hey!
Wh-where are you...?
Lets finish this up.
Did you two break up?
That chick's whacked.
We're history.
I just left out a couple of things:
rust-proofing...
"Rust-proofing"?
Transport charge, storage surcharge,
additional overcharge,
finder's fee...
"Finder's fee"?
It was on the lot!
Yeah, that's right.
Floor mats, keys...
"Keys"?
How are you gonna start it?
Excuse me.
I believe you just ate my Twix bar.
It was dangling.
And when you purchased your Twix bar,
you got a little freebie,
and you never bothered to ask why,
or seek out its rightful owner.
First of all, it wasn't a Twix.
It was a 5th Avenue bar.
You must think I'm pretty stupid.
That was no 5th Avenue bar.
I can see the crumb
right there in the corner of your lip!
That is a cookie!
And we all know that Twix is
the only candy bar with the cookie crunch.
That's a little nougat.
Nougat?
Please.
I think I've reached the point in my life
where I can tell between nougat and cookie.
So, let's not just say things
that we both know are obvious fabrications.
You know, you're getting a little vein there...
I know about the vein!
I can't believe this guy...
Hey, George!
I'm starving!
No, last one.
Listen, you gotta help me out.
Elaine and Puddy just broke up.
He treats me just like a regular customer now!
I tried to tell you, but you wouldn't listen.
No-ho-ho!
You were gonna get a deal, huh?
There's no laws in this place.
Anything goes!
It's Thunderdome!
Is someone helping you?
Stay back!
Where is it now?
There's still some overlap
between the needle and the slash below the "E".
How long are you gonna go?
Oh, I've been in the slash many times.
This is nothing.
You'll get used to it.
Just put it out of your mind.
Have you ever been completely below the slash?
Well, I almost did once, and I blacked out.
When I came to,
the car was in a ditch, and the tank was full.
I don't know who did it,
and I never got to thank them...
Mr Kramer, the road!
So, listen, Puddy.
When we first started this deal,
I thought things were gonna be different.
Now, if you want to play hardball, I got my friend
George here, and he can play pretty hard... ball.
George, vein it up.
Alright, Puddy, listen, and listen good:
I need to know the name of that mechanic
that walks around here.
Big guy, a liar.
Short name.
Sam? Moe? Sol?
George!
Can we focus on the car here?
I'm starving!
I can feel my stomach sucking up against my spine.
Jerry, I just need your signature here,
and we'll get you that yellow car ready to go.
Yellow?
I wanted black.
I can't give you black at that price.
George, would you help me, please?
Yes.
This is wrong!
Sing it, sister!
Just because a candy bar
fails to fall from its perch,
does not imply transfer of ownership.
Moe, Sol, or... Lem
is not gonna get away with this!
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Hey, George!
Is it just the angle I'm looking from?
No, Sir.
We are down there.
Oh, this is amazing!
Oh, I've never felt so alive!
Alright.
I'm satisfied.
We better get some gas.
What?
Well, we can't stop now.
What do you mean?
We have to keep going. All the way back
to the dealership. That was the plan.
There was no plan.
Well, let's make it the plan!
Lets just go for it!
Like Thelma and Louise.
What, they drove to a dealership?
No, they drove off a cliff.
You are one sick mama...
I like it.
Mr.
Kramer, the road!
Hello?
Elaine, you've got to get
back down to the dealer.
Puddy is screwing me on this car,
which is yellow now!
Who is this?
Elaine!
What?
You gotta get back together with Puddy
so I can make this deal.
You know, just that you cared enough to call
means so much, Jerry.
You've gotta get back together.
Anyway, it's thousands of dollars!
Oh, I don't know...
Come on. Then you don't have to see him again
till my 15,000-mile check.
Well, will you pay my cab fare out there?
Fine.
And I didn't like that roast beef,
so how about some lunch?
No.
No lunch.
I'll hang the phone up right now!
- Alright! Lunch!
I'll see ya.
- Bye.
Everybody's ripping me off!
I'd like to report a problem
with one of your mechanics.
When did you bring the car in?
Yeah, right.
I'm gonna get my car repaired at a dealership!
Why don't I just flush my money down the toilet?
Sir, what exactly is the problem?
One of your guys - Kip, or Ned, short name -
stole my Twix candy bar!
Are you saying
he grabbed the candy bar away from you?
He might as well have!
I caught him, and his face
was covered in chocolate and cookie crumbs.
I thought you said it was a Twix.
Oh, it was.
But he claimed it was a 5th Avenue bar.
Maybe it was.
Oh, no. No.
Twix is the only candy with the cookie crunch.
What about the $100,000 bar?
No.
Rice and caramel.
Nougat?
- No.
Positive?
- Please.
You know they changed the name
from "$100,000 Bar" to "100 Grand"?
All I want is my 75 cents back,
an apology, and for him to be fired!
I remember when you used to be able
to get a Hershey for a nickel.
What's the one with the
swirling chocolate in the commercial?
They all have
swirling chocolate in the commercial!
Not Skittles.
Dad, I told you you could sit here
only if you don't talk.
You make your father sit here all day?
He likes it!
Alright!
Do you mind?
I have the window!
Now, what are you gonna do about my Twix?
Twix has too much coconut.
No!
There's no coconut!
I'm allergic to coconut.
I'm not.
A nickel!
Cab receipt.
Hey, Puddy.
I'm with a customer.
No, no.
No, Elaine, the car can wait.
What's important is
you two getting back together.
Then we'll talk about the car.
I don't want to get back with her.
She's too bossy.
David...
Okay.
Now, I know this is an important decision.
Why don't we all just sit down and talk about it?
Come on, come on.
Now, look.
You both find each other attractive, right?
Right.
Clearly, no one else can stand to be
with either one of you...
I guess.
- Good point.
Alright.
Now, what do I have to do
to put you two in a relationship today?
Cars can go on empty,
but not us humans, huh, fella?
I'll get us a couple of Twix bars.
No, no coconut for me.
Alright, I'll get ya a Mounds bar.
Keep the engine running.
No, man!
Not the gas!
But it needs it, Kramer!
It needs it bad!
Do you think that this'll make you happy?
Cause it won't!
Ah, you can just go on without me.
Listen to me.
When that car rolls into that dealership
and that tank is bone dry,
I want you to be there with me
when everyone says: "Kramer and that other guy,
oh, they went further to the left
of the slash than anyone ever dreamed!"
Maybe we better get moving.
It's good to have you back, Stan.
It's Rick, by the way.
No time!
Mr.
Costanza, I really don't have time for this.
Now, if this mechanic guy was in fact
eating a 5th Avenue bar, as he claimed,
wouldn't you agree he would have no problem
picking one out from a candy line-up?
"Candy line-up"?
I've spent the last hour
preparing ten candy bars,
with no wrappers of identification
of any kind, for him to select from.
It took you an hour?
Only I hold the answer key
to their true candy identities.
And so, without further ado, I give you...
the candy line-up.
Hey, Willie, check it out!
Free candy!
That's my candy line-up!
Where are all my cards?
They're all on the floor!
How many Twix does that make for you today?
Like, 8 Twix?!
No.
Hey, this Clark bar is good.
Its a Twix!
They're all Twix!
It was a setup!
A setup, I tell ya!
And you've robbed it!
You've all screwed me again!
Now, gimme one!
Gimme a Twix!
They're all gone.
Twix!
What was that?
There's a mental hospital right near here.
Alright.
Elaine, David, I believe we have a deal here in principle:
Arby's - no more than once a month.
In exchange, Elaine comes to your softball game
and doesn't read a book.
That's not bad.
- I can live with that.
So, you're back together?
Yeah.
Alright, alright.
Alright, that's enough!
Let's get back to my deal.
That undercoating -
that's a rip-off, isn't it, David?
Oh, we don't even know what it is.
So, I'm getting the insiders' deal?
Insiders' deal.
High-five.
There's the dealer!
Hey!
We did it!
We pulled it off!
I can't believe it!
Where's the needle?
Oh, it broke off, baby!
Woo, hoo, hoo!
Oh, Mr Kramer, I gotta thank you.
I learned a lot.
Things are gonna be different for me now.
Well, that's a weird thing to say.
I wonder how much longer we could have lasted.
Yeah, yeah.
I wonder.
This is nice.
What kind of car is this?
Caprice Classic.
You couldn't just give him one high-five?
It's like the wave at ball games.
Air quotes.
The phrase "Don't go there."
Someone's gotta take a stand!
This Arby's is good.
So, George, I still don't understand -
how was that a setup?
And who were you trying to set up, anyway?
The mechanic or the manager?
I don't know.
All of them.
Theyre all crooks!
Besides, I couldn't get
all different candy bars anyway.
What was that?
I think there's a mental hospital near here.
Very near.
Well, I think we stopped.
You can probably let go of my hand now.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I'll think about it...
Do you have my card?