Cup of tea with lemon.
What happened to your voice?
I was screaming at hecklers all night.
The last time I open for a rodeo.
Well, Jerry, I been thinking.
I've gotten as far as I can go
with George Costanza.
Is this the suicide talk
or the nickname talk?
The nickname.
George. What is that?
It's nothing.
It's got no snap, no zip.
I need a nickname
that makes people light up.
You mean like...
Liza!
But I was thinking...
T-bone.
But there's no "T" in your name.
What about G-bone?
There's no G-bone.
There's a G-spot.
That's a myth.
T-bone, the ladies
are gonna love ya.
Why did they hire you for a rodeo?
They heard I opened
for Kenny Rogers once.
Didn't he throw you off a bus
in the middle of Alabama?
Oh, I had that coming to me.
You know, Kenny Rogers has a--
Why did you get a maid?
You don't have to whisper.
She knows she's a maid.
Where did you get her?
I hired her from a service!
All done.
Thank you. Nice job.
Is this mine?
Yeah.
What?
Come on, Jerry.
You didn't notice?
Notice what?
She's not really even a maid.
Oh.
She wants to be an actress.
Or a, uh, model...
or a dancer...
or a... news woman.
- News woman, uh-huh.
Hey.
Well, bad news, boys.
My life is over.
My girlfriend's moving away.
You have a girlfriend?
Jerry, where have you been?
At a rodeo.
Where's she moving?
Downtown.
Downtown New York?
Yeah. I don't know if I can handle
one of these long-distance relationships.
It's like 10 minutes by subway.
I don't know.
Well, you've got a maid.
It's a whole different world downtown.
Different Gap, different Tower Records--
And she's a 646.
What? What is that?
That's the new area code.
They've run out of 212s,
so all the new numbers are 646.
I was a 718 when I first moved here.
I cried every night.
Listen. Heads up, Elaine.
I'm gonna have to stop by later
and pick up a fax.
At work?
No. At your apartment.
I don't have a fax machine.
Here we go.
Well, now what are we gonna do?
See? This is why you should get
a fax and a Xerox.
And a dead bolt.
Are you sure you don't have one?
Because there's a lot of stuff
in my apartment I've never seen.
Then maybe you have a fax machine.
You just blew my mind.
Let's order lunch.
Mary, I will have a chef's salad.
Turkey sandwich.
T-bone steak.
For lunch?
Well, I am just a T-bone kinda guy.
Love that T-bone.
In fact, you might as well call me--
That sounds good.
I'll have one, too.
Watkins, you're having a T-bone?
I love 'em.
Well, then we should call you T-bone.
Uh, no. No, we shouldn't.
T-bone!
T-bone! T-bone! T-bone!
T-bone! T-bone!
Hello?
What?
You have 57 messages.
Message one...
Message two...
Message three...
Hey, it's George. Listen, I-
Message four...
Kramer!
Hello?
Well Cindy, the place looks great.
Thanks Jerry.
Gotta run.
Ok, I'll see ya.
Hi, Elaine.
All right!
Fooling around with your maid.
That is a wise decision.
Elaine, do you think I would go
willy-nilly into a situation
so obviously fraught with
potential complications?
You are paying a woman to
come to your house and sleep with you.
No. I pay her to clean.
The rest is--
What? A health plan?
I was going to say,
"Being a good host."
But the point is,
we have our personal relationship,
and we have our work relationship.
They're separate and, I think,
somewhat sophisticated.
So you consider this a relationship?
Yes, I do.
Oh. Have you been out?
Yes, we have.
Where did you go?
The store.
To get what?
Stuff.
Cleaning supplies?
And gum.
There's nothing more sophisticated than
diddling the maid and then chewing some gum.
She's not a maid.
She might be a news woman!
Hey.
Well, I just saw Madeline off.
Yeah. She's in a cab and--
on her way.
I miss her already.
Hey, Kramer--
What was it you were having
faxed to my house every 30 seconds?
Well, I signed up for
a food delivery service.
"Now We're Cooking".
That's a play on words.
You know, they're faxing me
the menus from some restaurants.
Which ones?
Well, all of them.
It's the deluxe package.
So this is never gonna stop?
Well, it better not.
Paid for the whole year.
So, should I pick those up later?
You can pick 'em up right now.
I wonder if anyone knows he's here.
If he just disappeared...
would anybody notice?
All right, miss Benes, all finished.
Here's your new number.
646? What is this?
That's your new area code.
I thought 646 was
just for new numbers.
This is a new number.
No, no, no, no.
It's not a new number.
It's-- just a changed number.
See? It's not different.
It's the same, just-- changed.
Look.
I work for the phone company.
I've had a lot of experience
with semantics,
so don't try to lure me
into some maze of circular logic.
You know, I could've killed you,
and no one would've known.
I could've killed you,
Kramer, you're still on the phone?
Madeline and I are watching Quincy together.
Jerry, you know this comes on
at the same time here as it does there?
Really? It's Tuesday here.
What day is it there?
Jerry's teasing.
Uh-oh! Commercial.
Oh, you going to the bathroom?
Yeah. I'll go, too.
Madeline stays here.
Hey, T-bone!
No. No T-bone.
No T-bone?
Hey, is that T-bone?!
No! There's no T-bone!
Well, why no T-bone?
Why no T-bone?
'Cause Neil Watkins from accounting
is T-bone!
I'm back.
Hey, you wanna play cards over the phone?
Oh, hey, uh, listen, Jerry, uh,
laundry's piling up there.
You might want to tell your girlfriend.
Your girlfriend is doing your laundry?
He's sleeping with his maid!
You're sleeping with the maid?
Yes.
I've done that.
Did you ever eat an ostrich burger?
No.
You're probably one of those women
who doesn't like to give out her number.
No, I'm not.
Here you go.
646?
It's a new area code.
What area?
New Jersey?
No, no. It's right here in the city.
It's the same as 212.
They just multiplied it by 3,
and then they added one
to the middle number. It's the same.
Do I have to dial a one first?
I'm really kinda seeing somebody.
Yeah? Well, so am I!
Excuse me. Can I talk to you
for a second there, Watkins?
It's T-bone.
The thing is...
I'm supposed to be T-bone.
You're not a T-bone.
You're a perfect George.
What?
Now, you listen to me!
Hey, look at George.
He's giving it to T-bone.
He's jumping up and down
like some kind of monkey.
Hey, what was the name of that monkey
that could read sign language?
All right, you can have T-bone.
Stop crying.
I'm not crying.
And I shouldn't have said that
about your wife.
Please accept my apologies.
OK, everybody, uh...
I have an announcement to make.
From now on, I will be known as--
Koko the monkey.
What?
Koko! Koko! Koko!
Thank you both for being here.
Um, excuse me.
I live in the building.
Did something happen to Mrs. Krantz?
She passed.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
A quick question--
Did she by any chance
have a 212 phone number?
I can't find my earring.
Oh, here it is.
Listen, can I borrow your suitcases?
Yeah. It's in your closet.
No, no, no. I looked.
They're behind my skis and my tennis racket.
Thanks, buddy.
Where you going?
Well, I'm getting out of town.
I'm gonna visit Madeline for the weekend.
You know, this place
is looking kinda messy.
What happened to Cindy?
Well, she's here.
She just didn't get around to it.
Hi, Kramer.
Thanks, Jerry.
Bye.
Now, what's the matter?
What did I just pay for?
Uh-oh.
You're a john.
Koko?
Koko.
Well, it's probably
the most intelligent ape there is.
Yeah.
So, how's Cindy the maid?
Everything's going great
except, basically, I'm paying for sex.
Tell me about it.
I went out with this girl last week.
First I had to pay for dinner, then--
No, George.
She's coming over and not cleaning.
It's like I'm seeing a prostitute.
How much you pay this maid?
40.
40?
I'm paying 60 to my maid.
She doesn't do laundry
and I'm getting nothing.
Once she pinched my ass,
but I don't know what that was.
I don't know what this is.
Hey, hey, hey.
Look at that.
Ooh.
Jerry, you wouldn't believe
what it's like down there.
Taxicab drivers are insane.
You know, everybody is in a hurry.
I can't eat with you leaning over like this.
Just look straight forward.
Well, now I can't see Jerry.
I look about the same.
What?
I was talking to him.
Never mind.
Come on. What'd he say?
Jerry, come on. What'd you say?
What?
Come on. Where'd you go?
Go back.
Come on. What did you say?
I said, never mind.
Yeah. I know that.
I hate the counter.
Hey.
Who's that?
Well, I got a 212 number
from this little old lady
in my building, Mrs. Krantz.
Oh, she didn't mind?
No. She died.
Hey, that's great.
What happened to Mrs. Krantz?
Elaine got a new number
because she died.
Newman died?
What did he say?
Some new kind of pie.
I'll try a piece.
All right, who's down there?
Hey, there's a booth.
Hey, Elaine.
Oh, hi.
Did you hear about Newman?
What?
Hey.
So how's it going at work?
They get tired of it?
Oh, yeah.
Double zero?
It's "oo".
As in "oo oo ah ah."
Your nickname's Koko?
One of the girls down at the maid service
is named Coco.
Really? Coco?
Yeah. Coco.
That girl's all right.
You know, if I could get
this Coco woman down to Kruger,
they wouldn't be able
to call me Koko anymore
because Kruger would never allow 2 Kokos.
Sounds like he runs a real tight ship.
Say good-bye to Koko.
Good-bye, Koko.
Jerry, this relationship is killing me.
The distance, the longing,
the distance, the--
You know, I didn't realize it,
but I'm a needy person.
Kramer, maybe
this relationship isn't for you.
Oh, yeah?
So what am I supposed to do,
be more like you?
All sealed up in here,
emotionally unavailable,
paying scrubwomen
for sexual favors?
No! Jerry, I won't be like you!
Never! I'll never be like you!
What was that?
I didn't hear anything.
All right, I'm taking off.
- OK.
Aren't you forgetting something?
Oh, right!
Hey, it was great seeing you again.
I love your outfit.
No. My money.
For what?
For my maid services.
You booked me for today.
But you didn't really do any work.
I made the bed.
But you took a nap in it.
So?
I thought that was kind of
girlfriend bedmaking.
No. That was the maid.
Well, who took the nap?
The girlfriend.
$40 seems kind of steep
for a nap.
So, what are you saying?
That I'm a bad maid
or some kind of a prostitute?
Ho, ho... ho!
Hold on.
Let's keep this sophisticated.
You know, I don't think I want to be
your girlfriend or your maid.
So is this a breakup/quitting?
Yeah. Don't ever call me
or hire me again.
Oh, yeah?
Well, then we're through!
And you're fired!
Sign here.
Yes! 212.
Hey, what happened to the guy
I had last time?
Oh, you know, it's an odd thing.
He went out on a job, never came back.
Nobody knows what happened.
All right!
I am back in the game.
Hello?
Gammy!
No. You got the wrong number, kid.
Gammy Krantz?
It's your grandson Bobby.
Why haven't you called?
Oh...nuts.
Do you hate me
'cause of my lazy eye?
No. It's just that I've been
kind of buried over here.
So the kid doesn't know
his grandmother is dead? G-5?
Hit. No, I guess his parents
didn't want to tell him. B-2?
Miss.
He called 6 times yesterday.
What a nightmare it must be
to have a real family.
I wouldn't worry about it.
B-6?
Hit. Uhh...
you sank my submarine.
Elaine...
Hello?
You have a collect call from--
Hey, buddy, don't say no!
I accept.
I went down to Madeline's.
I told her,
"You gotta move, or it's over."
Well, what happened?
I think it's over.
We had a big fight,
she threw me out,
I started walking,
and now I'm lost downtown!
I don't have any money.
I don't recognize anybody.
I miss home, and I don't even
know how to get there.
What's around you?
I'm looking at Ray's Pizza.
You know where that is?
Is it Famous Ray's?
No. It's Original Ray's.
Famous Original Ray's?
It's just Original, Jerry!
Well, what street are you on?
Hey, I'm on First and First.
How can the same street
intersect with itself?
I must be at the
nexus of the universe.
Just wait there.
I'll pick you up.
And, Kramer--
stay alive!
No matter what occurs,
I will find you!
You Steinfeld?
Yeah.
My name is Maxwell.
I'm from "Maid To Order".
It's a pun.
I sent one of my girls
over to your place.
Cindy.
She says she had
a little problem with you.
You didn't pay.
You know, she didn't really do
what she was supposed to do.
Oh, yeah?
She told me what you like.
You're a little sickie, aren't you?
Disinfectant on the blinds,
vacuuming the couch--
Hey, come on. Come on.
I gotta live around here.
You know what I do to
people who stiff me on a job?
What?
Well, it kinda depends
on the situation.
But if I don't get my money from you,
I'm gonna get it from her.
I don't want her in trouble.
You want the money? Here.
Hey! Wait, wait, wait! Whoa!
Give it to the girl.
I'm an independent contractor.
Tax purposes.
Bobby, you gotta stop
calling your Gammy.
Why?
Because sometimes you call
very early in the morning
when Gammy has been out late
the night before,
and sometimes
when Gammy's not alone.
Your parents still haven't said
anything to you about your Gammy?
All right, here we go.
Gammy doesn't feel so good.
I think Gammy might be dying.
Yep. Yep.
OK. Good-bye, Bobby.
Don't call anymore.
I'm dead now. Gotta go.
9-1-1.
Nexus of the universe.
Hey!
Cindy. Cindy.
What do you want?
Here. I got your money.
I don't want any money from you.
Come on. Take it.
It's money. Let me give it to ya.
Looking for a good time, sir?
You wanna step out of the car, sickie?
Well, this is all
very sophisticated.
All right, hang on, Gammy!
You're gonna make it!
Hey, you look a little lost.
You from around here?
Uh, no.
You know where you're going?
Not really.
My friend was supposed to pick me up,
but I don't know where he is.
Doesn't sound like much of a friend.
You got any money?
Uh, no.
You wanna make some?
OK.
Do you know how to use
a mop wringer?
Yeah, yeah.
Why don't you get in the car?
Hi.
These are soft seats.
Hey, Koko, who's this?
This is our new
Vice-president of Acquisitions, sir.
So you're just
hiring new people now?
That's your job, to hire people?
Yes.
OK, good enough for me, Koko.
Now, what's your name?
My name is Coco.
Coco Higgins.
Coco?
We can't have 2 Cocos.
So I guess you're back to being George.
Well, it was a hell of a ride.
All right, the Grace building.
There's a big stain on the front.
How do we get it off?
When I was a little girl in Jamaica,
my Gammy taught me
to take a wet rag and in a circ--
Ah, excuse me, Vice-president Coco,
no one cares about your Gammy.
What did you say about my Gammy?
Forget Gammy.
Who's Gammy?
There's no Gammy.
Maybe there should be a Gammy.
Oh, no.
George.
Gammy! Gammy! Gammy!
Gammy! Gammy! Gammy! Gammy!
Gammy's getting upset!