When are they gonna learn that
any news about China is an instant page-turner?
What's that?
It's a Wizard electronic organizer for my dad.
I'm going to Florida for his birthday.
How much was it?
Two hundred.
But I'll tell him it's fifty.
He doesn't care about the gift.
He gets excited about the deal.
Where are you getting a Wizard for fifty dollars?
Ah, I'll tell him I got it
on the street, and maybe it's hot.
That's his favorite.
I got a message from the Rosses
at work today.
Susan's parents?
When's the last time you talked to them?
At the funeral,
give or take.
Deep down, I always kinda felt
that they blamed me for Susan's death.
Why, because you picked out
the poisoned envelopes?
That's silly.
Oh, um... Darryl.
These are... people I know.
Jerry, George.
Nice meeting you.
Ah, I gotta run, Elaine.
I'll see you later.
OK.
Still no Puddy?
I think his answering machine's broken,
so I just gave up.
What do you think?
What? About you dating a black guy?
What's the big deal?
What black guy?
Darryl.
He's black, isn't he?
He is?
No, he isn't.
Isn't he, Elaine?
You think?
I thought he looked Irish.
What's his last name?
Nelson.
That's not Irish.
I think he's black.
Should we be talking about this?
I think it's OK.
No, it isn't.
Why not?
Well, it would be OK
if Darryl was here.
If he's black.
Is he black?
Does it matter?
No, course not.
I mean, I'd just like to know.
Oh, so you need to know?
No, I don't need to know.
I just think it would be nice if I knew.
Should I take that?
Uh, one second.
- Oh, here.
Uh, yeah. Hang on.
Uh, Mrs. Ross?
It's-it's George.
Who?
George Costanza.
Susan's, uh, friend?
Long time no speak.
We're all out of lime juice.
I told that woman to buy more.
George, the Susan Ross Foundation
is having an event this weekend.
Oh, I just, uh, leased a house out in the Hamptons,
and I have got to get out there
this weekend and sign the papers.
I'm going back to bed.
Thank you for calling, George.
Oh, sure.
I mean, after all,
you were almost my, uh...
OK, I gotta go.
House in the Hamptons?
Well, you know, I've been lying
about my income for a few years.
I figured I could afford
a fake house in the Hamptons.
Well.
- Hey.
Well, grab a cigar, boys.
Yeah, it's time to celebrate.
Wow. What are we celebrating?
Uh, you remember my coffee table book?
With the little legs?
That's the one.
A big Hollywood so-and-so
optioned it for a movie.
How are they gonna make
that book into a movie?
You remember that photo book
on toy ray guns?
Yeah?
Independence Day?
How much are they paying you?
Let's just say that I don't have to
worry about working for a while.
A long while.
That's funny because
I haven't seen you working for a while.
A long while.
And you're not going to,
because I'm hanging it up.
Boys, I'm retiring.
From what?
From the grind.
I mean, who needs it?
I've accomplished everything
I've set out to do.
What's that?
Oh.
Bought myself a little retirement gift. Gold watch.
Ooh!
Well, it's not really gold.
Aww.
Hey.
- Hey.
Great music.
Oh, it's my neighbor.
They blast that stuff 24 hours a day.
I hate it.
Yo, you!
Turn it down!
Oh, wow, these are nice.
Do they have any cultural significance?
They're... African.
Right.
African.
Well, not Africa, actually.
South Africa.
My family used to live there,
but, we got out years ago,
for obvious reasons.
You know how it is.
Maybe.
You must hate hot dogs, huh?
Or else, you really like them
and that's why you do this.
I'll tell you,
if I had one of these things,
I'd be eating hot dogs all the time.
Are you gonna buy a hot dog or not?
Mmm... no.
Rise and shine, sleepyhead!
It's 5:30 in the morning!
We let you sleep in.
Well, as long as I'm up.
Dad, I got you a birthday present.
Here.
Happy Birthday.
Aw, Jerry.
I should be buying you presents.
What does that mean?
Leave your father alone.
It's his birthday.
Oooh!
It's a radar detector.
Radar detector? I've never seen you
go over twenty miles an hour.
You're like the Grand Marshall
of the Rose Bowl Parade.
It's a Wizard organizer.
This looks like too much money.
Nah, I got it from a guy on the street.
It was, like, fifty bucks.
You think it's hot?
Could be.
Attaboy!
Helen, Jerry got me a hot Wizard computer!
I'm right here.
And you can do everything with it.
You can get email, fax,
there's a calculator.
So, I can use it in the restaurant
to figure out the tip?
Yeah, I guess.
But the really cool thing
is the daily planner.
Helen, we got into restaurants
and figure out the tips.
Jerry,
you're getting your father too excited.
Hey, buddy.
When'd you get here?
Kramer, what are you doing here?
I told you I was retiring.
I moved in next door.
Mr. Kornstein died,
and it's a beautiful apartment.
Yeah, your folks said it was for rent,
so I jumped on it.
Kramer, you can't live down here.
This is where people come to die.
Not you.
Older people.
Don't eat cookies for breakfast!
I'll fix you something.
How 'bout a feta cheese omelette?
Mmmm, that sounds great, Mom.
If you feed him,
he'll never leave.
We don't have any feta.
How about cottage cheese and Egg Beaters?
I guess.
I don't believe this.
I know, I know.
Don't I look more relaxed?
So George, do you have any thoughts
on this Darryl situation?
Actually, I did have a thought.
Oh.
Why don't you just ask him?
Because if I ask him,
then it's like I really want to know.
Maybe he's, um...
... mixed.
Is that the right word?
I really don't think we're supposed
to be talking about this.
Yeah.
I'm just gonna go to the bathroom.
You know what, I'm leaving.
- Yeah.
I'll just talk to Jerry
when he gets back.
Oh.
Mrs. Ross, Mr. Ross.
Oh, you're George's friend.
We saw him in the city this weekend.
What happened to his
place in the Hamptons?
The Hamptons?
George Costanza?
I don't think so.
Have a good one.
Rosses.
George, we were just talking about you.
Well, sorry I missed that, uh,
charity thing.
But this was one of those truly glorious
Hampton weekends that you always hear about.
Really?
Yeah, I may move out there.
I mean it,
I'll do it!
OK, I'll see you later.
Keep it real!
Another fine meal,
and now for my Wizard tip calculator.
Dad, it's got lots of other functions.
Don't worry.
I'll get to the other functions.
I can't get it open.
Yay! Jerry got it open.
The service was slow.
And God forbid they should refill the water.
How does 12.4% sound?
Well, your tip is 4 dollars
and 36.6666 cents.
We'll round down.
Jerry, it was so nice of you
to come down here on your father's birthday.
You've helped take his mind
off the condo election.
Oh, right.
You can't run for condo president because
you were impeached at the other condo.
I was never impeached!
I resigned!
Even so,
the press would bury him!
What press?
The condo newsletter,
the Boca Breeze.
Pinko Commie rag.
Hey, Morty.
Your boy here, he just got a date
with that young aquacise instructor.
She's fifty.
You know what he's got?
He's got charisma.
That's my man.
All right,
I'll see you guys.
Yeah.
Morty, what're you looking at?
I'll tell you what I'm looking at:
the next condo president
of Del Boca Vista, Phase Three.
Elaine, thank you for the Wizard!
Wow, it's got so many functions.
Yeah, yeah.
Forget about all that.
First thing is first.
Warranty information.
Name, we know that.
Uh, hobbies.
Skiing, racquetball...
Well, I don't do that stuff.
It doesn't matter, it doesn't matter,
it doesn't matter.
Oh, here's one: race.
Isn't that optional?
It certainly should be.
It's nobody's damn business!
But they really would like to know.
All right, then...
Asian.
What?
Just to mess with 'em.
Oh. Right.
Good one.
Average income, uh...
over a hundred thousand.
Really?
Does that matter?
No, but...
it is very nice to know.
So did you figure out Darryl's...
you know.
Ah, I've given up.
So, now we're going to
a bunch of Spanish restaurants.
I figure that'll cover us either way.
You're a master of race relations.
Hey, so Kramer's running for
president of the condo?
Yeah, it's all my father's doing.
He wants to install Kramer in a puppet regime
and then wield power from behind the scenes.
Preferably from the sauna in the clubhouse.
Who are they running against?
Common sense
and a guy in a wheelchair.
Jerry?
He's still
down with his folks.
What are you doing here?
Elaine, Elaine--
I'm getting his mail.
Oh, no.
He asked you to get the mail?
Mm-hmm.
Jerry, why is Elaine
getting your mail?
George, listen to me.
I have a very important job for you.
I want you to come by twice a day
and flush the toilet,
so the gaskets don't dry out and leak.
What?
What about the mail?
This is far more important.
You must exercise the gaskets, George.
All right, Jerry.
I'll do it.
See you.
So, I ran into the Rosses again.
Oh, right, at the coffee shop.
Where did they get the idea that
you have a place in the Hamptons?
From me.
What did you say?
I told them
I have a place in the Hamptons.
What did you say?
I told them you didn't.
And I laughed and I laughed.
So, they knew?
Those liars!
But you lied first.
Yeah, but they let me go on and on
all about the Hamptons!
They never said a thing!
You don't let somebody lie
when they know you're lying.
You call them a liar!
Like you're a liar!
Yes. Thank you!
Is that so hard?
So, this is over, not over?
I'm betting, not over.
Not by a long shot.
I'm calling up the Rosses and inviting them
up to my non-existent place in the Hamptons.
Then we'll see who blinks first.
Haven't you done enough
to these people?
This is not about them.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to exercise Jerry's gaskets.
Vote for Kramer.
Cosmo Kramer.
I'm running for condo president.
I'd like your vote.
Thanks.
Remember, ma'am,
a vote for me is a vote for Kramer.
Can you cut my meat?
Gladly.
Coffee?
Sure.
Are you black?
Or should I bring some cream.
I'm black.
Oh, you know what?
Bring a little cream.
Look at that.
Did you hear that?
What?
God, there are still people
who have trouble with an interracial couple.
Interracial?
Us?
Isn't that unbelievable?
Yes, it's awful!
They're upset because
we're an interracial couple.
That is racism!
I don't feel like eating.
Me neither.
Well, maybe this turkey club.
So... here I am.
Ready to take you to the Hamptons.
Sounds grand.
Do you have your bathing suits?
It's March.
Speak now, or we are
headed to the Hamptons.
It's a two-hour drive.
Once you get in that car,
we are going all the way...
to the Hamptons.
All right, you wanna get nuts?
Come on.
Let's get nuts!
Hey, Dad.
You know you can program this thing
to beep every time you need to take a vitamin.
Dad, you look so different.
Oh, no.
We're campaigning, Jerry.
To rule the people,
one must walk among them.
This is the home stretch.
Tomorrow's the election!
Right. Yeah.
The polls close after dinner,
3 o'clock.
But then when we win,
the celebration goes all night
until the break of 8pm.
You know, you can put that whole schedule
right in your daily planner.
Daily what?
Have you read
today's Boca Breeze?
Hey, look at that.
Picture of me, huh?
Candidate Cosmo Kramer
caught barefoot in clubhouse.
Barefoot in the clubhouse?
Kramer!
Don't you realize
this is against the rules?
Well, I couldn't find my shoes.
Kramer, these people
work and wait their whole lives
to move down here,
sit in the heat,
pretend it's not hot,
and enforce these rules.
Who wants hot chocolate?
Oh, yeah!
Me.
This is a huge scandal!
We need damage control.
All right, look.
People seem to like
those tip calculators, huh?
Wizards!
Yeah, well, how 'bout if we give one out
to every member on the condo board.
Kramer...
There are twenty people on the board.
Thank God you can get that deal.
Payoffs.
Now we're playing politics.
All right,
what do we do next, Morty, huh?
Wiretaps, slush funds?
First, I need a nap.
Oh, I'll get your electric blanket!
Kramer, I can't get that many Wizards.
Well, what about your deal, huh?
I didn't have a deal!
They're two hundred dollars a pop.
What do I do?
Well, don't worry about it.
I know a guy.
Down here?
Yeah, Bob Saccamano's father.
And that leads
into the master bedroom.
Tell us more.
You want to hear more?
The master bedroom
opens into the solarium.
Another solarium?
Yes, two solariums.
Quite a find.
And I have horses, too.
What are their names?
Snoopy and Prickly Pete.
Should I keep driving?
Oh, look, an antique stand.
Pull over.
We'll buy you a housewarming gift.
Housewarming gift.
All right,
we're taking it up a notch!
Here you go.
Long day?
Yeah, I just worked a triple shift.
I hear ya, Sister.
Sister?
- Yeah.
It's OK.
My boyfriend's black.
Here he is.
See?
Hi, Elaine.
- Hey.
He's black?
Yeah.
I'm black?
Aren't you?
I'll give you a couple minutes
to decide.
What are you talking about?
You're black.
You said we were an interracial couple.
We are.
Because you're Hispanic.
I am?
Aren't you?
No.
Why would you think that?
Your name's Benes.
Your hair.
And you kept taking me
to those Spanish restaurants.
That's because
I thought you were black.
Why would you take me to a
Spanish restaurant because I'm black?
I don't think we should
be talking about this.
So, what are you?
I'm white.
So, we're just a
couple of white people?
I guess.
Oh.
Yeah.
So do you want to go to the Gap?
Sure.
Oh, well...
I handed out all the Wizards.
Polls close in one hour.
I think we've got this baby
all sewn up, huh?
Oh, uh, there was an extra one.
Norman Burgerman, he won't be
leaving any tips where he is.
Congratulations, Mr. President.
Congratulations, Mr. Puppetmaster.
Hey, Morty, what's wrong with
these tip calculators?
What are you talking about?
It's overtipping.
I just left five bucks for a BLT.
Let me see that.
This isn't a Wizard,
it's a Willard.
A Willard?
Saccamano senior screwed me!
Mine doesn't have a seven!
I'm ruined!
Jerry, why didn't you get them Wizards?
Because a real Wizard's $200!
You didn't have a deal?
No deal.
Not hot.
Morty, you, and Kramer,
you're finished.
What?
Everyone vote for
the guy in the wheelchair!
Let's go!
The people have spoken.
Well, that's it for me.
I'm heading back to New York.
Dad, I'm sorry.
You should be!
How could you spend $200
on a tip calculator?
It does other things!
Where are we, George?
Almost there.
Well, this is the end of Long Island.
Where's your house?
We, uh, we go on foot from here.
All right.
There's no house!
It's a lie!
There's no solarium.
There's no Prickly Pete.
There's no other solarium.
We know.
Then, why?
Why did you make me drive
all the way out here?
Why didn't you say something?
Why? Why? Why?
We don't like you, George.
And we always blamed you
for what happened to Susan.
Oh.
All right!
Let's head back.