Any second now. Light is on
Light is on! waffles are ready.
Oh, fantastic! I'm starving.
How about that.
She ate breakfast naked?
She didn't even want a napkin.
I've had bedroom naked, I've had
walk- to-the-bathroom naked...
I have never had living-room naked.
Oh, it's a scene.
- It's
like you're livin' in the Playboy
Mansion! Did she, uh, did
she did she frolic?
I don't really have enough room.
Yeah. Hey, Lainie, Puddy.
Back together?
- His apartment
was being fumigated,
so we thought we'd give
it another shot.
So guess who called me
last night? Jason Hanke.
'Stanky Hanke'? What did he want?
He called to apologize for standing
me up five years ago.
- Why now?
A.A. It's one of the Twelve Steps.
Step number Nine is you have to
apologize to anyone
you've ever wronged.
Ho ho ho ho! I can't wait for
Hanke to come crawling back to me.
Still with the neck hole?
- Still upset. Very upset.
What neck hole?
Remember that New Year's
party he threw a few years ago? He
had that very drafty apartment, you
know, I think on Ninth Avenue.
Faster.
I asked if I could borrow a sweater.
A cashmere sweater.
- I said
preferably cashmere, , for warmth.
So in front of the
whole party, he says, 'No. I
don't want you
stretching out the neck hole.'
Oh, yeah, sure, laugh it
up. Everybody else did!
Well, it's funny. I
mean, you have a big head.
Or is it 'cause of your neck?
No, I think the head does
most of the stretching.
Regardless. I had to walk
around for the rest
of the party in some cheap
Metlife windbreaker.
Now, it is payback time.
I really think it's the size
of your neck.
- It's my head!
Isn't this great? With
those nerds in accounting
moved, you and I are the
only ones who use this bathroom.
Yeah. Great.
You went to the
coffee shop without me? I told
ya, I just wanted to hop in the shower.
That was an hour ago. What were
you doing in there?
- Showering.
How long does it take
you?
- Ten minutes.
Ten minutes? That's kooky talk.
Hey Elaine, how long do
you spend in the shower?
Ten minutes.
- Let me smell
you.
- All right. Whiff away.
Uh... that's not bad at
all.
- Hup! That's it.
So get this. I'm in
the bathroom at work today,
and I see Peggy using a seat protector.
So?
- So... we're the
only women on the floor.
I mean, we're like roommates.
Would-would
you use a seat
protector if you had a roommate?
I think the damage is
probably already done.
All right! I'll get that. Well, maybe
she just practices good hygiene.
Yeah, you're
probably right. She's probably
one of those neurotic clean freaks.
Well, here's my shower routine.
Maybe I can make some changes.
Get  wash cloth mittens and maybe some
liquid soap, and
just... -pop- focus!
Zephyr? That is not a word.
Do you challenge?
- No, I do not challenge.
66 points. Ha ha.
I'd accuse you of cheating, but I
don't know where you'd hide the tiles.
You want some more ice tea?
- Sure.
Wrong  pipe.
So she coughed.
- Coughing... naked...
It's a turn-off, man.
Everything goes with naked.
When you cough, there are thousands of
unseen muscles that suddenly
spring into action.
It's like watching that fat guy catch a
cannonball in his
stomach in slow motion.
Oh, you spoiled, spoiled man.
Do you now how much mental
energy I expend
just trying to picture women naked?
But the thing you don't realize is
that there's good naked and bad naked.
Naked hair brushing, good; naked
crouching, bad. Hey, there's Hanke.
All right. It's grovel
time.
- Hey, George. Jerry.
Listen, I just got sober, so I've
been going through the Twelve Steps.
What are you up to now, uh, Step Nine?
Yeah. Making amends.
- Important step.
Maybe the most important.
Anyway, uh, Jerry, you
know, this may sound dumb, but,
you know, when we first met
I thought your name was Gary.
And, I think I may even have
called you Gary a couple of times, and...
I don't know if you noticed, but I always
felt bad about it, so, I'm sorry.
Thank you. I did notice, and
I appreciate you rectifying it.
Great. Great. Well,
I'll see you guys later.
Well, I just got out
of a 27-minute shower.
I made some good cuts, and I
didn't lose anything I needed.
Yeah, I think what I
kept is even stronger now.
You got some suds over here.
Wha...? Oh, man! Geez!
Look at that! I'm all lathery. Jerry,
you got to show me
what I'm doing wrong.
Oh, come on!
- No, I
mean it, man. I'm lost!
You promise you'll
never come in here again?
Oh, Jerry, you know I can't do that.
Now my sense of it is that
you're probably wasting time
working piecemeal, first cleaning
one area, then another.
Well, that's how cats do it.
But, when you have a faucet instead
of a tongue, you want to use gravity.
OK. Let's turn the water on now.
No, I told you, it's just a dry run.
Well, Hanke's moved on to Step Ten. He
was spotted taking personal inventory.
That's Step Ten?
- All
he has to do now is
count his blessings, say
a prayer, and he's done.
Do you believe this?
Come on, Jerry. How
about a-a baggy swimsuit?
You're not gettin' any skin, Kramer.
Well, this has all been one big tease!
These proofs look pretty
good. Oh. Can I move this?
Yup. I think this will work.
I'm... gonna  get
another bottle of water.
Here, take mine.
There's a little left.
Guys, there's no doubt
that the pay is good. But I don't
just know if I see
myself working with ice cream.
You get pretty buff forearms.
- I don't know if I'm into that.
Oh, hello, Hanke, others.
You know, Jason, I, uh, I couldn't
help notice, I... I
didn't get my  apology.
Apology? For what?
- A drafty apartment?
A... sweaterless friend? A ball-game
giveaway Metlife windbreaker?
George, come on, not that neck
hole thing.
- Yeah, the neck
hole thing, and I would appreciate
it if you would  say you're sorry.
No way, you would've
completely stretched it out.
You're an alcoholic! You have to
apologize. Step Nine! Step Nine.
All right, George,
all right. I'm sorry.
I'm very, very sorry. I'm so sorry that
I didn't want your rather
bulbous head struggling to find its
way through the normal-size
neck hole of my finely knit sweater.
Now see, that's smart.
Constant motion. Wow.
Oh, yeah, yeah,
I-I'm watching you, too. But
this guy's really showing me something!
You got a steak?
- What happened to you?
Ah, people in this city
are crazy.
- Here ya go.
Thanks, buddy. Oh... yes! Hey, you
got any A1, 'cause I'm cooking a steak.
What?
- Yeah, a different one.
OK, Jerry. I fixed that bike.
Oh. That wasn't really necessary.
I don't ride it. It's just for show.
I should really clean those bearings.
Hold this. Look at all that gunk.
Please don't crouch.
- Ouch! Caught my skin.
Oh, that's bad. Especially that area.
You got anything to
snack on?
- Oh, pickles!
Unnhhhh! It's a tough one.
Look, please stop! Let
me help you with that!
Unnnnh! Oooh. That's gonna
leave a welt. Look at that.
I can't. I can't look anymore.
I-I-I've seen too  much.
Peggy, we've got to talk. What is it
about me that you find so  offensive?
You seem to be with
a lot of men.
- What!?
I happen to have a
very steady boyfriend.
You know, I mean,
we broke up a few times
and there has been an
occasional guy here or...
or there, but, wh-why
is this your business?
It's not. Good day.
Oh. All right. You
think I've got germs?
I'll give you some germs. How about
some for your keyboard, huh? Huh?
Oooh, how about for your stapler. Hmmm?
That's good, isn't it? You
have a happy and a healthy.
Well, technically he did apologize.
Jerry, I felt like a
straight man in some
horrible sketch. He was riffing!
Riffing! On my pain!
So now you want an apology for the
apology, plus the original apology?
That's right. I'm two in the hole!
Well, I hit the wall
yesterday with Lady Godiva.
She did a full body
flex on a pickle jar.
Did you explain to her about
the good naked and the bad naked?
Where am I gonna get a
fat guy and a cannonball?
Well... what if you showed up bad
naked, huh? You still
got that belt sander?
Well, you on all fours, that
thingvibratin', kickin'
up sawdust, ho ho! She'll
get the picture!
Hello?
- Hey, Jerry, guess
where I'm calling from!
World War I plane?
- No, I'm in my shower.
Well, you know, I'm trying to get
out of the shower sooner, and
then I ask myself, 'Why?' I mean
this is where I want to be.
So I got a waterproof phone,
I shaved, I brushed my teeth,
and now I ordered a
pair of chinos from J. Crew.
When are ya gettin' out?
- I'm
not! I'll see ya later, buddy.
Bad news, people. Peggy
is home sick.
- Oh, please.
She's stuffed up, achy, and
suffering from intense malaise.
Oh, come on, we all have
intense malaise. Right?
I just spoke with her,
Elaine. She's in bed.
Yeah, let me tell you something:
this is all in her
mind, OK? She is insane.
She thinks I made her sick
because I coughed on her
doorknob, rubbed her
stapler in my armpit, and put
her keyboard on my butt.
Yeah, she's a  wacko.
So you're Jason Hanke's
supervisor?
- Sponsor.
Whatever. Listen, I'm very
concerned about this guy.
He's doing very well. He's
already on to Step Ten.
Yeah, well when you don't actually
do the steps, you can
go through them pretty quick.
You can get through six a day.
Is there some unresolved
issue between you and Jason?
I don't know. A little
thing called Step Nine? Instead of
an apology, he was
beboppin' and scattin' all over me.
I'm not sure what you want me to
do.
- Well, aren't you the boss of him?
You shouldn't let him move up! When
I was in the Cub Scouts, I got
stuck on Weebolos for three years
'cause I kept
losing the Pinewood Derby.
You're quite upset, George.
- Well, I think
you should drop him down to Step Two.
Admit there's a higher power?
Yeah, let him chew
on that for a while.
You know George, I
think I can help you. We're
having a meeting tomorrow.
Why don't you just come by?
All right. That's
more like it. Thank you very
much.
- By the way, my
uncle was an alcoholic, so...
Lomez, you're not listenin'.
Jerry likes the
naked, just some of the
things she does when she's naked.
Calm down, I'm on your side.
Geez. Hey, hold on a second. I
got a clog, I'll call ya back.
What are you doing?
I found a rough spot
on the kitchen floor, I
thought I'd polish it up with
this belt sander I have here.
No, not that. Why are you naked?
I thought naked is good.
- This isn't good naked.
George, here, have a
seat.
- Where's Hanke?
OK, let's get started. Welcome
to Rage-aholics Anonymous.
What? Rate-aholics?
- George, this can help you.
George, this can help you.
- Hey, I am
not here for rage. I'm
here for revenge.
Excuse me. We have a 'no
yelling' policy at these meetings.
Excuse me. Am I talking
to you, Pinhead? Am I?!
Please don't call me
'Pinhead'.
- I'm losin' it!
He took you to Rage-aholics? Why?
Probably because this
whole Universe is against me!
You've got a little rage.
- I know. And now they
want me to bottle it up.
It makes me so mad!
By the way, my bad naked
demo didn't quite
work.
- This bread has nuts in it!
Oh, great. Elaine. What is wrong with my
body?
- Chicken wing shoulder blades.
That's it?
- No, but
that's one problem. Why?
Well, I was walking
around naked in front of Melissa
the other day--
- Whoa! Walking around naked?
hh... that is not a
good look for a man.
Why not? It's a good look for a woman.
Well, the female body
is a... work of art. The male
body is utilitarian, it's
for gettin' around, like a jeep.
So you don't think it's
attractive?
- It's hideous.
The hair, the... the
lumpiness. It's simian.
Well, some women like
it.
- Hmm. Sickies.
Installing your
Clarkman garbage disposal.
Dismantle latch hasp beneath main
drainage lot. Oh, come on, Clarkman.
Is, uh, David Puddy
there?" This is Puddy.
Well, this is Kramer.
- I know.
Um, listen, you're a mechanic. Could
you help me install a garbage disposal?
Well, it's a big job.
You've got to dismantle
the latch hasp from the
auxiliary drainage line.
No. It says 'main line'.
- It's a
misprint. What do you got, a Clarkman?
Yeah."  "Hey, man, I'll call you back.
I'll talk you through it.
- Oh,
OK. Well, thanks, buddy.
Hey, Puddy.
Hey, Babe, your boss called. You
owe five bucks for a balloon bouquet.
Yeah, he says you can just give it
to him tomorrow when you see him.
Balloon bouquet? For who?
- Peggy took a turn for the worst.
Peggy. Oh, great. I suppose she's
still blaming me?
- That's what he said.
I don't believe this
woman.
- Talk to me, Babe.
She's this crazy woman who is convinced
that my germs make her sick.
- Oh, germ-o-phobe.
I know what that's about.
I'm a recovering
germ-o-phobe. Ten years.
What is this symbol?
- It's a germ.
Elaine, it was very nice of you
to bring the man you're currently
sleeping with over to talk to me, but I
assure you, I don't
have any problem with germs.
Don't you? Elaine.
- Please!
I know it looks bleak. I've been
there. Ten years ago waking up in
bed next to a woman like this would've
sent me running for the Phisohex.
Really?
I still have trouble
looking at those disgusting
old bedroom slippers
she slogs around in.
Hey, I've had those since college.
They're bunnies.
- They're bacteria traps.
So you... just learned to live
with it?
- For the most part.
OK, we're broken up
for the rest of the day.
So I'm glad we had a
talk and worked this out.
Don't you feel this is better?
This is nice.
- Yes,
clothes. This is normal.
Hey, what are you doing tomorrow?
I was thinking that we could go down...
Jerry? Jerry, are you listening to me?
Oh... yeah. What? I'm sorry.
I wanted to know what
you're doing tomorrow.
Oh, maybe a haircut, and,
I don't know, maybe a...
So you broke up?
- We couldn't
carry on a conversation.
I kept trying to picture her naked, she
kept trying to not picture me naked.
Hang on.
So what are you up to?
Oh, just cooking up a little
thank you for Puddy.
Hey, how do you
make those radish roses?
Insert a knife into the
center and twist. Then,
to make it bloom, soak it in
water for thirty to forty minutes.
No problem there.
George. Thanks for
coming down to talk to me.
I wanted to see you right
away, but my hours
here aren't very
flexible. I just started yesterday.
Well, I'm here. What is it?
Well, I talked to my sponsor, and,
uh, I've thought it over,
and, you know, my apology
at the coffee shop was sarcastic,
and rude, and you deserve much better.
Well, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Can I get a Triple Minute Man
Mint?
- Waffle or sugar cone?
Uh, excuse me, uh, um, Jason. I don't
want to get into a
big thing here, but...
I'm not sure if, technically, what you
just said was actually
an apology.
- What?
Can you get on that cone?
Would you hang on just
a second, son? about?
George, what are you talking.
Well, it's just, all you said
was 'your welcome', which is
nice. It's very nice. But...
I feel I gotta get the apology.
Is there anybody else here but you?
I'm alone, and it's my second
day. You know, I don't even think we
have that flavor so... George,
really, enough, ok? You know,
I-I admitted I was wrong, so
what more do you want from me?
I would like an apology.
- All right, look, you know--
Did you try it?
No, this guy doesn't know what he's
doing.
- Oh, yes I do. Yes, I do. OK?
I'm interacting with someone here, if
you can understand
that. Now, I'm sorry.
Baah! There it is!
You just said it! That's
what I want! Now say it
again, and tell it to me.
I'm not saying anything to you.
I'm not sorry. I was never sorry. It
was cashmere. I hate Step Nine!
Where's that Rum Raisin?
Where is it? Can't
find anything. I need a drink. Ah,
daquiri ice. Here we go. What are
you looking at? Get out! Come on,
can't you see we're closed?! Get out!
Mmm. This food is fantastic,
And what a pretty radish rose, huh?
Well, thank you.
- Here's to Peggy, on
her first week of
being germ-free, free.
Yeah. And here's to David
Puddy for helping me install
a much needed and much appreciated
garbage disposal in my bathtub.
You have a garbage
disposal in your bathtub?
Oh, yeah, and I use it all the time.
I made this whole meal in  there.
This food was in the shower with you?
- Mm-hmm. I prepared it as I bathed.
Oh, germs. Germs. Germs!
Excuse me. Is this, uh,
Rage-aholics?
- No, germ-o-phobes.
Thanks. What are you
guys doin' here?
- Kramer.
Right.
Hi, I'm, uh, Jason. I'm a
rage-aholic.
- Hi, Jason.
Uh, this is my first meeting.
- Step-skipper. That man is a step-skipper!
He skips Step Nine!
- Please. Step Nine.
That's right! He never
apologized to me for saying
that I would stretch out the
neck hole of his sweater.
It wasn't funny.
It was a very nice sweater. Take a
look at his neck, not to mention
the melon sitting on top of it.
I don't know if I'd trust him with a V-neck.
He's beboppin' and
scattin', and I'm losin' it!