Maura, I want you to know--
I-I've given this a lot of thought.
I'm sorry, but we--
We have to break up.
No.
What's that?
We're not breaking up.
We're not?
No.
All right.
She said no?
She said no.
What did you do?
What could I do?
We fooled around and went to a movie.
George, both parties don't have to consent
to a breakup.
It's not like you're launching missiles from a submarine
and you both have to turn your keys.
Obviously, you didn't make a convincing case.
Let me hear your arguments.
Well, I don't really like her.
That's good.
I don't find her attractive.
Solid.
I'd like to sleep with a lot of other women.
Always popular.
Sometimes at restaurants she talks to her food.
"Oh, Mr. Mashed Potatoes, you are so good."
You have an airtight case.
And in bed--
I'm afraid we're out of time.
Hey.
- What?
Check these out.
These are Jerry Lewis' old cufflinks
that he actually wore in the movie "Cinderfella".
I got 'em at an auction.
I got some cufflinks I could've loaned you.
No, Jerry Lewis is gonna be at this
Friar's Club roast I'm goin' to next week.
Now I have an in
to strike up a conversation with him.
You already have an in.
You have the same first name.
Jerry!
Oh, that'll intrigue him.
Well, it worked when I met
George Peppard last week.
George Peppard has been dead for years.
Well, whoever he was,
he knew a lot about The A-Team.
So you would choose your last meal
based on the method of execution?
Right, right.
I mean, if I was getting the chair,
I'd go for something hot and spicy.
You know, Thai, maybe Mexican.
Lethal injection -
feels like pasta.
You know, painless,
don't want anything to heavy.
So, um, why don't we get together some time?
Oh, sure. Why don't you give me your number?
I think it'd be better if I called you.
Oh. OK.
Maybe we could grab some lunch sometime.
Do-do you work around here?
No, not really.
So, is there anything
you can tell me about yourself?
I think you're very beautiful.
Oh? That'll do.
What about Puddy?
I haven't talked to him in
like three weeks.
I think it might be over.
So, what's this guy about?
I don't know.
He wouldn't tell me his phone number
where he worked.
I'll bet he's in a relationship.
Or he's a crime fighter
safeguarding his secret identity.
Elaine, you could be dating
the Green Lantern!
Which one is he?
Green suit, power ring.
I don't care for jewely on men.
Hey. It happened again.
Another robbery in the building.
So you bought a cooler?
No, it's a strongbox
to protect my irreplacables.
And... what would those be?
Some taxidermy
that's been in my family for generations.
My Tony,
my... military discharge.
You were in the Army?
Briefly.
Now, I gotta find a good place to hide this key.
Because if somebody finds this,
they hold the key to all my possessions.
Literally.
"Literally"?
What's that supposed to mean?
You mind if I hide this somewhere?
No, go ahead.
A little... privacy, huh?
Oh, come on!
Come on, Jerry, this is a security issue.
Boy, you wouldn't last a day in the Army.
How long did you last?
Well, that's classified.
Hey, what if he's married?
Kramer?
No, the Green Lantern.
OK!
So, you would date a married guy?
That's so hacky.
Well, I don't know. I may never marry.
This might be the closest I get.
You peeked!
This is your hiding place?!
It was under a spoon!
And so, for all these reasons,
we are officially broken up.
Thank you--
and good night.
No, George, we're not.
But I proved it!
I refuse to give up on this relationship.
It's like launching missiles from a submarine.
Both of use have to turn our keys.
Well, then, I am gonna have to
ask you to turn your key.
I'm sorry, George,
I can't do that.
Turn your key, Maura.
Turn your key!
So, how is a guy like you not involved?
I might ask you the same thing.
That's true, maybe he's not married.
Oh, that is so sweet.
How long do I have to hold this?
Oh, no.
Who is it?
Uh, no one, no one.
Here, uh, let me show you a short cut. Come on.
Married. That's it, I'm chucking the flower.
Jerry! Jerry!
Elaine, what are you doin' down there?
You didn't hear me buzzing?
Oh, I guess it's broken.
Throw down your key.
It's liable to bounce and go into a sewer.
I'll catch it!
You'll chicken out at the last second.
Yeah, you're right.
Well, will you at least keep me company
until somebody comes out?
All right.
Hey, you know what's weird?
Huh?
I used to be able to have a huge meal,
go right to sleep.
But I can't anymore.
Nodding off!
Well, I was right.
He's an adulterer.
And he's cheating on his wife with me.
We haven't done anything yet.
I'm hungry. Can you throw something down?
All right. Here!
I'm gonna try and fix the buzzer.
It went in the sewer!
Hey...
- What are you doin'?
You jammed your key in here? You shorted out my intercom!
You just had to go lookin' for it,
didn't you?
See, you hate it that I have a little secret.
Anything I do--
you gotta know all about it!
You're so obsessed with me.
I'm gonna go let Elaine in.
What are you doing with her?
Kramer!
Security issue!
Oh, hey. You got in.
Yeah, flirted with the menu guy.
Here.
Oh, thanks.
That wasn't me!
So, he's definitely married, huh?
Boy, I would've loved to have been there
when you told him off.
Oh, come on!
Well, he could be a superhero!
You should've seen him run.
OK!
All right, Jerry.
Let's see if you can get it in your head
that this is not an Easter egg hunt
for your childish amusement.
Jerry!
George, the buzzer's broken!
I'll come down!
I believe this belongs to you.
Where did you get that?
I bought it.
Thanks.
I'm sorry. I-I don't know you.
What?
There's been some robberies in the building.
I-I can't let you in.
But, I live here.
I ran out to buy some birdseed,
and I forgot my key.
Sounds like a scam.
Very sorry.
So, I broke up with Maura.
It's done. I'm out.
Great, you're lonely and miserable again.
Feels right.
Is that guy still there?
He's starin' at us.
Don't look at him.
We don't hear that.
Want a bite?
No, I don't.
I think that ginger ale at the coffee shop
is just Coke and Sprite mixed together.
How can I prove it?
Can't. Damn it.
Hey, honey.
What?
Maura, what are you doing here?
I ended this relationship, twice.
George, you didn't mean that.
That was just a fight.
Why does it always seem like
I'm the only one working at this breakup?
George, I listened to your arguments,
and they were rambling and flimsy.
I'm not convinced.
Come on, get dressed and let's get some dinner.
All right.
Eww, Mr. Apple!
You have a brown spot!
So, this is your little... love nest?
It's nothing special,
just a little place I keep.
Shall I light a fire?
Oh, that sounds romantic.
I'm having a little problem with the heat.
I got some cardboard out here.
This is wrong. I should go.
Can you get that, please?
Oh, sure.
Where's Glenn?
You're the woman from the street,
and I am so sorry.
You know, I'm not really a home-wrecker.
I-I thought he was a superhero.
I swear.
Lady, I'm not his wife,
I'm his welfare caseworker. Is he home?
This is his home?
Yes.
So, he's...
Poor.
I think this will burn!
So you do live here.
Yeah.
You live on this floor?
So you live right... there.
Yeah.
So I guess I'll see--
He wouldn't give me his number
because he doesn't have a phone.
He's not married.
He's poor.
Is he wretchedly poor?
Does he wear one of those barrels,
with the straps?
He probably busted it up
and burned it for heat.
So, when are you giving Boxcar Willie
his walking papers?
How can I end it over money?
I feel bad.
Well, let's think.
Have you ever dealt with the poor
in any other situation?
Yes.
There was this homeless guy
who used to urinate on our garbage cans.
Good. How did you handle that?
Well, we gave him a few bucks, and...
Now he goes in the alley across the street.
Same situation.
Pay him off, and you're clean.
Well, I am not paying Glenn off
to get out of this relationship.
What am I supposed to do?
Just walk into his hovel, and hand him...
Well, how much do you think it would be?
Hey.
Hey, where have you been?
Seeing Maura.
Apparently, I was unable to break up
beyond a reasonable doubt.
If only he could have been
cheating on his wife, you know.
Things would have been so much simpler.
Who's this, Blue Arrow?
Green Lantern.
We found out
his super power was lack of money.
All right.
He's invulnerable to creditors.
We get it.
He's the 'Got-no-Green' Lantern.
Thank you.
Hey, Elaine.
Maybe his girlfriend is Lois Loan.
Well crafted.
Hey, maybe this cheating thing
is what I could use to ditch Maura.
Sure, just tell Maura you're having an affair.
She's like a District Attorney.
If it's not the truth, I'll break under the cross.
I actually have to do it.
Could you move over there?
Hey, you know, there's this secretary at work
that always had a crush on me.
Really?
How come you never pursued her before?
She's too tan.
It's the middle of the winter,
she's like a carrot.
Did I leave my glasses here?
He can wipe out his checking account
in a single bound!
Keep 'em!
Hey.
There's a giant parrot in the hallway.
It's Phil's.
Who?
Our neighbor that you turned against.
Anyway, I told him it'd be fine with us if he wanted to
let it stretch its wings out in the hallway.
What'd ya tell him that for?
Because since you've been
playing God with the front door,
I've been tryin' to smooth things out, Jerry.
In fact, I was just hanging out at his place.
Really? What's it like?
Is it nicer than mine?
Where does he have the couch?
Well, I don't know,
but the key problem is solved.
I hid it at Phil's.
He let you?
No, he doesn't know.
See, I hid it without telling him.
So, uh, Phil won't be compulsively
looking for it like some people.
You!
So, you... you say
you've been in the city all winter?
I was in Maine for a couple days.
Well... here we are.
George, I've always fantasized
about jumping into bed with you.
But... I don't want to spoil things
by sleeping with you too soon.
Are you sure?
'Cause it could really help me out of a jam.
I want to build something with you, George.
Oh, not more building.
And I won't take no for an answer.
No?
No.
All right.
What are we doing in this alley, anyway?
It's a surprise.
What are you doing? What is that?
It's a bag of donuts.
It's garbage.
No, no, no.
When they make the new ones,
the old ones come out right here.
All right, that's it.
How do you spell your last name?
It's a bear claw!
You have no idea how rare this is.
I'll make it out to cash.
How 'bout two hundred bucks? Two-fifty?
Make it three hundred.
You know, Elaine--
You are the bear claw in the garbage bag of my life.
Aw, Glenn.
Hi. Is Phil here?
Yeah, I'm here.
Phil... hi.
I-I know we kind of got off to a bad start.
But your bird-- which is lovely, by the way--
made a mess on my door.
And?
I thought maybe you'd clean it up,
or your maid, there.
That's my wife.
All right, I think we're done here.
So, you're in a relationship
with a woman you don't like,
and you're having an affair
with a woman that won't have sex with you.
This isn't going well.
I cannot find my Jerry Lewis cufflinks.
Without 'em, I have no in!
You don't need the cufflinks.
You have the same name.
Jerry!
Where are you going?
Help me look.
It's a big night.
I'm ice skating with one,
and going to a staged reading of "Godspell"
with the other.
Which is with who?
It doesn't matter.
Whoo! Boy.
Yeah, you clean up nice.
I can't go until I find my cufflinks.
Yeah, see? I knew you would lose 'em.
That's why I took 'em out of your dresser drawer
and put 'em in my strongbox.
You're a lifesaver.
Would you get them, please?
Yeah, we'll stop by Phil's,
we'll pick up the key.
Hey, what's going on?
Fredo is dead.
That strange Portuguese guy
that lives next-door to the incinerator?
No, my bird!
We just got back from the pet cemetery.
Oh, Phil. Mrs. Phil.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, I'll bet you are!
They told us he was poisoned!
Something in his food.
But I, I didn't--
Kramer, they think I killed Fredo!
And who buries a bird?
Yeah. Just give it to the Portuguese guy,
and he puts it in the incinerator.
Just get the key and let's get out here.
You know, it's a funny thing
about that bird dying.
I hid the key in Fredo's food dish.
Whew! That's a weird coincidence.
You killed Fredo!
Fredo was weak and stupid.
He shouldn't've eaten that key.
Kramer, I need those cufflinks.
But now they're in the box,
and the key is in the bird.
What are we gonna do?
You just answered your own question.
Oh, no.
I'll get the shovel.
The, uh, actor that played Jesus
made some odd choices.
What?
I mean, uh...
I had fun ice skating.
George?
Maura!
Oh, my God!
What are you doing here?
You told me to meet you here for lunch.
Oh, I'm caught in my own web of lies!
I'm Maura.
I'm Loretta. You want to join us?
This is all blowing up in my face!
My serious girlfriend and my torrid love affair
have accidentally crossed paths!
I have ruined three lives.
Well, I understand if you
never want to see me again, so...
George, what we have is too important.
We can work through this.
So can we.
What?
So this is still not over?
No.
You?
All right.
Elaine, wow, a TV, a stereo?
Yeah, and I got you a cord of wood,
so you won't have to burn 'em.
Oh, my God, Allison.
You're home early.
Who is this?
His wife.
You're poor and married?
Looks like it.
Who the hell are you?
I guess I'm Lois Loan.
Kramer, I can't believe we're grave robbers.
"Man's best friend."
Jerry, I want something like that
on my tombstone.
Oh, my God.
Here he is.
I don't want to dig him up.
All right, then you're the one
getting the key out of him.
I'll dig.
Listen, I heard that
Lassie #3 is buried around here.
I'm gonna go check it out.
Well, that was easy.
All right, honey.
One last look,
then you have to let Fredo rest in peace.
Hey, Kramer!
I dug Fredo up, now let's cut him open!
Oh, my God!
Hey, neighbor.
All right.
I'm gonna try giving them $55 each.
What do you think?
Give me forty, you'll never see me again.
So, what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna live here,
or are you gonna move out, or what?
Ah, I'll just take the fire escape
to get in and out of the building.
So, what's in the cooler?
Well, would you look at that.
Guess I forgot to lock it.
You mean it was open?
We desecrated a pet cemetery for nothing?
Well, this is one for the books, huh, Jerry?
Really one for the books.