What is Holland?
What do you mean, "what is it"?
It's a country right next to Belgium.
No, that's the Netherlands.
Holland *is* the Netherlands.
Then who are the Dutch?
You know I cannot stand this thing anymore.
I know, I hate it too.
I feel like an out of work
porn star.
I told you, we should have taken
some kind of vacation.
Well why didn't we?
Because you said this would be better.
Remember?
A  vacation from ourselves.
That's what you said.
What if we grew muttonchops?
No.
Buzz cuts? Parachute pants!
Stop it, George. Stop it.
I'm sorry, you've gotta get a job.
Dammit.
Hey hey hey, check me out, huh?
No more crutches,
that must be a relief.
Yeah, with crutches
everyone has questions.
Not with a cane?
Nah, with crutches
it's a funny story,
with a cane it's a sad story.
You through with those?
Always a sad story. Hey, you
should have been here tonight.
Some guy from NBC saw my set,
he wants me to do a showcase.
I might have another shot
at a pilot.
Alright, we're back in!
We? No.
Ladies and gentlemen, Kenny Bania.
Thank you, thank you,
Hey, Jerry, didja see me up there?
I was killing, Jerry.
Killing. I killed.
Killed?
Killed.
I'm gonna go pick
up some chicks.
Good looking ones,too!
Hey, what's your name?
Killed.
Because I killed first
and warmed up the crowd.
He's like that fish
that attaches himself to the shark.
And you're the shark?
Yeah, I'm the shark and he's
the fish eating my laughs.
I don't know how
a fish could eat laughs.
Well, I'm glad
I brought it up.
Got any shredded coconut?
Uh, we're not doing that anymore.
Yeah, yeah, right.
Oh my god.
What?
I got a job interview.
They want to see me this afternoon.
So what's this job?
Oh, it's beautiful. It's in sports.
Knicks? Rangers?
Playground equipment.
Welcome back to the show.
Yeah, this is better.
So, you got any shredded coconut?
No.
I gotta hobble.
D-d-d-d. I gotta switch shaving
cream. I'm getting no protection.
What kind do you use?
Whatever you get.
Look, postcard from Elaine
from Europe.
Don't tell me she's dragging another
poor guy across Europe.
Remember David Puddy?
She's dating him again, huh?
Well, I guess she's batted around
and she's back at the top of the order.
Boy, a month in Europe with Elaine.
That guy's coming home in
a body bag.
Well, let's see, I've got a ten kroner,
a five kroner, a twenty kroner.
No wait, that's another ten kroner.
A fimty kroner?
How much is that?
We have to break up.
What?
I can't take this anymore!
I don't want to hear how interesting
the change with the hole in it is!
And if you tell me what time
it is in New York again,
you are going home in a body bag!
Well what about you?
What do you think The Gap in Rome
has that's notin The Gap on Broadway?
Okay, alright listen. Forget about
The Gap because we are through!
Fine!
Okay, terminal three.
Have a nice flight.
Ladies and gentlemen, our flight time,
with stopovers, will be
approximately 22 hours.
Hey, you gonna bust out
that drink cart or what?
Hey, what are you doing?
Oh, I'm taking this lace out.
It came undone and
touched the floor of a
men's room. That's the end of that.
Did you see Bania's set last night?
'Cause I read on the Internet
he killed.
He killed. He only does well when
he has me for a lead-in.
He's a time slot hit.
Well, you gotta give him
some credit.
You're just being totally ridiculous.
I'll see you later buddy.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute.
What?
Do I have to ask?
I ran out of butter so I had
to borrow yours.
Anything else, Mr. Nosy?
Why are you buttering your face?
I'm shaving with it.
Oh Moses smell the roses.
Jerry, it's vastly superior to any
commercial shaving cream.
Now feel  my face.
No.
Feel it.
I don't want to.
Feel it. Feel it.
That is close.
I got the job?
I don't want you to think that
anyone's gonna treat you any differently
just because of your, uh, handicap.
Handicap?
I'm not handicapped.
I'm sorry. Differently, uh, advantaged.
Yeah, I didn't mean that.
Of course you will have your own private,
fully equipped bathroom.
When do I start?
Whenever you feel
that you're able.
Um, you need a hand here.
Yeah, what the hell.
You got the job?
Jerry, it's fantastic.
I love the people over there.
hey treat me sogreat.
You know they think I'm handicapped,
they gave me this incredible
office, a great view.
Hold on, they think
you're handicapped?
Yeah, yeah, well,
because of the cane.
You should see the bathroom
they gave me!
How can you do this?
Jerry, let's face it,
I've always been handicapped.
I'm just now getting
the recognition for it.
Name one thing I have that puts me in a
position of advantage. Huh?
There was a guy that worked
at the Yankees-- no arms!
He got more work done than
I did, made more money,
had a wife, a family, drove
a better car than I did.
He drove a car
with no arms?
Alright I made up the part about the car,
but the rest is true.
He hated me anyway!
Do you know how hard it's getting
just to tell people I know you?
I love that bathroom.
It's got that high, high toilet.
I feel like a gargoyle perched
on the ledge of a building.
They hooked me up.
What's with all the butter?
I'm shaving with it, and you know
what I discovered?
You can eat it?
No, my face feels so good,
I'm gonna use it all over my body.
Oh my god, it's Bania and Jenna.
Who?
The tooth brush
in the toilet bowl.
Hey Jerry, this is Jenna.
Pretty good lookin' huh?
Jerry's the guy that I dated
right before you.
Oh. This is awkward.
Don't worry, Kenny.
After dating Jerry, you're a pleasure.
I don't believe this.
You miss her, don't you?
No! He's riding my coattails again.
He's getting everything off me,
first laughs now ladies.
You miss her.
You know I think ultimately,
I'm upset with myself.
I knew what I was getting into,
she's a bitter, unstable person.
I   mean the sex was good.
I'm sure it was fine for her.
I need more.
Huh. You believing this?
Excuse me, I was sleeping.
You missed quite a performance.
That's my apple juice.
Someone's cooking.
Hello, Jerry.
Hello, Newman.
You know, old friend,
sometimes I ponder this silly gulf
between us and I say, "Why?"
Are we really so different. For what is--
I'm not the one doing the cooking,
Newman.
Damn you Seinfeld.
You useless pustule.
Um, somebody's got something
on the griddle. maybe it's Kramer.
No, he's up on the roof getting
some sun with the butter
Oh no!
Butter?
-Fimty kroner.
You know my last boyfriend, he had
a real kroner comprehension problem.
No what I mean?
A real cement head.
David, you are so funny.
Yeah, I know.
What are you doing?
It's a long flight, Elaine.
I had to get on with my life.
By making time with some floozy
across the aisle?
Yeah, that's right.
Well, what's going on over there with you
and, uh, vegetable lasagna?
This guy? He's an idiot.
I can here you.
Well, she doesn't mean
anything to me either.
If it were up to me, we'd
still be together.
Well maybe I feel
the same way.
Ok.
Ok, so now what?
Let's make out.
Kramer!
Oh, man. I think I cooked myself.
Look at your skin.
Stick a fork in me, Jerry. I'm done.
I'm fried.
Technically, you're sautéed.
So, what are you doing for that?
Well, I just gotta keep my skin
moist so I don't dry out.
Is that what the doctor said?
No, I read an article in
Bon Appetite magazine.
Hmm. Game hen?
Kind of. Nice limp, you're bringing
your work home with you?
No, I fake limp on my right.
This is a real limp because
I sprained my ankle.
What happened?
Well, I was buttering myself up
for a nice shave
Oh no, not you too?
I must have dripped some
on the floor and I slipped and...
You know what's good for that?
Relish.
Hello? Yeah, this is
Jerry Seinfeld.
What? No. No! No! No!! No!!!
Thank you.
I don't believe this.
They've added Bania to the
network showcase
and he's going on right after me.
So what, he's got
a couple of good jokes.
Like what, Ovaltine?
Why do dogs drink out of the toilet?
Shopping carts with
one bad wheel?
That's true, that always happens to me.
You think that's funny?
I don't know, I like stuff
you don't have to think about too much.
You like Bania's act.
You're a closet Bania fan!
maybe I am.
Oh, I'm gonna puke.
Puke! That's a funny word.
Puke. puke! Don't have to
think about that.
I can't believe
we broke up like that.
Do you want something to read?
Nah.
Well, are you going
to take a nap or
You're just going to sit there
staring at the back of a seat?
Yeah.
That's it! I cannot
take this!
I mean, look at this,
nothing has changed.
We're back together two hours,
we're having the same problems
we had  12 hours ago.
Tell me about it, I don't know
why I ever took you back.
Please! I took you back.
You know it, I know it,
vegetable lasagna here knows it.
I don't want to get involved.
and we just ram right into it
and end this whole thing!
Oh god.
Ow! Ow!!
How much longer you gonna be,
I'm starving here.
Just a few more squirts.
Cause I gotta stay juicy.
The smell. It's still
with you, huh?
Yeah, it's baked on it.
Put some butter in.
Stir it up so it melts.
Ahh, now I'm simmering.
I'll meet you at the coffee shop.
Good morning, George.
Is something wrong
with your other leg
Oh, no, that's just the
old handicap acting up.
But your cane's on
the wrong side.
That's just because we're standing
on opposite sides.
See, when we
met, I was over there a
and you were over here so the image
was reversed, like in the mirror.
See? This looks right to you,
doesn't it?
Uh, yeah, I guess.
But, see here.
Right. Wrong. Right. Wrong. Right.
Will you stop it, George?
Just stop it!
I think I can see
what's going on here.
Well, you're not gonna believe
what happened.
You mugged Stephen Hawking?
Play Now thinks I got problems
in both legs.
My own personal Rascal,
Jerry. On the house.
Well it must be comforting to know
you'll be going straight to hell at
no more than three miles an hour.
Hello?
Jerry.
Hey, Lainie, how's
the trip going?
Awful. This trip was
a *huge* mistake. Huge!
Please don't shout.
I can't take it.
Who's that?
It's Vegetable Lasagna.
Who?
Vegetable Lasagna!
My name is Magnus.
Shut up or I'll snap you in half
and stuff you in the overhead!
Get me some duty free Kahlua.
How's the trip?
Sounded good.
Well. Gotta motor.
Hey, if you got any juice left,
you might wanna roll by
the big showcase  tonight.
Ah, you still going on in front of
Bania, eh?
That's right, and I'll tell you what.
I'm feeling a little off.
What are you talking about?
You're not!
That's right, I'm taking
a dive.
You're throwing the set?
I'm laying down! Then let's see
how he does up there,
without all the
assistance.
Listen Jerry.
Bania's voice is the voice of
a  new generation. My generation.
We're four months apart.
nevertheless. His time has come.
Now if you will kindly help me
unwedge my front wheel,
I'll be on my
way.
Butter. Kramer.
Hey buddy.
What are you doing?
George tells me you're gonna
throw your set?
That's right, Choochie.
Let's see how Bania does
without the cushy timeslot.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Jerry Seinfeld!
If you'll excuse me.
Hey everybody! Who's ready
to laugh?
What's the deal with lampshades?
I mean if it's a lamp, why
do you want
shade?
And what's with people
getting sick?
I mean, what's the dea
l with cancer?
I have cancer!
Oh, tough crowd.
Hey, hey! You dented
my ride.
Whatcha got there, the 4 volt?
Heh, I did you a favor.
How about I do you a favor
upside your head?
Oh yeah?
Oh yeah.
Hey!
Get the bikes.
Ouch.
You didn't do so bad.
What are you talking about?
I bombed!
No, you had some good stuff.
The cancer bit?
It was edgy, it was not my sort of thing
but some of those people out there,
they really liked it.
Like who?
Like that guy who yelled out.
He had cancer!
And laughter is the
best medicine.
Ladies and gentlemen, Kenny Bania!
Hey, Jerry, he could have used
your laugh.
He was a big turkey out
there.
Turkey?
A big fat turkey.
I'm sorry I missed that.
He worked so hard
and then he just--
What is this, oregano?
Look at me! I'm all covered
in oregano and Parmesan,
and it's sticking to me because
of the butter! Look at me!
Here. Hold this.
What is this, parsley?
Ah, the sweet stench
of failure.
Get off of me,
get off of me!
Now I got you!
George? Your legs!
Are you a religious man, sir?
no.
Eat hickory!!
Hey Jerry, didja see it?
Ouch.
Kenny! There you are.
Jay Shermak and Stu Crespi from NBC.
Listen, Kenny.
Really funny out there.
What?
That thing you did having
the two guys running through?
I love stuff you don't have
to think too much about
Give us a call. We want to be
in the Kenny Bania business.
By the way, Jerry? The suspenders?
A little hacky.
How about that Jerry?
First you had a pilot on NBC
and now I'll have one.
Looks like I'm following
you again.
Oh, I'm gonna puke.
Puke? That's a funny word.
Can I use that?
David, this has been the worst
month of my life
and if I never see you
again it'll be too soon.
Ditto.
Oh that's origi-
Shut up.
86th and Broadway please.
I'm sorry lady, there's a
cab shortage.
The Transit Police are
making everybody share.
Oh no.
Hello! Oh no. I'm sorry.
Noooooooooooo!