So, Elaine,
are you going to sleep with me or what?
George, I just got off
a twenty-three hour plane ride.
I'm too tired to even vomit at the thought.
Fine. I'll ask you again
when you're rested.
Oh, I'm sure she'll come around.
Yeah, I hope so. For your sake!
I said I was sorry.
You can stuff you sorries in a sack, mister!
Would you please stop saying that?!
What's up with you two?
I don't want to talk about it.
So how was the big trip?
I don't want to talk about it!
Well, what happened to your nose?
I don't want to talk ab-ow!-t it!
Well, you gotta give me something!
Come on, how was the wedding?
Was the bride radiant?
She.. was.
'Till she found out Elaine slept with the groom.
Ooohh.
That sounds juicy.
Listen, I gotta go to the bathroom,
but I want to hear all about it.
You know, I didn't go to the bathroom
the entire time we were in India.
I can't believe we went all the way to India
for a wedding!
That's it!
The wedding's off.
What?
But, Sue Ellen -
Elaine, you were my maid of honor
and you slept with my Pinter?!
No, no, no!
It was years ago - before you met him.
And, and I got to tell you -
it was very mechanical.
I have never been so humiliated!
Idiots! This is all your fault!
Not me! Him! His fault! He betrayed me!
George, I'm sorry..
You can stuff your sorries in a sack, Mister!
I don't know what that means.
Alright, Nina, you have to decide right now.
Jerry or me?
Alright.. Neither.
What?!
Well, what are you doing here?
A free trip to India.
And by the way, you can take off those boots.
Everyone knows you're 5'6".
5'8"!
5'7"!
See? See the way they are?!
We're - we're still best friends, right?
No.
And take that stupid thing out of your nose!
That's got to hurt,
I don't care where you're from!
What time is our flight back?
I got to go to the bathroom.
Hey.
- Hey.
What happened last night?
Oh, you were pretty loaded.
I know. I woke up with this.
Oh. Hello, Tetanus.
George, I've used the bathroom.
3It's fine.
No, no, no, no.
I can walk it off.
It's a hundred and twenty degrees in here.
I'll sweat it out.
Hey.
Are those Timberlands...
painted black?
Is your nose pierced?
Yeah.  Sit down there.
I believe you know Nina.
George, we need to talk.
I think you've done a lot more than talk!
You betrayed me!
Alright, I admit it.
I slept with Nina, but that's all.
"That's all"?! That's everything!
I don't know what all the rest of it
is for anyway!
I'm really sorry.
You can stuff your sorries in a sack, mister!
Where'd you get that one?
It's an expression.
Hey! Shhh!
Look, we are gonna settle this right now!
I demand reparations!
I should get to sleep with Elaine.
That's the only way to punish you!
That doesn't punish me.
It punishes Elaine!
And cruelly, I might add.
Funny guy!
Hey! Monkeys!
Knock it off.
My best friend
is trying to get married up here!
Elaine, you have to sleep with me.
I'm not gonna sleep with you.
Reparations!
Would you grow up, George?!
What is the difference?
Nina slept with  him, he slept with me,
I slept with Pinter.
Nobody cares! It's all ancient history.
You slept with the groom?!
Oh, thank you, FDR!
I stuck a rock in there too.
- I felt that.
Alright, FDR.
This wish is for all the marbles.
You win, you get your wish -
I drop dead.
I win, I don't drop dead,
and I get one-hundred percent
anti-drop-dead protection. Forever.
Alright.
Oh, man!
Well, then, come on.
There's got to be something
that'll change your mind, FDR.
Something...
What, you want my kidney?
Mama!..
George knows that you slept with Nina.
That's why he was acting so weird.
How did he find out?
He schnapped me.
You know you're not supposed to drink
while you're keeping a secret!
Is there anything else?
I can't tell you.
Here, drink this.
I slept with the groom.
Pinter?
He used to be called Peter.
So? Who cares about that?
Sue Ellen!
If she knew,
she'd call off the whole wedding.
Oh, nobody's calling off any weddings.
Alright, it's time to go.
Come on. Up.
Do you know what 'Jerry' is in Indian?
No, what?
Jugdish.
Yes, jugdish.
Hey, what if I got my nose pierced?
That would be pretty freaky.
Yes, I think it's a fine idea.
Well, good night.
Good night, Jugdish!
Bless you.
Thank you..
Hello FDR.
I'll have a hot one, everything on it.
These things will kill you.
But so what? You're already gonna drop dead.
Well, guess what, FDR?
I made a wish on a shooting star last night,
and I wished against your wish.
That's funny.
As it happens, I saw the same shooting star,
and I double-wished you to drop dead.
Here's your change.
Alright, I'm triple-wishing!
Yep!
Then I'm quadruple-wishing!
Alright -
how do you like this?
I like it a lot.
Oh, God, it's so hot!
What is that smell?
I think it's the stench of death.
George, you've been wearing those boots
since I met you.
You're not gonna wear them to the wedding,
are you?
No.. I'm gonna wear black shoes.
Oh boy. There's Sue Ellen.
She didn't want me at this wedding,
but here I am with a bunch of my idiot friends!
This is gonna be great!
Elaine? Oh! Oh, I am so happy to see you!
You are?
Well, of course!
No one else was even
willing to come to India.
I mean, not even Pinter's parents -
and they're Indian.
Come on, Sue Ellen.
You don't wear a bra, you're tall -
we hate each other!
Elaine, I know.
I know we've had our problems, but -
I want you to be my maid of honor -
and my best friend.
Huh.. alright. I guess.
Uh, this is my fiance, Pinter.
Say hello.
Hello.
Peter?
Uh, no. It's Pinter.
Does anyone want to use the bathroom?
Oh, no. No. We're good.
Let's get goin'. Alright.
Watch it, funny man!
Elaine, have you noticed
George was acting strange the whole flight?
No. What? Like what?
What? Strange... No. I...
Look what they had on the plane.
Schnapps.
Ooohh.
Come on.. Come on.
Yes!
There's one!
I wish I don't drop dead!!
Hey, shut up up there!
You shut up!
Aw, drop dead!
Hello, friend.
Enjoying the flight?
Coach to India - The only way to go.
Good one. Very funny.
You're very funny, Jerry.
That's what I always tell people.
Jerry Seinfeld's a funny guy!
You all right?
Of course I'm all right.
I'm here with my girl. Nina.
And what better way to pass the time
than gabbing with my best friend,
with whom there are no secrets.
Like this. Since fourth grade.
Hey, didn't I beat you up
in the fourth grade?
Funny guy!
Right here!
By the way, you never said anything
to George about Jerry and me, did you?
Oh please.
It's in the vault.
Ho, ho! Jerry Seinfeld's a funny guy!
Hey, what time is it?
You just asked me two minutes ago.
I'm not wearing a watch.
Is this tooth chipped?
Yeah. How'd you do that?
I have no idea.
Watch this.
Oh, God.
So, Jerry and Nina, huh?
Oh, m-m.
I'm not gonna tell you any more things.
You already told me everything.
Okey-dokey.
I mean, we had a deal, Newman.
You were supposed to
give my your birthday wish.
And now you've wasted it!
Did I?
Newman, I'm bored.
Aww.
Does your girlfriend have to be here?
Does yours?
I'm just hanging out in this hellhole
because of George.
Alright, come on, Newman. Now you gotta help me!
What am I gonna do about FDR?
Why don't you just make another wish?
And how am I gonna do that, Toots?
What about a shooting star?
That's perfect.
Beauty... and brains.
Oh, come on.
You know he's a postman, don't ya?
Here's your plane ticket.
What are you talking about?
Sue Ellen sends me an invitation
one week before her wedding in India.
I'll show her.
By flying halfway around the world?
Spite never sleeps!
Wish you wouldn't have gotten a layover in Sarajevo.
Hey.
Here. You're going to India with us tomarrow.
For how long?
Three days.
Great.
Jerry, I gotta tell you, I had the best time with that Nina last night.
I think I'm in love with her already.
You are a great friend. A great, great friend.
Hey, Kramer, what are you doing?
You want to borrow something? You want to eat something? Come on in!
You want to go to India?
I can't.  I'm gonna drop dead!
Great! Nina could go, huh?
Jerry, this is great. You and Elaine. Me and Nina..
Hey, Kramer, wait up. I'll go with you.
I'm goin' to Newman's!
Great, I love Newman!
Jerry seem a little weird when I mentioned Nina?
Nina? Nina? No. Psshhh.. Not weird. No. Nina.
Why do you keep saying Nina?
I don't know. Nina. Nina!
I'm gonna go grab a bite.
Uhh.. I'll meet you down there.
Cereal, cereal -
Peach schnapps.
Come on, Lomez! We're gonna be late for the movie.
You see, my dear, all certified mail is registered,
but registered mail is not necessarily certified.
I could listed to you talk about mail all day.
Anything you wish..
I'll tell you a little secret about ZIP codes:
They're meaningless!
Wish?! Newman!
Lomez, I'm leaving!
..And you smell like one, too.
Make a wish, Newman!
We've gotta get back to work in three hours!
Newman, wait!
Kramer!
I'm with people.
Yeah, yeah.
And thanks for inviting me!
I did invite you.
Your invitation must've gotten -
lost in the mail.
Well, Newman, I need your wish
to protect me from FDR.
Can't do it.
I'm on an unbelievable birthday-wish hot streak!
My last five birthday wishes came true.
Come on!
Look, I'll give you my next birthday wish, huh?
Your next.. fifty wishes.
Forty-eight.
Fourty-nine.
Done!
Sucker.
Alright, alright, back, savages.
Back! I haven't made my wish yet..
Well, this Mischke mish-mash is just gettin' worse.
I talked with the groom's parents
and it's so obvious that they don't want me to go.
And the only reason she sent me an invitation
was that so I'd send her a gift.
Jerry?
Uh, well, you know,
a coffee grinder is nice.
Or a coffee maker. Everyone likes coffee.
Anything to do with coffee.
Maybe you should go get some coffee.
Oh. Hi.
Hi.
Oh, I should.. um..
Sure.
Bye.
- Bye-bye.
Who else ya got back there?
Look, there was an awkward moment in the conversation.
It never happened before.
You slept with Nina?
What are you gonna tell George?
Nothing. And neither will you.
George can never know about this.
It'll crush him.
Uh. Alright, alright.
I'll put it in the vault.
No good.
Too many people know the combination.
What combination?
Don't be ridiculous.
Oh my god.
This drawer is filled with Fruit Loops!
So what?
And milk.
Oh, geez.
Hello?
Hi.
Mr and Mrs Ranawat?
Please, call us Usha and Zubin.
Oh.
Well, Usha...
I'm Zubin.
Anyway, your son is marrying
my friend, Sue Ellen Mischke...
You're not going to the wedding, are you?
Well...
Don't go.
India is a dreadful, dreadful place.
You know, it's the only country
that still has the plague?
I mean, the plague! Please!
Here's the registry.
Send her a gift,
and be glad you did not have to go.
Right. Don't go. Send a gift.
I think I understand.
If I had to go to India,
I wouldn't go to the bathroom the entire trip.
That's fantastic.
And I'm not so crazy about Manhattan, either.
Oh, you were going to tell me all about George.
Ah, just remember when you see him tomorrow night
to tell him that the waiter liked him.
Really?
Believe me.
You know, I forgot how much fun it is hanging out with you.
I know.
You know, we never had a bad conversation.
I know. No awkward pauses.
Probably the reason we never fooled around.
Heh... yeah.
Probably the reason...
Are - are you dense?
I said I wanted you to drop dead. Now.. drop dead!
I knew it.
Stupid Jerry.
Kramer, I know what I'm talking about.
There's no way FDR wants you to drop dead.
But you haven't seen...
- Just go back and ask him again.
That's right.
My birthday wish was that you drop dead.
Well, why?
I have my reasons.
Woah, wait, wait, wait.
If you make a birthday wish out loud,
it doesn't come true.
That's just a silly superstition.
Hey, FDR wants me to drop dead.
FDR?
I go to his birthday party,
and just before he blew out his candles, he gives me this look...
Stink eye?
Crook eye?
Evil eye.
Well, everybody's a little cranky on their birthday.
Oh, it's a bad day.
You got everyone in your house,
you're thinking, "these are my friends?"
Everyday is my birthday.
I can't have this hanging over my head.
It's bad mojo.
Hi.
You're not gonna believe
what I got in the mail.
Invitation to Sue Ellen Mischke's wedding.
Well, at least the wedding gown
will give her some support.
Not the point.
The wedding is in one week.
I got this today.
So you think it's a non-vite?
It's an un-vitation!
Hey, are you gettin' taller?
Timberlands.
Ah.
Hey, look at this.
'Pinter Ranawat'.
I wonder if he's related to that guy I dated, Peter Ranawat..
Ah, it's probably like Smith over there.
Jerry, would you make the call already?
What call?
He wants me to set him up
with this girl, Nina Stengal.
Oh, the great conversation girl.
The one you think can replace me?
I was kidding when I said that!
Told me the same thing.
Nina, Hi. It's Jerry.
You-you sure you never slept with her?
Perfect.
Hey, how 'bout my friend, George?
Quite a guy, huh?
Ooh.. Something's not sitting right..
I'll have the clams Casino.
Get outta here.
"Chef recommends"
I think she likes me.
Sure.
So, how come nothing ever happened
between you and Nina?
Is there a problem with her?
Is she a man?
Are you?
Well, what's the reason?
We were too compatible.
Our conversations were so engrossing.
How engrossing?
If we ever had a problem with Elaine,
we could bring in Nina and not lose a step.
You don't, huh, have a replacement
lined up for me, do ya?
Anyway, like I was saying,
I couldn't make the trasition from conversation to sex.
There were no awkward pauses.
I need an awkward pause.
I'm all awkward pauses.
Fix me up with her.
Wait a minute,
Nina just saw me in my Timberlands!
Now I have to wear them
every time I see her.
Why?
In any other shoe,
I lose two inches.
I can't have a drop down.
We were eye to eye,
I can't go eye to chin!
So, you're gonna wear them
no matter what the situation?
In every situation.
No matter how silly I look.
Hm... tastes a little funky.
Oh, I'm sure it's fine.
...to you!
Come on, make a wish! Make a wish!
Yeah!
Ah, this is the kind of day
that almost makes you feel good to be alive.
Almost.
Hey, new Timberlands?
Yeah, and a whole new me.
I'm up two inches in these babies!
Really?
Five' eight. Five' seven.
Jerry?
Nina?
- Hi.
It's been years!
- Yeah!
George, this is Nina.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
India?
Yeah, right.
I'm going to India.
And they call it the World Wide Web.
You can e-mail anyone!
What are you, a scientist?!
Ah, I gotta go.
- Ah.
It's great talkin'.
Great talkin' to you.
What the hell is e-mail?
How was the date?
Pretty good. I think she might be the one.
- No.
Oh, French fries.
Fat, George.
Baked, uh, potato.
Sorry.
Yeah, you stuff your sorries in a sack, mister.
Hey, hey.
Yeah, check it out.
It's packin' tight!
What are you bringing snowballs in here for?
I need some water.
Ice it up nice and hard.
And when you throw it -
Oh look,  there's my friend, FDR.
I'm gonna nail him in the back of the head.
It's gonna be great!
Hi, Elaine.
- Hey!
Hey, let's go someplace else,
okay, Peter?
Oh, hey, how you doing?
Oh, hi. I-I'm Jerry Seinfeld.
I'm movin' in.
I saw your name on the buzz.
You must be Kessler.
Uh, no.
Actually, it's Kramer.
You need any help, or...?
No, thanks.
But I ordered a pizza.
You want some of it?
Uh, no, no, no.
I couldn't impose.
Why not? We're neighbors.
What's mine is yours.
Really?
Good night, Jugdish!