I just think, if you borrow my blender,
you should return it.
Why, what's the difference?
Come on. We're like Cain and Abel.
You know, Cain slew Abel.
He didn't. They were in business together.
Drywalling or something.
All right, then what was it?
Well, I think Abel worked hard all summer,
harvesting his crops,
while Cain just played in the field.
Then when winter came, Abel had all the nuts.
Cain had no nuts. So he killed him.
The way I remember it,
Cain was a successful doctor,
but when he took this special formula,
he became Mr Abel.
You broke my blender, didn't you?
Yeah. When I was trying to make gravel.
It just didn't work out.
Why were you making gravel?
Well ... I like the sound it makes
when you walk on it.
This looks familiar.
Of course. It's garbage.
No, no, no, no. These brown things.
The chairs.
Jerry, this is the set
from the old Merv Griffin Show!
They must be throwing it out.
This stuff belongs in the Smithsonian!
Yeah, at least in the dumpster
behind the Smithsonian.
Boy, one minute Elliot Gold is sitting on you
and the next thing - you're yesterday's trash.
Come on, Kramer, get out of there.
No, no, no. You go on ahead.
I'm not finished taking this in.
Oh, Jerry, look!
Merv Griffin's cigar!
You know, I spilled a yohgurt smoothie
in here two days ago.
Can't smell anything, can y'a?
Banana?
Right.
George watch out for those pigeons.
Oh they'll get out of the way.
You really smell banana?
Oh my God. Oh.
So, uh--
where are we eating?
And it was his idea to put
a sprig of parsley on the plate.
You're making this up.
There was never a Joseph Garnish.
Wow!
Oh yeah the toys.
Where did you get all these?
My dad was a collector.
I inherited them after he died
from a long and painful bout ...
Super bowl!
Hey, an original G. I. Joe.
With the full frogman suit.
Jerry, what are you doing?
I'm putting this on him
and we're going to the sink.
No, Jerry!
They're priceless.
They've never been played with.
I just want to touch them a little.
I said no. Now come here.
Hi!
I'm Lou Filerman. I'm new here.
Hey, Walter,
what is the deal with that guy?
Oh, he's Lou Filerman.
He's new here.
Hey, your coffee stain
looks like Fidel Castro.
You've been an enormous help.
You ran over some pigeons?
How many?
Whatever they had.
Miranda thinks I'm a butcher.
But it's not my fault is it?
Don't we have a deal with the pigeons?
Of course we have a deal.
They get out of the way of our cars,
we look the other way
on the statue defecation.
Right!
And these pigeons broke the deal.
I will not accept the blame for this.
So Miranda's cooled on ya?
I'm getting nothing.
Yeah, me neither.
Really?
I thought you and Celia were sleeping together?
Oh, the sex is wild,
but she's got this incredible toy collection
and she won't let me near it!
I don't understand women.
Here comes one.
Hey. What's going on?
Hey.
Art Garfunkle?
No, Castro.
Right.
All because of
this creepy new guy at work.
He just comes out of nowhere
and he's right next to you!
So he just sidles up?
That's right! He's a real sidler.
Maybe you didn't see him.
You never see him.
He sidled me again in my office.
I was sitting there making a cup of soup,
singing that song from "The Lion King".
Hakuna Matata?
I thought I was alone.
That doesn't make it right.
See, to me, the Hakuna Matata
is not nearly as embarrassing as the cup of soup...
Would you just let it go?
Hey, Jerry! Come in here a sec!
Hey!
Oh my God!
It's the Merv Griffin set.
How did you get this in here?
Oh, you just bring it in sideways and hook it.
So where are you gonna sleep?
Yeah ... backstage.
Phew! This chair smells like garbage.
Oh, well a lot of the stars from the 70's -
they were not as hygienic as they appeared on TV.
Take Mannix for example.
I'm gonna get that.
All right. Well, Jerry,
we'd love to have you back anytime.
Well, Elaine Benes!
Well, it's great to have you!
Why, is it possible that you are even more beautiful
than the last time I saw you?
We had a deal!
Mr. Peterman,
here are these pages that you wanted.
One moment!
I'm reading the most fascinating article
on the most fascinating people of the year.
And - done.
Oh, yes. I'm sorry I needed this so quickly.
It must have been an awful lot of work.
Thank you very much, you two.
What?
So, three dates, and she still won't
let me play with her toys.
That's interesting.
You know, someone mentioned to me
you were not very happy with your toys growing up?
Yeah, that was me.
Oh, that's right, right, right.
And you mentioned that you didn't get a G.I. Joe.
You had -
An Army Pete.
Right.
He was made of wood,
and in the rain
he would swell up and then split.
And we all know how painful that can be.
Jerry?
Oh, Elaine Benes!
Well, this is quite a thrill, yes.
Come on sit down. Yes.
Well, I'll tell you,
this sidler guy is really chapping my hide.
Excuse me.
We're talking this way.
Well, he's getting credit for work I did!
He's gonna sidle me right out of a job.
Now, for those of us who don't know,
uh, sidling is what?
Kramer, what is wrong with you?
What do you mean?
Well, for starters,
you're looking at note cards.
I'm gonna have to give that guy
a taste of his own medicine.
So I am going to sidle the sidler.
You, sidle?
You stomp around like a Clydesdale!
Not with these honeys.
Wrestling shoes!
Only in New York!
Jerry?
Oh!
Well, ladies and gentlemen!
It's our good friend, George Costanza!
What a surprise!
Yeah, sit, sit, sit.. Weeell!
Well, it happened again.
What happened?
Tut tut, I'll ask the questions.
Well, I just stomped some pigeons in the park.
They - they didn't move.
All right, let's change the subject.
Now, you and Jerry dated for a while.
Tell us... what was that like?
That was the wrong card.
I don't get these birds!
They're breaking the deal.
It's like the pigeons decided to ignore me!
So they're like everyone else.
All right, let's take a short break.
Okay! We're back!
Boy, that bank clock is eight minutes off.
Then why don't you just run IT over too?
Zing.
George, what are you doing?
Did you see that?
That-that pigeon didn't move!
I had to swerve to get out of the way!
I saved that pigeon's life!
What pigeon?
You drove right onto that squirrel!
Squirrel?
Well, we have no deal with !
Jerry!
Those hands! They never stop!
I'm sorry.
You got any booze?
Let's say you and I get ripped!
No, thanks.
I have a headache.
Can you just get me an aspirin?
All right.
Ah. "Will not cause drowsiness."
"May cause drowsiness."
Here's the new copy you wanted.
Ah, yes.
Well, this certainly looks like a lot of words.
In record time. I'm very impressed ...
with both of you.
Thank you.
Unfortunately, I am also disgusted.
This is incoherent dribble!
This is a total redo,
and I'm assuming I need it right away.
Well, I guess we'll just have...
All right, just gimme that.
Mission accomplished! Back to base, Joe.
Doctor, is the squirrel going to live?
There's been massive trauma.
We could of course try to save him,
but it would be costly, difficult,
and we'd have to send away
for some special, really tiny instruments.
Well, uh, are there any other options?
We could put him to sleep.
What might that cost?
Well, it's by the pound, so -
about 80 cents.
Well?
I was just - I'm curious, that's all.
We - we'd like you to do everything possible.
He... he's not going to be the same, you know?
Yeah. Yeah. I know.
So they're flying the tiny instruments in
from El Paso.
El Paso? I spent a month there one night.
El Paso!
What's he here for?
To take some of the pressure off of me.
So, Jerry, what's going on with you?
I understand there's a young lady in your life?
Well, actually, it's kind of a funny story,
because she has this amazing toy collection
and last night I finally got to play with them.
Well.
It sounds like things are progressing.
Do I hear wedding bells?
Are you married right now?
- Newman!
Actually she doesn't even know
about the toys.
I gave her the wrong kind of medicine,
and I guess she passed out!
What do you mean "wrong kind of medicine"?
She's even got
that old Mattel football game that we love!
Oh, come on! You gotta get me over there!
Wait a minute, wait a minute!
You mean to say that you drugged a woman
so you could take advantage of her toys?
Let's pause a moment.
Jerry, now, what you do
with your personal life is your business,
but when you're on my set -
you clean it up, mister!
I told you he was a risk.
Oh, like he's not just carrying you!
And has been for years!
Yeah? Well, you bombed!
That story stunk worse than these chairs!
Smile, everyone!
We're back!
You wanted to see me, Elaine?
Yes, Lou.
You've got a lot going for you.
You're, ... um ... you're spontaneous.
You're symmetrical.
You're...
You're very quick, aren't ya?
It's just that your...
My dead tooth?
No. Your -
My breath?
Ugh.
What can I do?
Well, you should never ever go anywhere -
without these.
Thanks, Elaine.
You're such a super lady!
More wine and turkey?
So when I saw George on the street
with an 18 pound turkey and a giant box of wine,
I thought, what a coincidence.
We're just about to eat.
What is that stuff in turkey
that makes you sleepy?
Triptophan.
... I think.
Have some more wine.
What video did you get?
Oh, George brought
home movies of his boyhood trip to Michigan.
Four hours.
More heavy gravy?
Yes! Touch down!
Your turn, Jerry.
Lately though, I've been buying
the generic brand of waxed beans.
I rip of the label.
I can hardly tell the difference.
Well, we've officially bottomed out.
Who's our next guest?
We've got no one!
We need a new format.
We should shut down and re-tool.
What about a guest-host?
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
Doctor, how's the squirrel?
Is he dead?
No.
Fortunately, the special tiny instruments
arrived just in time.
Would you like to visit him?
Yes he would.
You have 30 minutes.
So, uh...
squirrel...
One more thing, Mister Costanza.
We just need to know
what time you'll be picking him up tomorrow.
What's that?
Oh, we're discharging the squirrel.
We think he'll be better off at home.
He has no home.
He's a squirrel.
Your home, Mister Costanza.
Just make sure he gets his medicine 6x a day
and keep his tail elevated.
Maybe it'll be fun having a pet.
It's not a pet!
It's a wild invalid!
And it knows that I tried to kill it.
As soon as it gets better,
it's gonna gnaw my brain out in my sleep!
Jerry, what are you doing tomorrow?
I want you to come by the set.
What about my "questionable material"?
Nope, we got a whole new format.
Edgy, youthful,
plus we got Jim Fowler!
Jim Fowler?
The animal guy from "Wild Kingdom"
is coming to your apartment?
Well, I practically raised his kids.
That's perfect!
He's a zoo guy!
He take's care of animals.
Can I bring the squirrel by?
What?
Two animal acts on the same show?
What is this, amateur hour?
Look, George, I'm sorry, but
maybe another time, all right?
I gotta get to Fowler.
I know he would take this squirrel off my hands.
It's practically bionic!
Hey!
Nice sidle, huh?
Speaking of which,
I think I've got that problem solved.
Tic-tacs worked?
He's a human maraca.
Boy, my knuckles are still cramped
from that football game.
You took him over to Celia's?
What?
It's a victimless crime.
What about the woman
who's been drugged and taken advantage of?
Okay, one victim.
I think it's unconscionable.
Last night I found a whole Weeble Village
right behind the EZ Bake oven.
EZ Bake oven?
Who wants cupcake?
Oh, me, me, me, me, me!
You know, that batter is
like 30 years old.
Why is your father giving
a tour of a rest stop?
Oh, don't look.
This is the part where they change me.
You're like eight years old.
I was seven and a half.
That noise.
That's the noise!
What?
That infernal rattling sound
that has plagued me these past two days.
And I could not find the source.
In my office, in the hallway.
Even in the men's room!
Shame on you, Elaine!
No, no, Mr Peterman,
that wasn't me!
That reminds me of
the Hatian Voodoo rattle torture!
You haven't gone over to their side have you?
No, Mr Peterman.
Because, if I hear one more rattle -
just one -
you're out on your can.
And if you are undead -
I'll find out about that too.
Lou! In here!
We have to talk.
Oh, right.
No, stop it!
Bad voodoo.
You gotta stop using these.
Why?
Because they're turning your teeth green?
I only buy the white ones.
Okay ...
Well, then your teeth are green
for a different reason.
Just stop carrying these, okay?
Just use mouth wash.
I can't. It burns my cankers.
Binacca?
Again.
Right, right, cankers.
Um, I got it! Chew gum!
I hate gum.
The only gum I ever liked
came with the Mickey Mouse gumball machine.
They stopped making that 20 years ago.
Well, stinky, this is your lucky day.
Okay. A little later,
we're gonna be talking with animal expert Jim Fowler.
Where are the cameras?
But first, we're talking with...
Jerry.
Okay, Jerry, uh, you drugged a woman
in order to play with her toy collection.
How do you feel about that?
It was great!
I've done it a few more time since then.
And she doesn't know anything about this?
No, not a thing.
laughs
Well, Jerry,
we have a little surprise for you!
Come on out, Celia!
What kind of a sick twisted creep are you?
Wow!
What is this?
What is she doing here?
It's the new format.
Scandals and Animals.
If you think you can drug me and play with my toys,
you got another thing coming, buddy!
Go girl!
Well, what kind of woman
drinks an entire box of wine?
Ohhh!
Mister Fowler, I have a squirrel here
that is a miracle of modern science!
George, I told you we're booked!
Careful.
Hawks and squirrels don't get along together.
Ohhh.
Another interesting confrontation.
This could be spicy.
Yeah, George, bring him over.
No, you idiot!
Hawks eat squirrels!
Are we getting this?
So the whole set was destroyed?
Well, the squirrel kept scurrying
and the hawk kept clawing.
Well, at least we know
the prosthetic squirrel hips work.
Sorry about the set.
I tell you, it was a grind
having to fill 10 hours a day.
I'm not sure I was ready
to have my own talk show set.
I got the nut bread, George.
Let's go.
So the squirrel's gonna make it?
Yeah, he's in my bed.
I'm sleeping on the couch.
On the couch?
So you're...
Still getting nothing!
Go ahead, pigeons.
Laugh it up.
I'm getting in my car now,
and the last I heard...
we have no deal!
I'm glad you called, Elaine.
I really needed to talk to someone.
Hey, I dated Jerry too.
I know what a monster he can be.
More wine and turkey?
Who's he?
Oh, he's nobody.
Hey, listen,
let me top that off for you.