Every mall has a Hoffritz in it.
That's got to be a scary place
to work. I don't know how you feel.
Do you want to stand there
having people going:
"I need knives.
I need more knives.
Do you have any bigger knives?
I'd like a bigger knife.
A big, long, sharp knife.
That's what I'm in the market for.
I like them really sharp.
Do you have one
with hooks and gouges...
...and blades
that are kind of serrated?
That's the kind of knife
I'm looking for.
I need one I can throw.
I need one I can hack away with.
Do you have anything like that?"
Like you know
what you're talking about.
Oh, no. You do?
Well, what do you think,
they put the statue on a giant raft...
...and a tugboat pulled it
all the way from France?
Think they brought it in pieces...
...and screwed it together
like a coffee table?
What's going on? It's a little early
for a Christmas party.
- Why'd France give that to us anyway?
- It was a gift.
Countries just exchange gifts
like that?
If they like each other.
- There's Elaine.
- See that guy she's talking with?
- That's her new boyfriend.
- Really?
He works here in the office?
They're having a little fling,
so don't say anything to anyone.
Who am I gonna tell, my mother?
Like I have nothing better to talk about.
You don't.
He's a recovering alcoholic.
- Really?
- He's been off the wagon two years.
- "Off the wagon"?
- I think it's "off the wagon."
I think it's "on the wagon."
Jerry, George,
what are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
My God! My watch!
You found my watch.
Keep your hands to yourself
if you know what's good for you.
- Where'd you find it?
- Under the sofa cushion.
- You stopped by just to give it to me?
- It's your Christmas present.
- I thought I'd never find it.
- Today's your lucky day.
No, today is your lucky day.
- It would be my first one.
- You want to work here?
- What?
- Yeah. One of the readers just left.
There's a job opening.
Dick, this is Jerry.
And this is George.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
- Is this the guy?
"The guy"?
- Dick.
- How can you just get it?
My boss said to find someone.
I'm in charge.
All you have to do is meet him.
Come on.
- No, come on. Hold my drink.
- Cranberry juice?
And vodka. Come on.
I got the cranberry juice.
So...
...you're Jerry.
- So...
...l'm Jerry.
So have you ever done
this kind of work before?
Well, you know, book reports,
that kind of stuff.
- Who do you read?
- I like Mike Lupica.
Mike Lupica?
He's a sportswriter
for the Daily News.
- I find him very insightful.
- No, I mean authors.
Well...
...a lot of good ones.
Lot of good ones.
I don't even wanna
mention anybody...
...because I'm afraid I'm gonna
leave somebody out.
- Name a couple.
- Who do I like?
I like Art Vandalay.
- Art Vandalay?
- He's an obscure writer.
Beatnik, you know, from the village.
What's he written?
Venetian Blinds.
I got news for you.
I'm funnier than you are.
Why don't we get together New Year's,
watch some football?
- Where's my drink?
- There. So how'd it go?
I think he's impressed.
No, no, this is just cranberry juice.
I think maybe Dick picked up yours.
Dick?
He can't drink. He's an alcoholic.
I told you to hold it.
I didn't know you meant hold it.
I thought you meant hold it.
One drink like that,
and he could fall right off the wagon.
Told you.
I never feel comfortable
in the women's department.
I feel like I'm just a little too close
to trying on a dress.
Do I really have to
buy her something?
The woman got you a job.
Least you could do is buy her a gift.
How about this?
- What is that, cashmere?
- Yeah. She loves cashmere.
Who doesn't like cashmere?
Find me one person that doesn't
like cashmere. It's too expensive.
Wow, look at this.
It's $85, marked down from 600.
- Excuse me, miss?
- Yes.
How come this sweater's only $85?
Oh, here. This is why.
- What? I don't see anything.
- See this red dot?
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, it's damaged.
It's not really damaged.
Wow. $85?
There's no exchanges on this.
- Think she'd care about the dot?
- It's hard to say.
I don't think she'd notice.
Can you see it?
- Well, I can see it.
- But you know where it is.
- What do you want me to do, not look?
- Pretend you didn't know it was there.
- Can you see it?
- It's hard to pretend...
...because I know where it is.
- Can't you take an overview?
You want me to take an overview?
I see a cheap man
holding a sweater...
...trying to get away with something.
That's my overview.
- Yeah, so?
- He's acting very strangely.
I think he started drinking again.
- Oh, boy. Can you smell it?
- No, I can't smell it.
If you can't smell it,
then he hasn't been drinking.
- You don't always smell from a drink.
- Yes, you do.
What about one drink?
Would you smell from one drink?
Yes, you would.
- I'll prove it.
- How?
- Would you do me a favour?
- Okay.
Would you take a drink,
and let us smell you?
You can smell me without the drink.
No, no.
I suspect that this guy I'm seeing
might be drinking, but I can't smell it.
- Come on.
- Okay. Well, what am I drinking?
I got a bottle of Scotch my uncle
gave me. Hennigan's.
It's been there two years.
I've been using it as a paint thinner.
All right.
- I don't smell anything.
- We're too close to the bottle.
- Yeah?
- It's George.
- Come on up.
- That is damn good Scotch.
I could do a commercial
for this stuff.
Boy, that Hennigan
goes down smooth...
...and afterwards,
you don't even smell.
That's right, folks. I just had three
shots of Hennigan's, and I don't smell.
Imagine, you can walk around
drunk all day.
That's Hennigan's,
the no-smell, no-tell Scotch.
- Hello, everybody.
- Hey, George, come here.
I'm gonna tell you what I think.
I know you don't care what I think,
but I'm gonna tell you.
I think that you are terrific.
That's all.
Thank you.
- Hey, what's that?
- It's an early Christmas present.
- A Christmas present?
- That's right.
- For who?
- For you.
Get out of here.
Say you got a big job interview
and you're nervous.
Throw back a couple of shots
of Hennigan's...
...and you'll be as loose as a goose
and ready to roll in no time.
And because it's odourless,
why, it'll be our little secret.
Kramer.
Yeah. That'll do.
Oh, George, this is beautiful.
Is this cashmere?
- Of course it's cashmere.
- Oh, I love cashmere.
- Who doesn't?
- Oh, my God.
George, this must have
cost a fortune.
Money.
Jerry, how could you
let him spend so much?
I tried to stop him.
I couldn't. He just wants
to make people happy.
George, this is one of the nicest
things anyone has ever given me.
Good. Good. Listen, take it off.
You're gonna wear it out already.
It's for special occasions, this thing.
What's that red dot
on your sweater?
- What?
- Listen, take it off.
I'm getting hot just looking at it.
What is this?
It's like a red dot.
What? What red dot?
What are you talking about?
Jerry, come here for a second.
Do you see anything here?
I don't know.
- What don't you know?
- I don't know.
Well, do you see it, or don't you?
Say that again.
Do you see it, or don't you?
Do I see it or don't I?
That's the question.
Now, what did you ask me again?
You're still here?
You're a dynamo.
- I can't believe I get paid for this.
- God.
I'll see you tomorrow.
- How you doing?
- Hello.
You had sex with the cleaning woman
on your desk?
Who are you?
How did you do that?
Hennigan's.
Hennigan's?
I was sitting there in the office,
and the cleaning woman comes in.
I've always been attracted
to cleaning women.
Cleaning women, chambermaids...
Yeah, chambermaids,
I'm attracted to them too.
- Why is that?
- It's a woman in your room.
- So go ahead.
- So...
...she starts vacuuming,
back and forth, back and forth...
...her hips swivelling...
...her breasts...
Convulsing?
- Convulsing?
- I don't know. I'm trying to help you.
So then I asked her
if she wanted a drink.
- You don't drink.
- I couldn't think of anything else to say.
- So you started drinking.
- So we started drinking, and...
I don't know if it was the alcohol
or the ammonia...
...but the next thing I knew,
she was mopping the floor with me.
- And how was it?
- The sex was okay...
...but I threw up
from the Hennigan's.
Good thing the cleaning lady
was there.
Dick was fired.
You mean to tell me, I put that drink
six inches over to the right...
...and this wouldn't have happened?
- You knew he was an alcoholic.
- Why'd you put the drink down?
- What are you saying?
- I'm not saying anything.
- Yes, you are.
- What could I be saying?
- You must be saying something.
If I was, I would have said it.
- Say it.
- I said it.
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
It's exhausting being with you.
- Yeah.
- It's George.
- Come on up.
- Hey.
Let me ask you something.
Did George buy that sweater
knowing the red dot was on it...
...because it was cheaper?
- Okay. You just gave me the answer.
- No, I didn't.
Yes, you did. Yes, you did.
I saw your expression.
I didn't have an expression.
I have a deviated septum.
I have to...
I have to open my mouth
sometimes to breathe.
How much did he save?
Frankly, I am shocked that you
could ask such a question of me.
If l... The only surprise was how
you could even think of that.
That's what you were seeing.
I have to talk to you.
This cleaning woman's
turning the screws on me.
She's pushing for this
whole relationship thing.
She keeps calling me.
She's threatening to go to the boss.
I could lose my job.
I gotta keep her quiet.
Elaine's in the bathroom.
She's wise to the red-dot thing.
She's asking me
all kinds of questions about it.
- Did you tell her anything?
- No.
- You swear?
- I'm not swearing. I don't wanna swear.
- Come on, swear.
- No.
- Oh, you told her, didn't you?
Hey, George, did you buy that sweater
knowing the red dot was on it...
...because you could get it
at a discount?
What?
- Did I what?
- You did, didn't you?
Elaine, I'm shocked.
I'm shocked.
Here I go out, in the spirit of the
season and spend all my savings...
...to buy you the most beautiful
Christmas sweater I have ever seen...
...to show my appreciation to you
at Christmas...
...and this is the thanks I get
at Christmas.
- Well, Jerry told me that you did.
- You told her?
How could you tell her?
What kind of friend are you?
I didn't tell her, you stupid idiot.
She tricked you.
Elaine, you don't understand.
I had a 103 temperature
when I bought that sweater.
I was so dizzy, I was seeing
red dots everywhere.
I thought everything in the store
had a red dot on it.
I couldn't distinguish one red dot
from the other.
I couldn't afford anything.
I have nothing. I haven't worked
for a really long time.
I mean, look, I have no clothes.
Look at what I'm wearing.
It was just a little red dot.
A little red dot.
- This is for you.
- Oh, Georgie, you bought this for me?
Oh, I knew you cared for me.
As you care for me,
which is why it's very important...
...that you never breathe a word
to anyone about...
You know? What with
Clarence Thomas and everything.
- Okay. Can I open it now?
- Yes, of course. Go ahead.
My guess is you're gonna
like this very much.
- Is that cashmere?
- Of course it's cashmere.
Oh, a cashmere sweater.
Oh, Georgie Porgie.
Just a little something for Christmas.
When I was a little girl in Panama,
a rich American came to our town.
And he was wearing the softest,
most beautiful sweater.
I said, "What do you call
this beautiful fabric?"
And he said:
"They call it cashmere."
I repeated the word.
"Cashmere, cashmere"...
...and I asked him if I could have it...
...and he said:
"No. Get away from me."
And he started to walk away.
Oh, but I grabbed onto his leg...
...screaming for him
to give me the sweater...
...and he dragged me
through the streets.
And then he kicked me
with the other foot...
...and he threw some change at me.
But I didn't want the change, Georgie.
I wanted the cashmere.
I had a feeling you would like it.
- I'm going to try it on.
- No. Don't try it on now. Try it later.
Oh, look, it fits beautiful.
All right, take it off.
You're gonna ruin it.
What's this?
I was in a men's room the other day.
They had the hand blower instead of
the paper towels. You know this thing?
I like the hand blower, I have to say.
Takes a little bit longer,
but I feel when you're in a room...
...with a revolting stench, you want
to spend as much time as you can.
The only stench is coming from you.
Oh, well, wait a second.
I believe we have a heckler,
ladies and gentlemen.
Dick, I don't know
what your problem is.
It's not my fault
you're back on the wagon.
It's "off the wagon."
In the old days, how do you think they
got the alcohol from town to town?
- I don't know.
- On a wagon.
Don't you think they broke into a
couple of those bottles along the way?
You can't drink on a wagon.
It's too bumpy.
They had smooth trails.
What about the Cumberland Gap?
What the hell do you know
about wagons?
I know enough not to get on them.
I'm gonna get right to the point.
It's come to my attention
that you and the cleaning woman...
...have engaged in sexual intercourse
on the desk in your office.
Is that correct?
- Who said that?
- She did.
Was that wrong?
Should I not have done that?
I gotta plead ignorance
on this thing...
...because if anyone
had said anything to me...
...when I started here that that
sort of thing was frowned upon...
You know, because I've worked
in a lot of offices...
...and I tell you,
people do that all the time.
You're fired.
Well, you didn't have
to say it like that.
I want you out of here
by the end of the day.
What about the whole Christmas-spirit
thing? Any flexibility there?
No.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
She wanted me to give you this.
You had sex on your desk
with the cleaning woman.
You never had sex
in the office before?
No. I once made out with someone,
but that's it.
Okay. All right. So you made out.
- Well, that's not sex.
- Kissing is sex.
Kissing is not sex.
- George.
- Jerry.
Hey, did Jerry leave that drink
next to Dick's on purpose?
- No.
- George?
Over here.
What are you doing here?
I'm taking the kid out to dinner
to cheer him up.
Hey, Jerry, when do you consider sex
has taken place?
I would say...
...when the nipple
makes its first appearance.
So George told me that you left
the drink next to Dick's on purpose.
Nice try.
So guess who heckled me
at the club last night.
Merry Christmas!
- Oh, my God, that's Dick.
- Dick?
Dick!
It's Cape Fear.
Hide. Hide under the desk.
- Move over.
- Get off of me.
- I have no room.
- My foot's sticking out.
Shut up. He's coming.
Is that cashmere?
Of course it's cashmere.
What's this?
But, in a way, I think I inadvertently
turned this guy into an alcoholic.
I hate being around alcoholics.
They're either saying how much they
love you or how much they hate you.
Those are the two statements
that scare me most.
But I think he's okay now because
I don't know how he feels about me.
- He's finally off the wagon.
- You mean on the wagon.
Don't get smart.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
I'm going to get
a physical examination.
That urine sample. Giving them that,
that's always a pleasure, isn't it?
Then there's always
the amount question:
"I don't know what you need.
I gave you whatever I had there.
I got more. Whatever you need,
I can get it for you.
Just let me know what you need.
It's no problem, I mean..."
But any kind of physical test,
I don't know what it is...
...I always click into this thing
where I wanna do really well.
If it's gonna be a physical test,
I wanna do well.
Remember in school,
they'd do hearing tests?
And you'd really be listening,
you know...
...trying to really...
Trying to do well, I wanna do well.
I wanted to do unbelievable
on that test.
I wanted them to come to me
after the test and go:
"We think you may have something
close to super hearing.
What you heard was a cotton ball
touching a piece of felt.
We're sending the results
to Washington.
We'd like you
to meet the president."
Let me ask you a question.
If you named a kid Rasputin...
...do you think that would have
a negative effect on his life?
No.
What are you doing?
We're going out to dinner.
Do you realize this is the last meal
I'm gonna have for three days?
- Yeah.
- George.
Come on up.
I never heard of this. You gotta fast
for three days to take an ulcer test.
- How will you do that?
- I don't know.
How could I possibly have ulcers?
Who could have given me ulcers?
I think I'll take out the garbage.
Have you ever fasted?
Well, once I didn't have
dinner till, like, 9:00.
I'll tell you, that was pretty rough.
Hey. Do me a favour, will you?
Throw out my garbage for me.
Yeah. Right.
Come on. It's just down the hall.
Give me 2 bucks.
I'll do it for 2 bucks.
I'll give you 50 cents.
There's no way I'd touch that bag
for less than $2.
Come on, 50 cents. You can
get yourself a Drake's Coffee Cake.
You're not getting no
Drake's Coffee Cake for 50 cents.
I'm all set. I got the ticket. I'm going
to the Cayman Islands Friday.
I don't get you. Who goes
on vacation without a job?
What do you need, a break
from getting up at 11?
It's a deal. I don't know
why you don't come with me.
I don't go for nonrefundable deals.
I can't commit to a woman,
I'm not committing to an airline.
- Hi.
How are you?
Gina, do you know
Drake's Coffee Cake?
The plain cake with the sweet
brown crumbs on the top.
- Right. How much do they cost?
- The junior?
- No, the full-size.
- No, junior.
- You didn't say "junior."
- I haven't had one since I was little.
Really?
You should be ashamed of yourself.
I want you out of here.
- How you doing?
- Good enough.
- Boy, she's sexy, isn't she?
- Yeah.
- Do you believe that guy?
- What guy?
- My neighbour.
- That creepy guy?
- Did he think I was flirting with her?
- He didn't seem too pleased.
Maybe I'll get a steak
with French-fried onion rings.
Hey, you know what?
I just remembered something.
I had a dream about that guy
last night. This is amazing.
- Amazing? You've seen him before.
- I haven't seen him in months.
What was the dream?
He was doing standup comedy
in Kennebunkport, Maine...
...in this really ominous nightclub.
The stage was on a cliff
and the audience...
...was throwing all the comics off.
I think I've played there.
I've had a lot of paranormal stuff
happen to me.
You're a little paranormal.
Name one paranormal thing
that happened to you.
- I knew I was gonna be bald.
- Your father's bald.
Baldness is inherited
from the mother's side, Jerry.
But your mother's bald too.
George, you know,
my friend goes to a psychic.
- Really?
- We should go sometime.
I'd love to go.
Make an appointment.
Psychics, vacations.
How about getting a job?
- I just got fired.
- All right. Let's get out of here.
I wonder what Gandhi ate
before his fast.
I heard he used to polish off
a box of Triscuits.
- Really?
- Oh, yeah. Gandhi loved Triscuits.
Who is it?
- Who is it?
- It's Gina!
- Who?
- Martin's girlfriend.
- Martin?
- Your next-door neighbour.
Oh, Martin!
It's Martin. I think he's dying.
He tried to kill himself with pills.
- What?
- Come on.
- Let me get my robe.
- We do not have time.
- Two seconds.
- There's no time.
- We don't have two seconds?
- All right, go ahead.
- No, forget it.
- No, go ahead.
- No, I'll just wear the pyjamas.
- Just get it!
- Are you sure?
- Forget it. Come on.
No, I'll go get the robe.
It's not too bad. It's not
like a Sunny von Bülow coma.
Doctor said he should
snap out of it any time.
You know why he did this?
Because I told him it was over.
- I did not want to see him anymore.
- Really? It's over?
I could not stand it another minute.
Yesterday, he turned over
a hot dog stand...
...because he thought
the man looked at me.
Then, after he saw you in the hall...
He was crazy with jealousy.
Oh, boy.
Did he say anything about me?
He does not like you.
And all indications are he does not
like Drake's Coffee Cake.
- He said that?
- He was screaming about it all night.
How it's too sweet and
it falls apart when you eat it.
I'm sorry if I caused any trouble.
I was just being friendly.
I wasn't.
You weren't?
No. I have thought
about you many times.
- Have you thought about me?
- Of course.
Tell me everything.
Are you sure
he can't hear anything?
Martin.
Martin!
I wish he was not in a coma.
I wish he was dead.
I would like to pull the plug out
from him!
I would wait on that one.
I know how you feel,
but juries today...
...you never know how
they're gonna look at this.
I saw you looking at your watch.
You want to leave? Go ahead.
- I wanted to see what time it was.
- Are you afraid of him?
- No.
- Then kiss me.
- Here?
- Yes, right here.
Is this the proper venue?
- You don't want to?
- No, no, I want to.
I very much want to. I desire to.
I pine to.
Then kiss me right in front of him.
I can't! What if he wakes up?
A man is lying here unconscious
and you're afraid of him?
What kind of a man are you?
I'm a man who respects a good coma.
If it was one of those
in-and-out comas, maybe.
But when a guy's got a coma
going like this...
...you don't wanna mess with it.
- Hey.
- Did you hear about Martin?
- Yeah, I heard.
I can't believe he's in a coma.
He's got my vacuum cleaner.
I loaned it to him, he never
returned it. The carpets are filthy.
- What am I gonna do?
- Who told you about Martin?
Newman.
He's good friends with him.
Bigmouth Newman.
I should have guessed.
He's got all my attachments,
you know.
Let me ask you something.
How long do you have to wait...
...for a guy to come out of a coma
before you ask his ex-girlfriend out?
Oh, Gina?
Why wait?
Why not just call Dr. Kevorkian.
I don't get that
whole suicide machine.
There's no tall buildings
where these people live?
They can't wrap their lips around
a revolver like a normal person?
What's going on
between you and Gina?
Well, I went with her
to the hospital last night.
So we're in the room and she's trying
to get me to kiss her in front of him.
That's the great thing
about Mediterranean women.
All right. So, what did you do?
- Nothing.
- What kind of a man are you?
The guy is unconscious, in a coma...
...and you don't have the guts
to kiss his girlfriend?
I didn't know what
the coma etiquette was.
There is no coma etiquette.
See, that's the beauty of the coma.
It doesn't matter what you do.
So you're saying his girl, his car,
his clothes, it's all up for grabs.
You can just loot the coma victim.
I give them 24 hours to get out of it.
They can't get out of it
by 24 hours, it's a land rush.
So if the coma victim wakes up
in a month...
...he's thrilled. He got out of the coma.
- He goes home, there's nothing left?
- Nothing left!
That's why I'm trying to get that
vacuum. Somebody's gonna grab it.
Martin's spirit came to you
as a warning.
Why would he come to George?
Because George has heightened
extrasensory perception.
Faithy, get your finger
out of your nose!
- I knew it. I always felt different.
- You are. Some coffee cake?
- Drake's?
- Yes.
- Did you buy this for me?
- No, why?
Because I love Drake's Coffee Cake.
- Maybe I did.
- Take it away.
She hasn't eaten in two days.
- Who's Pauline?
- Pauline?
Wait a minute. Oh, my God.
My brother once impregnated
a woman named Pauline.
- You think about her?
- When I hear her name.
Cut these with your left hand.
There was a woman. Audrey.
She had a very big nose.
I see an Audrey,
but with a small nose.
Yes, yes. She had a nose job.
I loved her very deeply.
Will she ever speak to me again?
Not in this life.
- Should you be smoking?
- Does it bother you?
- You're pregnant.
- Elaine.
I smoked when I had Faithy.
What? What?
I don't know about this trip, George.
You can see the Cayman Islands
in there?
Is something gonna happen
to me? What?
It's really bad for the foetus,
you know that?
She's a psychic.
She knows how the kid's gonna be.
Should I not go on this trip?
George...
...I am going to tell you something
and I want you to really hear me.
Now, listen, I just don't know
how a person, with everything...
...we now know about prenatal care,
can put a cigarette in her mouth!
- What are you doing?
- It's disgusting.
- I don't need this!
- Look, please!
- I would like you both to leave.
- Oh, fine.
Well, I don't like to be around people
who are just so irresponsible.
- Get the hell out.
- A plane crash?! A heart attack?!
Lupus? Is it lupus?
Do you want me to call the super?
He was an Israeli commando.
If you don't say anything,
I'll assume it's a plane crash.
- Get out.
- Not a plane crash.
Is it a plane crash?
Psychics should be licensed.
And it wouldn't be hard. We could
just give them the regular DMV test...
...only with the silver dollars and
the pizza dough over the eyes.
If you can do the parallel park
like that, you're a psychic.
We can test these people,
no question about it.
Like Kreskin. Instead
of just hiding his check...
...why don't we try
stopping his check.
Let's see how he handles that.
I do not like your toothbrush.
There are no bristles.
You can say what you want
about me...
...but I'll be damned
if I'm gonna stand here...
...while you insult my toothbrush.
It is too small for someone
with such a big mouth.
Let me ask you...
...what will you do if Martin
wakes up? Run away like a mouse?
No, more like the Three Stooges
at the end of every movie.
Who are these Stooges
you speak of?
They're a comedy team.
Tell me about them. Everything.
Well, they're three funny-looking guys
and they'd hit each other a lot.
- You will show me the Stooges?
- I will show you the Stooges.
- When?
- Well...
...I don't really know where
the Stooges are right now...
...but if I locate them,
you'll be the first to know.
Come. You walk me to a cab.
Well, I...
I don't want you to get upset
or anything...
...but with Martin and all, maybe it's
not a good idea to be seen together...
...in the building,
because he had a lot of friends.
You are still afraid.
You are not a man.
Well, then what are all those ties and
sport jackets doing in my closet?
Are you going to walk me
to a cab or not?
Yeah, all right, all right.
- Why don't you just eat fruit.
- Fruit makes me incontinent.
I don't want you eating over here.
Hello, Gina. Hello, Jerry.
Hello, Newman.
Do you think Newman
would tell Martin if he wakes up?
What kind of sicko would do that?
He could kill me.
People smoke, Elaine.
My mother smoked.
It didn't hurt me.
Did you guys see that wall move?
Boy, it's a good thing we came.
Could there be a native problem
in the Caymans?
Maybe there's native unrest.
Hi. I haven't eaten in three days.
I was wondering how much longer
it would be till I get my X-ray.
We'll call you.
George, I want you to promise me
something. If I'm ever in a coma...
...in the first 24 hours, get everything
out of my place and put it in storage.
- How come?
- Looters.
How do we know the dog food's
any good?
Who tastes it?
She is really hungry.
- Hey.
- Kramer.
Well, Newman's upstairs
visiting Martin.
Would you buy
my Cayman Island ticket?
- You're not going?
- No.
- Why not?
- The psychic said...
...something terrible will happen.
I dig.
I want my vacuum cleaner!
Martin, I know you can hear me.
Look, my mother's coming to visit me.
She sees that rug, she's gonna kill me.
He can't hear you, you idiot.
Why don't you just buy another one.
Why would I buy another one when
I spent 100 bucks on this one?
I have a carpet sweeper
you can use.
I don't want a carpet sweeper.
They don't do anything.
It gets my rug clean.
The carpet sweeper
is the biggest scam...
...perpetrated on the American
public since One Hour Martinizing.
You should take a look
at my rug, then.
I wouldn't set foot in your house.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Hello, Jerry.
- How's he doing?
- Well, he looks happy to me.
I hope he stays this happy
when he wakes up.
- Why wouldn't he?
- No reason.
He'll have a lot of catching up
to do, I guess.
I'll bring him up to date.
- How up to date?
- All the way up.
Nothing could change your mind?
Well, it would take a lot, because
a friend is something you earn.
Jerry has a friend who has free tickets
to the Cayman Islands this weekend.
He's not going.
I don't care much for the beach.
I freckle.
- Is that a...?
- Drake's Coffee Cake.
Where did you get that?
From my house.
I got a whole box of them.
Boy. That's the full-size.
That's your big boy.
Can I have a bite?
I don't like to give out bites.
I got another one...
...but I'm saving it for later.
Just one bite?
I don't think so.
You know, they're so fragile.
All right! All right.
I won't say anything.
- You swear?
- I swear.
- On your mother's life?
- On my mother's life.
But here it was...
...mountains of duck.
And not fatty duck either,
but juicy, tender breasts of duck.
- Beautifully sliced...
- Faithy!
Sweetheart, no, don't run!
You could take
as much as you want...
Sweetheart! Sweetheart! Faithy!
Hi. Hi! What are you doing here?
How did I know you were here?
Something drew me here.
This is phenomenal.
The nurse said she'd be back.
Supposed to take me
to the delivery room.
Oh, that's great. That's great.
I have to apologize for my friend
the other day...
Friend? I don't even
know that woman.
I met her on the way over.
I couldn't get rid of her.
I tell you, my psychic instincts
were a little off...
- Where's the nurse?
- I'm sure she'll be right back.
Sweetheart, why don't you
run and get a nurse for Mommy.
I was just curious. The other day
you said something about my trip.
- Don't take that trip.
- Yeah! Why? Why?
- Because... Because...
- All right, Rula. It's time to go.
Yeah, because...? Because...?
Assassins! How dare they keep
a person waiting like this!
Drake's Coffee Cake?
- Give me that!
- Jerry, you better stop her or I'll tell!
Elaine, no! No!
Are there terrorists on the plane?
A hotel fire, is that it?
Typhus? Malaria? Yellow fever?
Lupus? Is it lupus?
They did it right in this bed, Martin.
Right in front of you.
- I want my vacuum cleaner!
- I can explain!
It was disgusting!
What are you doing?
We're going to dinner in 10 minutes.
I never assisted in a birth before.
It's really quite disgusting.
- What did she name the kid?
- You wouldn't believe it.
Rasputin.
- Hey!
- When did you get back?
- A couple hours ago.
- So how was it?
- George...
...I would like to thank you
for the greatest four days of my life.
They were shooting the
Sports Illustrated swimsuit issue...
...right in the hotel pool.
Not only that...
...the hotel opened up an area
on the beach for nude bathing...
...and all of the models
went down there.
I am on the next blanket
from Elle Macpherson.
We played backgammon nude.
- Oh, she's a sweet kid.
- Nude backgammon...
...with swimsuit models!
Oh, you know what? The second day
I was there, I stepped on a jellyfish.
It stung my foot. That's probably what
Rula was trying to warn you about.
- You gotta watch for the jellyfish.
- Yeah.
What's this?
It's an invitation to a housewarming
for Martin and Gina.
- They moved in together?
- Yeah, some place in the Village.
- Yeah.
- It's Elaine.
All right, we're coming down.
- Where you going?
- We're taking Elaine to dinner.
She's gotta start the fast again.
You wanna go?
I'd like to, but a bunch of us
from the islands are getting together.
- Elle Macpherson gonna be there?
- I gotta call her back.
The thing I don't understand
about the suicide person...
...is the people that try
and commit suicide...
...for some reason, they don't die,
and then that's it. They stop trying.
Why?
Why don't they just keep trying?
What has changed? Is their life better?
No. In fact, it's worse,
because now they've found out...
...here's one more thing you stink at.
That's why these people don't
succeed at life to begin with.
Because they give up too easy.
I say pills don't work, try a rope.
Car won't start in the garage?
Get a tune-up. You know what I mean?
There's nothing more rewarding...
...than reaching a goal
you've set for yourself.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
As a kid, my favourite ride...
...was the bumper car. Remember?
Going around in a circle.
There was always one kid
that could not do it.
Do you remember this kid?
As soon as the ride gets started...
...he'd be, like, stuck
in a pack of empty cars.
Just...
"Excuse me.
Excuse me. It won't go!
Come on!
It's almost over!"
He always ends up
with the attendant...
...hanging off that big pole
helping him steer it.
"Stop crying."
Then there's always
that other...
One other really bad car...
The helpless father-and-son team.
This is another car just
not going anywhere.
They're never organized.
Who's on the wheel?
Who's pressing on the gas? Just:
"Son, turn the wheel."
All right, Coney Island?
Okay, you can take the B or the F
and switch for the N...
...at Broadway and Lafayette.
Or you can go over the bridge
to DeKalb...
...and catch the Q
to Atlantic Avenue...
...then switch to the IRT,
2, 3, 4 or 5.
But don't get on the G.
That's very tempting,
but you wind up on Smith...
...and 9th Street.
Then you gotta get on the R.
Couldn't he just take the D
straight to Coney Island?
Well, yeah.
Okay. What time is your
job interview, George?
9:45.
Don't whistle on the elevator.
- Why not?
- That's what Willy Loman told Biff...
...before his interview
in Death of a Salesman.
You're comparing me to Biff Loman?
Very encouraging.
The biggest loser in the history
of American literature.
- I gotta get going.
- What time's the lesbian wedding?
- 9:30.
- Lesbian wedding.
How do they work the bride and groom
on that? Do they flip a coin?
Yeah, they flip a coin.
What, was that not politically correct?
It's a legitimate question.
I'm so tired. I'm gonna fall asleep
on that train.
I feel when lesbians are looking at me,
they're thinking:
"That's why I'm not a heterosexual."
All right, Jerry, come on.
Pick up the check so we can go.
- I'm paying for breakfast?
- Yeah.
- Why do I always pay?
What am I, made of money?
You bunch of deadbeats.
How many tickets you paying today?
Let's see. Speeding, running a
red light, no licence, no registration...
...no plates, no brake lights,
no rear-view mirror.
Look at that one.
- "No doors"?
- Yeah, I'm fighting that one.
You know, this is gonna cost me
over 600 bucks.
I can't carry change in these pants.
It falls out.
- Here you go.
- There you go.
Thank you.
That guy's not blind.
So can I convince anybody
to come down to Coney Island?
Gotta pick up my car
at the pound. George?
I can't believe they found
your stolen car.
Not only did they find it...
...it was simonized,
and the front end was aligned.
- That's amazing.
- So, what do you say?
Ride on the Cyclone.
Hot dog at Nathan's on me.
Who are you, Satan?
I'm close to a job here.
- It's my second interview.
- All right, Biff.
Elaine? Merry-go-round?
I can't. I'm the best man.
Kramer. Bumper cars.
I gotta go to court. I'll get in trouble.
What's the matter with you?
It could be years till I get
back to Coney Island.
I can't go on the rides alone.
42nd Street. Change for the D
and the double R...
...the 2, 3, 4, 5, 7,
the C, K and F train.
Well...
See you.
Hey!
Yeah!
- You looking for a job?
- Me? Why?
Well, you're reading
the classifieds.
Oh, no. No, no.
I was just looking for the stock page.
Here it is.
Looking for the quotes.
Gotta check the quotes.
Love a good quote.
IBM up a quarter.
What do you know?
You didn't look like someone
who needed a job.
Me? No, I don't.
Doing very well. Very well, yeah.
So you're in the market?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I'm in the market.
Which market?
Which market? The... The big one.
The big market with the big board.
Bull market, bear market.
You name the market, I'm there.
So do you work for one of
the big brokerage houses?
They wish.
I hate the big brokerage houses.
Hate them with a passion.
Big brokerage houses
killed my father.
- Really?
- Well, they hurt him bad.
Really hurt his feelings.
It's a long story.
I don't like to talk about it...
...but I swore I would never work
for a big brokerage house.
See, all they care about is money.
I'm about more than money.
I'm about...
...people.
So I've always gone my own way...
...and I've never looked back.
I started riding these trains
in the '40s.
Those days, a man would give up
his seat for a woman.
Now we're liberated.
We have to stand.
It's ironic.
What's ironic?
This. That we've come all this way,
we made all this progress...
...but, you know, we lost
the little things, the niceties.
No, I mean, what does
"ironic" mean?
Where you off to
with such a nice present?
- Birthday party?
- A wedding.
- A wedding?
- Yeah.
I didn't think people
still get married.
It's hard today
with the men and women.
You're telling me.
- So they're a nice couple?
- Oh, very nice.
What does he do,
if you don't mind my asking?
- She.
- She?
She. She works, he doesn't.
He sounds like my son.
There is no "he."
There's no he?
So who's getting married?
Two women.
It's...
...a lesbian wedding.
Lesbian wedding?
Yep. Yep, I'm...
...the best man.
Great.
My luck. I don't talk to a soul
on the subway for 35 years...
...I get the best man
at a lesbian wedding.
No, no. You don't understand.
I'm not a lesbian!
I hate men, but I'm not a lesbian.
I'm really looking forward to this.
I love weddings.
Maybe I'll meet somebody.
Maybe not.
Oh, man. We're stopping?
Well, this is where I get off.
- You do?
- Yeah.
Hey, why don't you...? Oh, nothing.
No, no. What?
Well, I was gonna say,
"Why don't you get off with me."
But you're obviously very busy
on your way...
...to some important meeting
or something.
Yeah. Well...
See, I knew it was a bad idea.
Hey, what's another million,
give or take? I get off...
...when and where I wanna get off.
I'm stuck. Could you just pull it
a little...?
This'll just be a second.
Don't... Don't start the train!
Don't start the train!
Here it is. Here it is,
the four horse in the first race.
- Pappernick.
- How do you know he's gonna win?
My UPS guy. Lance.
The guys who own the horse are
his regular customers.
Every horse he's ever given me
has won.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. They've been sandbagging...
...looking for a good spot.
He's been getting in light...
...because they're using a bug boy.
The workouts have been unpublished.
They're ready to run with him.
Gonna break his maiden.
He's gonna go for a great price,
maybe 30-1.
- I'm telling you, it's a lock.
- But it rained last night.
Exactly. This horse loves the slop.
It's in his bloodlines.
His father was a mudder.
- His mother was a mudder.
- His mother was a mudder?
What did I say? Let's go to the office.
I'm gonna call my bookie.
Hey, don't tell anybody.
Oh, man.
Okay.
You realize, of course, you're naked.
Naked, dressed,
I don't see any difference.
You ought to sit here.
There's a difference.
You got something
against the naked body?
I got something against yours.
How about a couple of deep knee
bends, maybe some squat-thrusts?
Who's got time for squat-thrusts?
All right, how about
skipping breakfast?
I'm guessing you're not a
"half-grapefruit and black coffee" man.
I like a good breakfast.
I understand.
I like a good breakfast...
...long as you don't wind up trapped
in a room in overalls and pigtails...
...being counselled by Dick Gregory.
I'm not ashamed of my body.
Exactly. That's your problem.
You should be.
Don't get up.
Please, allow me.
Oh, this is great.
This is what I need, just what I need.
Okay, tak e it easy.
I'm sure it's nothing.
Probably rats on the track.
They're stopping for rats.
God, it's so crowded.
How could there be
so many people?
This guy really smells.
Doesn't anyone use deodorant
in the city?
What is so hard?
You tak e the cap off, you roll it on.
What's that? I feel something
rubbing against me.
These disgusting animals.
These people should be in a cage.
We are in a cage.
What if I miss the wedding?
I got the ring. What'll they do?
You can't get married
without a ring. Oh, God...
I can't breathe.
I feel faint.
Okay, tak e it easy.
It'll start moving soon.
Think about people in concentration
camps, what they went through.
And the hostages! What would
you do if you were a hostage?
Think about that. This is nothing.
No, it's not nothing, it's something.
It's a nightmare. Help me!
Move it! Come on!
Move this f****** thing!
Why isn't it moving?!
What could go wrong with a train?
It's on tracks.
There's no traffic.
How could a train get stuck?
Step on the gas!
What could it be? You'd think the
conductor would explain it to us.
"I'm sorry, there's a delay.
We'll be moving in five minutes."
I wanna hear a v oice.
What's that on my leg?!
Nice.
Your company sends you
on the road often, huh?
Nice. Oh, hey, nice ice bucket there.
Make yourself comfortable.
Mak e myself comfortable?
What does that mean?
Does she want me to tak e my clothes
off? Is she taking her clothes off?
What if I tak e mine off
and she still has hers on?
I'd look lik e an idiot.
She'd get offended and leave.
So maybe I should leave them on.
But what if she tak es hers off?
She'll feel humiliated.
"Mak e yourself comfortable"?
This woman's unbelievable.
This "comfortable" thing
could ruin me.
I got it. I'll tak e my shoes off
and sit on the bed.
There. That's comfortable.
She can't accuse me
of being uncomfortable.
I gotta tell you,
I'm pretty comfortable.
Oh, yeah, it's all set.
- They've got the bug boy on it.
- The bug boy?
Yeah, the little fellow's
been riding his heart out.
- They're gonna break his maiden.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- It's a little slow out.
- Rained last night.
- This baby loves the slop.
Loves it. Eats it up.
Eats the slop. Born to slop.
His father was a mudder.
- His father was a mudder.
- His mother was a mudder.
His mother was a mudder?
What did I just say?
Hey. All right.
Six hundred, Pappernick to win.
They still have no pitching.
Gooden's a question mark.
You don't recover from those
rotator cuffs so fast.
I'm not worried about
the Mets' pitching.
- They got no hitting.
- No, they got hitting. Bonilla, Murray.
- They got no defence.
- Defence, please.
- They need speed.
- Speed? They've got Coleman.
- They need a bullpen.
- Franco's no good?
- They got no team leaders.
- They got Franco.
What they need is a front office.
- But you gotta like their chances.
- I love them.
If they win it this year, I'll sit naked
with you at the World Series.
It's a deal.
Why couldn't I tak e a cab?
For $6, my whole life
could have changed.
What is that on my leg?
I'll never get out of here.
What if I'm here
for the rest of my life?
Maybe I'll get out in five seconds.
One banana, two banana...
...three banana, four banana...
...five banana.
No. I'm still here.
Still here. When will they
start moving?
Move!
Move! Move!
It's moving.
It's moving!
Yes!
Yes.
Mother******!
Gee, I hope you have the key
for these things.
Oh, don't worry, I do.
My mother used to walk
around our apartment...
...in her bra and panties.
She didn't look anything like you.
She was...
...really disgusting, really bad body.
You know, if you can imagine an
uglier, fatter version of Shirley Booth.
Remember Shirley Booth in Hazel?
Really embarrassing,
because I had the only mother...
...in the neighbourhood
who was worse than Hazel.
- You can imagine the taunts I'd hear.
- Like what?
Like:
"Hey, your mother's
uglier than Hazel."
"Hazel really puts your mother
to shame." You know.
What's going on?
It was a pleasure doing business
with you, but I have to get going.
Get going? But we haven't really,
you know...
Eight dollars?
- Eight dollars?
- What are you doing, robbing me?
I wasted my whole morning
on you for $8?
Wait a second. What are you doing?
- I'm taking your clothes.
- No, no, that's my only suit!
It cost me $350!
I got it at Moe Ginsburg!
- Bye, George.
- You can't just leave me here.
Will I see you again?
It's Hoy's Boy followed by Jamet...
...Little Baggit, Kiss Harmony
and then a long way to Flagrant.
- Come on!
- Into the stretch...
...with an 1/8th of a mile to go,
Stepagain, Passionel battling it out.
Clear from Jamet, Pappernick's
starting to mak e some ground...
...but Stepagain is the leader...
- Come on.
- Come on! Yes!
- Look at Pappernick, sprouting wings.
- Yes! Yes!
- Stepagain, just falling back.
- Yes!
- Pappernick flashing home.
Stepagain, Pappernick, Pappernick
and Stepagain to the line...
- Yes! Yes! Yes!
- The winner is Pappernick.
Yes, yes! I won. Hey!
Yeah.
I haven't had a hot dog
at Nathan's in 20 years.
First, we ride the Cyclone.
Chilly out.
French fries.
Hey, hey!
Give me the money.
Freeze! Police!
No, I never got the car.
We had such a good time...
...by the time I got to
the police garage, it was closed.
Too bad.
You wouldn't believe what this guy
put away at Nathan's.
Look at what we won. You want him?
Get that out of my face.
So you missed the wedding.
You'll catch the bris.
Hare Krishna! Hare Krishna!
How'd you like a Hare Krishna fist
down your throat, you little punk?
George.
Biff.
What, did you whistle
on the elevator?
I have my spare key
in your apartment, right?
Yeah, in the kitchen drawer.
- Give me your key.
- What happened?
Never mind what happened,
just give me the key.
- Come on, I'll go with you.
- Here. Pay.
Wait, wait. Give me that.
All right.
So I take the subway
down to Coney Island...
...to go on the Cyclone.
I'm riding on the subway.
I'm sitting on the D train
for an hour and 15 minutes...
...to go on a scary ride.
Okay, how dumb is that?
You know that first sharp drop
on the Cyclone? Fell asleep.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
Women put on perfume
in an interesting way.
Ever notice that, guys?
They have their little key,
Stratego little areas.
Places they think we're going.
And they always hit this one.
Women are convinced...
...that this is the most action-packed
area that could ever happen...
...in the dating world.
What is that, ladies?
What is happening here?
Is that in case you slap the guy
or something?
He still finds you intriguing?
"Oh, Chanel!"
She's a pianist, a classical pianist!
She plays the piano!
She's a brilliant woman!
I sat in her living room,
she played the Waldstein Sonata.
The Waldstein!
We did a crossword puzzle
together in bed.
It was the most fun I ever
had in my entire life!
Do you hear me? In my life!
You know?
Were you talking?
I couldn't hear anything.
I was telling you about Noel.
Oh, Noel, yeah.
The one that plays the bongos.
So sidesplittingly funny.
All right, I'm sorry. What about her?
You think I'm gonna repeat
the whole thing?
You told me you like her.
Everything's going good.
No, everything's not going good.
I'm very uncomfortable.
I have no power.
Why should she have
the upper hand?
For once, I'd like the upper hand.
I have no hand, no hand at all.
She has the hand. I have no hand.
- Hand me that, would you?
- Yeah.
How do I get the hand?
We all want the hand.
Hand is tough to get.
You gotta get the hand
right from the opening.
She's playing a recital at
the McBierny School.
I got two extra tickets.
You and Elaine could go.
Yeah, that sounds like something.
Then afterwards, maybe we could all
go out together.
You know, she'll see me
with my friends.
She'll observe me
as I really am, as myself.
Maybe I can get some hand that way.
- Oh, hey.
- Hey.
Hey, smell my arm.
- What?
- Smell it. Smell it.
With all due respect,
I don't think so.
- Jerry, smell.
- That smells good. What is that?
- The beach.
- The beach?
Did you go swimming?
It's 29 degrees.
No, I just joined the Polar Bear Club.
- You joined the Polar Bears?
- What the hell's a Polar Bear?
These people go swimming
in the winter. They're terrific.
I just took my first swim today.
- It's invigorating.
- Yeah...
...so is shock therapy.
- What is that, a PEZ dispenser?
- Yeah. You want one?
I just bought it at the flea market.
You want one?
Hey, what goes on there, exactly?
You don't know?
No, I know. I know.
You think they have fleas there,
don't you?
- No.
- Yes, you do, Biff.
You've never been,
and you think they have fleas there.
All right, I think they have
fleas there. So what?
- Here, you want this?
- You don't want it?
- No, I bought five of them.
- Wow, great. Thanks.
I don't know how anyone does this.
This must be so nerve-racking.
How do they warm up their fingers?
They have a piano backstage
they warm up on.
No. We would have heard it.
You think they just crack
their knuckles and come out?
- I told her we'd go out afterwards.
- Sure.
Don't applaud when she stops playing
the first time. It's not over yet.
I really resent that.
That's directed at me, isn't it?
Is this okay? Can I do this?
Oh, God.
Something I said?
It's John Mollica.
Oh. Oh, John. Oh, hi, John.
- Hi.
- What are you doing out here?
I was just at this recital...
...and Jerry put this PEZ dispenser
on my leg...
...and I just started laughing.
- Jerry's in there?
- Yeah.
- I heard you guys broke up.
- We did. We're just hanging out.
Really? Boy...
...you really look great.
Oh, thank you.
Hey, are you still friends
with Richie Appel?
Oh, Richie? He's been doing comedy
in L.A. for a couple of years.
He just got back a month ago.
He's kind of messed up on drugs.
I don't know what to do.
Have you thought
about an intervention?
- What's that?
- You get all his friends in a room...
...and they confront him
to try to get him into rehab.
It's a very popular thing now.
Well, he'd never listen to anyone.
Except, of course, Jerry.
He'd listen to Jerry.
Jerry would have to be involved.
He really respects Jerry.
I'm sorry, George. I'm sorry.
What did you put the PEZ dispenser
on her leg for?
- I don't know. It was an impulse.
- What kind of a sick impulse is that?
How could I know she'd start to laugh?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I am.
- Could we go in already?
- What are we gonna tell her?
- I'll tell her I was the one who laughed.
- No, don't say a word.
If she thinks my friends are jerks,
then I'm a jerk.
Remind me to talk to you
about something.
- What about?
- Hey, we're discussing something.
I know, but I'm distracted now.
What are you, a baby?
All right, tell him.
When I was outside,
I ran into John Mollica.
- Really? John Mollica?
- Yeah.
The guy that used to bartend
at the comedy club.
- How's he doing?
- He's good.
Could we cut to the chase?
"Cut to the chase"?
- Yeah.
- What are you, Joe Hollywood?
A lot of people say it.
I would lose that.
What's that?
"Lose that"? That's not
a Hollywood expression.
Yes, it is.
Anyway...
So John told me that Richie
is in town from Los Angeles...
...and he's really
messed up on drugs.
So I told him
he should do an intervention.
- Really? An intervention?
- We got a situation over here!
- But he wants you to be a part of it.
- Why me?
He says Richie really respects you,
and he would listen to you.
These things are really hard to load.
All right, okay. All right, I'm going in.
- We got to talk about this.
- All right.
Hi. Hi. Hi.
- You were wonderful. Wonderful.
- No, no.
These are my friends,
Elaine and Jerry. Noel.
You play a hell of a piano.
Yeah, I was really moved.
Really moved.
Didn't you hear that person laughing?
I couldn't play. I was humiliated!
I'm sure it wasn't at you.
Well, then what was she laughing at?
- PEZ?
- No, thank you.
Did you see her?
Me? No, I...
Anyone who would laugh
at a recital...
...is probably some sort
of lunatic, anyway.
I mean, only a sick, twisted mind
could be that rude and ignorant.
Well, you know, maybe some
mental defective...
...put something stupid on her leg.
Even if this so-called mental defective
did put something on her leg...
...she's still the one who laughed.
I'll never forget that laugh
for the rest of my life.
I'm sure she would apologize
if she could.
Probably someone
is holding her back...
...maybe against
every fibre of her being.
If she wants to continue to have a fibre
of her being, she'll be very careful.
- Don't hit me.
- Stop it.
All right. So you ready?
We'll go out,
and we'll have a bite to eat.
I don't feel like it tonight.
- We'll be outside.
- Yeah.
It was nice meeting you.
By the way, how do you warm up
your fingers before you play?
I just crack my knuckles.
Come on, we'll have a good time.
- Well, I'm really not in the mood.
- Come on...
I said, I don't feel like it.
All right...
I'll... I'll call you.
I'll call you,
and we'll talk on the phone.
Have a telephone communiqué.
So, fine. Everything's fine.
Everything good?
Good. I feel good. Fine.
That's fine. That's good.
Okay. Okey-doke.
You know, I think Kramer might
have been indirectly responsible...
...for getting Richie
involved in drugs.
What? How?
A few years ago, the comedy club
had a softball team.
Kramer was our first baseman.
You couldn't get anything by him.
He was unbelievable.
Anyway, this one game, we came back
to win from, like, eight runs behind.
So Kramer says to Richie:
"Why don't you dump the bucket
of Gatorade on Marty Benson's head?"
- The club owner.
- Yeah.
So Richie goes ahead and does it.
- So? What happened?
- What happened?
The guy was, like, 67 years old.
It was freezing out.
He caught a cold, developed
pneumonia, a month later...
...he was dead.
- Shut up.
All the comedians were happy...
...because he's one of these
club owners nobody liked.
But Richie was never the same.
- What about Kramer?
- He's the same.
Are you sure you want me, John?
I mean, I haven't spoken
to Richie in two years.
I don't have a good apartment
for an intervention.
The furniture,
it's very nonconfrontational.
All right, all right. Goodbye.
Remember Richie Appel?
Oh, sure. The guy I told to pour the
Gatorade that killed Marty Benson?
Right. John Mollica is organizing
some kind of intervention for him.
We're having it here.
Can I get in on that?
What do you think,
it's like a poker game?
- Is Elaine going?
- Yeah.
Well, I knew him as well as she did.
Yeah, but John invited her.
So wait, you don't want me
to intervene?
No, intervene, go ahead.
Intervene all you want.
I'm just afraid you might be interfering
while we're intervening.
- Yeah?
- It's George.
Come on up.
Stop smelling your arm!
You know, I got a great idea
for a cologne.
It's called "The Beach."
You spray it on, and it's just like
you came home from the beach.
A cologne that smells
like the beach.
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but that's not a bad idea.
Tell me about it.
Why don't you call Steve D'Giff?
He works in the marketing department
at Calvin Klein.
In fact, he's a good friend
of John Mollica and Richie, also.
Okay.
Well, it's over. It's definitely over.
- She broke up with you?
- No, but she's going to.
I can sense it. We had this
terrible phone conversation.
I was so nervous before I called,
I made a list of things to talk about.
What was on the list?
Let's see.
"I'm very good
at going in reverse in my car.
Why isn't Postum
a more popular drink?"
Yeah, Postum is underrated.
Anyway, there was all this tension.
I asked her if she wanted
to go out to dinner...
...and she said,
"No, maybe we could have lunch."
- You know what that means.
- What's wrong with lunch?
Lunch is fine at the beginning,
then you move on to dinner.
You don't go back to lunch.
It's like being demoted.
I'll never do a crossword puzzle
with her again, I know it.
I like the jumble.
You ever do the jumble?
I have no power, you understand?
I need hand! I have no hand!
- Why don't you break up with her.
- What?
Break up with her.
You reverse everything that way.
A preemptive breakup.
- This is an incredible idea.
- Yeah.
I got nothing to lose.
We either break up,
which she would do anyway...
...but I go out with some dignity...
...or I completely turn the tables!
This is absolutely brilliant!
So I'm afraid I...
...am gonna have to
break up with you.
- You're breaking up with me?
- Yes.
I...
...am breaking up with you.
- Wow.
- Shocked?
- I really am.
- Never expected this, did you?
- I thought everything was fine.
- Well, live and learn.
Well, I don't understand.
You didn't enjoy being with me?
Didn't we have fun
doing the crossword puzzle?
Kind of.
- I'm very confused.
- Well, I didn't mean to hurt you, kid.
- I thought...
- Now, stop it, please.
What do you want?
I know I can make you happy.
When you're playing the piano...
...do you think about me?
- I don't know.
- This is what I'm talking about.
Okay, I'll think about you.
- All the time?
- You know...
- Okay, all the time.
- I can't hear you.
- All the time!
See? It's not so hard.
Go ahead. Smell. Smell it.
- Yeah? So?
- Now, you recognize it?
I don't know.
The beach.
- What are you talking about?
- Oh, I'm talking about the beach.
What about it?
You know the way you smell...
...when you first come home
from the beach?
Well, I want to make
a cologne that captures...
...the essence of that smell.
Oh, yeah.
That is the dumbest idea
I've ever heard.
Whoa, wait a minute. You...
Did you hear what I just said?
You think people
are gonna pay $80 a bottle...
...to smell like dead fish
and seaweed?
That's why people take showers
when they come home from the beach.
It's an objectionable, offensive odour.
So you don't think
that it's a good idea?
The membranes get dry,
and it just starts bleeding.
Since I was a kid, so I have to
stick a tissue up there.
You have to work like that?
Yeah. Nobody minds.
Nobody's ever said anything to me.
- There any ice cubes?
- Whatever's in the freezer.
I looked. I don't see any ice cubes.
Well, then I guess
there's no ice cubes.
I can't drink this. It's warm.
John, shouldn't we rehearse this...
...before Richie comes?
What's the plan?
Do I have to talk?
I don't want to.
If he's not gonna talk,
then I don't want to.
- No, we all have to talk!
- What's the order?
Alphabetical order.
You're first, Roberta.
- Why am I first?
- Albano's your last name.
- Not anymore. I'm divorced.
- I'll go first.
- Oh, hey!
- Hey.
- Is this the interference?
- Intervention.
- What are you doing here?
- Oh, is it all right if I stay?
He can't stay.
This is for close friends only.
Hey, I'm a friend.
Who told him to pour the Gatorade
over Marty Benson's head?
- Oh, let him stay.
- Yeah.
Hey, I got somebody to make up
that cologne for me, bigmouth.
Somebody's going to make that crap?
- Kramer!
- Hey, you guys! All right!
Come on in. These are some
of my Polar Bear buddies.
- They can't stay.
- You're having a party here?
No, we're having an intervention.
An intervention? Who's intervening?
He's a friend of ours on drugs,
and we're gonna confront him.
Sure. We used to do that...
...when one of our Polar Bears stopped
coming. We'd go to his house:
"What, you don't want to be
a Polar Bear anymore?
- It's too cold for you?"
- It's him!
- What do we do?
- Hide!
It's not a surprise party!
- Yeah?
- It's George.
Come on up.
It's not him.
You don't wanna go out with me
because I'm a bartender, right?
Look, you know, I don't really think
that this is appropriate right now.
Is it because I have a tissue
in my nose?
- You're getting warm.
- Hey, we just...
We just came from Chadway's.
What's going on?
The intervention.
We're waiting for Richie.
Right, the intervention.
Should we leave?
- Well...
- Elaine, hi.
Hi, Noel.
Well, you're looking well.
Jerry, let me tell you something.
A man without hand is not a man.
I've got so much hand,
I'm coming out of my gloves.
I gotta thank Kramer.
Even if I were dragged
through manure...
...I still wouldn't put that stuff on.
This man is a genius! A genius!
- You think so?
- I don't think so, I know so.
Come here. I gotta talk to you.
The male kangaroo
doesn't have a pouch.
Only the female has it...
...so the male has pouch envy!
"Why should she have
this huge pouch and I have nothing?
I have things to carry too.
At least give me a pocket."
That laugh. That's the laugh.
- That's it! You're the one!
- No, no.
No, it was an accident.
It wasn't my fault! It was Jerry!
Jerry put a PEZ dispenser
on my leg!
You put a PEZ dispenser
on her leg during my recital?
- I didn't know she would laugh.
- And, you...
You lied to me, George.
You lied to me!
No, l... I didn't. What did I do?
Where are you going?
I am breaking up with you.
You can't break up with me.
I've got hand!
And you're gonna need it.
Noel!
- Hey, Richie!
- Hey, Richie.
So, what's going on?
So we start the intervention,
and it's pretty ugly from the get-go.
He's not listening, he's hostile,
he's talking back.
I can't do these puzzles.
So he starts to get up.
Suddenly, he spots the PEZ dispenser
on the coffee table.
The PEZ dispenser.
He picks it up, he's staring at it.
It's like he's hypnotized by it.
Then he's telling us this story
about how when he was a kid...
...he was in the car
with his father...
...and his father was trying
to load one of them.
- Well, they're hard to load.
- Tell me something I don't know.
So as the father's trying to load it,
he loses control of the car...
...crashes into a high school cafeteria.
- Get out.
- Nobody's hurt...
...but PEZ was all over the car.
And the dispenser was destroyed...
...virtually beyond recognition.
- Poor kid.
- So as he's telling the story...
...he starts crying.
- What did you do?
- What do you think?
- I gave him my PEZ dispenser.
- Wow.
Two hours later,
he checks into Smither's clinic.
Talked to the doctor yesterday.
He's doing great on the rehab...
...he's hooked on PEZ.
He's eating them
like there's no tomorrow.
What's a three-letter word for candy?
I can't do those things.
Jawbreakers, to me, was like
the ultimate challenge candy.
It was like candy manufacturers were
sitting in their laboratories, going:
"I wonder if they'll eat this.
This seems pretty tough to eat.
Let's market it
as some sort of experiment."
But the concept of Jawbreakers...
What was the concept?
Multicoloured cement balls
for a quarter?
Was that the idea behind it?
"Let's see if we can hurt them.
Let's see if they'll pay to be hurt."
This is the idea behind Jawbreakers.
I did it, I ate them, I loved them.
"Oh, this is very painful.
I'm really hurting.
And this is hurting me a lot.
I love them."
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
At the health club,
people are working out...
...and they're training,
getting in shape...
...but strangely, nobody's really
getting in shape for anything.
The only reason that you're
getting in shape...
...is that so you can get through
the workout.
So we're working out...
...so that we'll be in shape
for when we have to do our exercise.
This is the whole thing.
The other thing I don't get
is why we're so careful...
...about locking up our dirty towels
and smelly jockstraps.
What exactly is the black market
on these disgusting gym clothes?
I'll give my car to any guy
in front of a restaurant...
...because he's got a short
red jacket.
"He must be the valet guy."
But my stinking,
putrefied gym clothes...
...I got one of these locks...
...you could put a bullet through it
and it won't open.
That stuff is safe.
Wide open!
I was wide-open underneath.
I had three inches on that guy.
See, you two were hogging the ball.
Me? It wasn't me.
I never even saw the ball.
All you do is dribble.
I have to dribble. If I give it to you,
you just shoot. You're a chucker.
- Oh, I'm a chucker.
- That's right.
Every time you get the ball,
you shoot.
I can't believe you
called me a chucker.
No way I'm a chucker! I do not chuck.
Never chuck!
Never have chucked!
Never will chuck! No chuck!
You chuck.
- Kramer, am I a chucker?
- Oh, you're a chucker.
My God, I'm a chucker.
- All these years, you never told me?
- It's not an easy thing to bring up.
Hey, you know, this is the first time
we ever saw each other naked?
Believe me, I didn't see anything.
Oh, you didn't sneak a peek?
- No. Did you?
- Yeah, I snuck a peek.
- Why?
- Why not?
What about you, George?
Yeah, I...
...snuck a peek.
But it was so fast, I didn't see
anything. It was just a blur.
I made a conscious effort not to look.
There's certain information
I just don't wanna have.
Okay...
I gotta go meet Newman.
- I'll see you later. Have a good one.
- All right.
Yeah.
Look at this guy.
Does he have to stretch in here?
- You know who that is?
- Who?
That's Keith Hernandez.
Keith Hernandez,
the baseball player?
Yeah, that's him.
- Are you sure?
- Positive.
Wow! Keith Hernandez!
- He's such a great player.
- Yeah.
He's a real smart guy too.
He's a Civil War buff.
Wow, I'd love to be a Civil War buff.
What do you have to do
to become a buff?
So Biff wants to be a buff?
Well, sleeping less than 18 hours
a day would be a start.
I only got two weeks left
of unemployment.
I gotta prove I've been looking
for a job to get an extension.
Hey, should we say something
to him?
Oh, I'm sure he loves to hear
from fans in the locker room.
Well, he could say hello to me.
I wouldn't mind.
He's Keith Hernandez.
You're Jerry Seinfeld.
- So?
- What, you're comparing yourself...
...to Keith Hernandez?
The guy's a baseball player,
Jerry, baseball!
I know what he is. I recognized him.
You didn't even notice him.
What, you're making some wisecracks
in a nightclub?
The guy was in game six, two runs
down, two outs, facing elimination!
Excuse me.
I don't want to disturb you.
I'm Keith Hernandez.
And I just want to tell you what
a big fan I am. I love your comedy.
- Really?
- I've always wanted to do what you do.
Do what I do?! You're one
of my favorite ballplayers of all time!
Mine too.
- I love that bit about Jimmy Olsen.
- Really?
Thank you.
You know, Keith,
what I've always wondered is...
...with all these ball clubs
flying around all season...
...wouldn't you think
there'd be a plane crash?
Are you performing in New York now?
At this club on the East Side.
You should come in.
But think about it:
26 teams, 162 games a season.
You'd think eventually, an entire team
would just get wiped out.
I live on the East Side.
I'll give you my number...
...and just tell me whenever
you want to go.
- Or maybe just get together for coffee.
- Oh, that'd be great.
Well, it's only a matter of time.
Who's this chucker?
It's been three days,
and he hasn't called.
Well, maybe you should call him.
I can't. I can't.
- Why not?
- I just feel like he should call me.
What's the difference?
You don't understand, Elaine.
I don't want to be overanxious.
If he wants to see me,
he has my number. He should call.
God, look at this ashtray.
I hate cigarettes.
I can't stand these guys.
You give your number to them,
and then they don't call.
Why do they do that?
I'm sorry, honey.
I mean, I really thought he liked me.
We were getting along.
He came over to me.
I didn't go over to him.
- I know.
- Why did he come over to me?
I mean, here I meet this great guy,
this ballplayer...
...best guy I ever met.
- Yeah. I know.
Well, that's it. I'm never giving
my number out to another guy again.
I've given my number out to guys,
and it takes them a month to call.
Good. Good.
Well, if he's calling in a month...
...he's got a prayer.
You know, maybe he's been busy.
Maybe he's been out of town.
Oh, what, they don't have phones
out of town?
I love how people say
they're too busy. "Too busy."
Pick up a phone!
Takes two minutes.
How can you be too busy?
- Why don't you just go and call him?
- I can't call here. It's a coffee shop.
- I mean, what am I gonna say to him?
- Just ask if he wants to get together.
For what, dinner?
Dinner's good.
Don't you think that's coming on a little
too strong? Isn't that, like, a turnoff?
Jerry, he's a guy.
I know, but this is all very confusing.
When you're in your 30s,
it's very hard to make a new friend.
Whatever the group is you've got now,
that's who you're going with.
You're not interviewing,
not looking at any new people.
You're not interested in seeing
any applications.
They don't know the places.
They don't know the foods.
They don't know the activities.
If I meet a guy at a club or a gym:
"Hey, look, I'm sure you're very nice.
You seem to have a lot of potential.
We're just not hiring right now."
When you're a kid...
...you can be friends with anybody.
Remember when you're a little kid...
...what are the qualifications? " If
someone's in front of my house...
...that's my friend.
They're my friend. That's it.
Are you a grownup?
No? Great. Come on in!
Let's jump up and down on my bed!"
And if you have anything in common:
"You like cherry soda? I like
cherry soda! We'll be best friends!"
You only have two more weeks
before your benefits run out.
Yes, and I was hoping, perhaps,
to get...
...a 13-week extension,
if that's possible.
So where have you been looking
for work?
You know what I've discovered,
Mrs. Sokol?
It's not so much the looking...
...as the listening.
I listen for work.
As I'm looking...
...and listening... I'm also looking.
You cannot discount looking.
It's a combination.
It's looking. And listening.
Listening. And looking.
But you must look.
Can you be specific
about any of these companies?
Specific. Let's see...
I've walked in and out
of so many buildings.
They all blend in together.
Just give me one name.
One name. Absolutely.
Let's see, there's...
Vandalay Industries.
I just saw them. I got very close there.
Very close.
What type of company is that?
Latex. Latex manufacturing,
Mrs. Sokol.
- And you interviewed there?
- Yes, for a sales position.
Latex salesman.
The selling of latex
and latex-related products.
They just wouldn't give me a chance.
Damn it!
Now I'm going to need an address
and a phone number for this...
...Vandalay company.
You like gum?
Because I have a friend in the gum
business. I got a gum guy!
I make one phone call, have boxes
of gum delivered right to your door.
The address?
The address is...
Jose Jimenez.
Do you recognize that?
- No.
- Jose Jimenez.
Very funny.
Really, he's very funny.
The address.
Vandalay is...
...129 West 81 st Street.
It's a very small industry, Vandalay.
It's why I wanted
to work for them.
A phone number.
That's... KL5...
...8383. Are you planning on
calling them soon?
Because they have
very strange hours.
As soon as I'm done with you.
Sure. Well...
You know, I'll check in with you
next week.
I gotta run now because
I got a full plate this afternoon.
- Okay.
- All right. Really good to...
He'll call you back!
It's a par five.
So, you know, I step up to the tee...
...and I hit a beautiful drive
right down the middle of the fairway.
- I mean, you know my hook, right?
- Elaine?
How about this shirt?
Is this okay?
Jerry, he's a guy.
Well, it's a dogleg left,
so I play the hook.
Wait, hold on.
There's another call.
- Jerry! Jerry!
- George?
- Kramer, put Jerry on!
- I'm in the middle of something.
- Call back.
- Kramer, no...!
So the ball takes off,
and I'm waiting for it to turn.
Would you...!
All right. Well, I'll talk to Jerry.
Yeah.
Hey, that was Michael and Carol.
She's wondering when
we'll go see the baby.
- See the baby. Again with the baby.
- Who are they?
A guy who used to live in the building
keeps calling us to see the baby.
"You gotta see the baby.
When are you gonna see the baby?"
Can't they just send us a tape?
Maybe if you wait a few months,
it won't be a baby anymore.
- Then you won't have to see it.
- Because he'll be all grown-up.
Yeah...
Hey, Kramer, what do you think
of this shirt?
It's too busy.
You're trying too hard
to make an impression on him.
- You're not being yourself.
- What guy?
I know he's just a guy,
but I really like him.
Who are you talking about?
Keith... Hernandez.
Keith Hernandez?
Keith Hernandez!
Do me a favor, would you?
Would you change lanes?
You gotta get out of this lane.
This lane stinks.
They're all double-parked.
Get out, I'm begging you.
Please. Please!
You know what?
Bad mistake. My mistake.
Go back. Your lane was better.
Forget this lane.
This lane stinks. Go back to your lane.
Go ahead. Bad mistake.
Go! Go! Go! Make this light!
Make this light! Oh, man!
That's it! Get out!
- What do you mean, get out?
- Get out of the cab!
What? I'm not getting out of this cab.
No! No! You cannot throw me out!
No! Get...
Hello, Newman.
I hate Keith Hernandez.
- Hate him!
- I despise him.
- Why?
- Why? I'll tell you why.
- Let me tell her.
- No, you can't...
- You always tell.
- All right, tell it.
- Just tell it.
- All right.
June 14th, 1987, Mets-Phillies.
We're enjoying a beautiful afternoon
in the right-field stands...
...when a crucial Hernandez error
opens the door...
...to a five-run Phillies ninth.
Cost the Mets the game!
Our day was ruined.
There was a lot of people waiting
by the players' parking lot.
Now we're coming down the ramp.
Newman was in front of me.
Hernandez was coming toward us.
As he passes us, Newman turns
and says, "Nice game, pretty boy."
Hernandez continued past us
up the ramp.
Then, a second later,
something happened...
...that changed us in a very deep
and profound way...
...from that day forward.
- What was it?
- He spit on us!
And I screamed out, "I'm hit!"
Then I turned, and the spit ricocheted
off him, and it hit me.
What a story.
Unfortunately, the immutable laws
of physics contradict...
...the whole premise of your account.
Allow me to reconstruct this,
if I may, for Ms. Benes...
...as I've heard this story
a number of times.
Newman, Kramer,
if you'll indulge me.
According to your story...
...Hernandez passes you
and starts walking up the ramp.
Then you say you were struck...
...on the right temple.
The spit then proceeds to ricochet...
...off the temple, striking Newman
between the third and the fourth rib.
The spit then came off the rib...
...made a right turn,
hitting Newman in the right wrist...
...causing him to drop
his baseball cap.
The spit then splashed off the wrist,
pauses...
...in midair, mind you...
...makes a left turn and lands
on Newman's left thigh.
That is one magic loogie.
Well, that's the way it happened.
What happened to your head
when you got hit?
Well, my head...
...went back, to the left.
- Say that again.
- Back and to the left.
Back and to the left.
So, what are you saying?
I'm saying...
...that the spit could not have
come from behind.
That there had to have been
a second spitter.
Behind the bushes,
on the gravelly road.
If the spitter was behind you,
as you claim...
...that would've caused your head
to pitch forward.
So the spit could've only come
from the front and to the right.
But that's not what they
would have you believe.
I'm leaving.
Jerry's a nut.
Wait, wait, wait.
The sad thing is,
we may never know the real truth.
Did anybody call
asking for Vandalay Industries?
- No, what happened to you?
- All right, listen closely:
I was at the unemployment office.
I told them I was very close to getting
a job with Vandalay Industries...
...and I gave them your phone number.
So when the phone rings...
...you have to answer,
"Vandalay Industries."
- I'm Vandalay Industries?
- Right.
- What is that?
- You're in latex.
- Latex?
- Right.
- What do I do with latex?
- I don't know! You manufacture it!
- Right here in this little apartment?
- And what do I say about you?
You're considering hiring me
for your latex salesman.
- I'll hire you as my latex salesman?
- Right.
I don't think so.
Why would I do that?
Because I asked you to.
If you think I'm looking for someone
to just sit...
...pushing papers around,
you can forget it.
I've got enough headaches
just trying to manufacture the stuff.
- Yeah?
- It's Keith.
All right, we're coming down.
Keith Hernandez?
- Yeah. Come on, Elaine, let's go.
- Where are you going?
They're giving me a ride downtown.
You know, there had to have been
a second spitter. Who was it?
Who had the motive?
That's what I've been trying
to figure out the past five years.
What the hell are you two
talking about?
- That was really fun. Thanks.
- Yeah, it really was.
Should I shak e his hand?
Well...
You want to catch a movie
this weekend?
Have you seen JFK?
No, I haven't.
This week end. Wow!
Sure. That would be great.
Damn. I was too overanxious.
He must have noticed that.
I mean, if you want to.
- Well, how about this Friday?
- Yeah, Friday's okay.
Go ahead, shak e his hand.
I'm Jerry Seinfeld.
I've been on The Tonight Show.
Well, good night.
Good night.
Oh, Jer, by the way...
...the woman we gave
a ride to earlier...
- Elaine.
- Yeah.
- What's her story?
- I don't know. We used to go out.
Would you mind if I gave her a call?
- For a date?
- Yeah.
Oh, no...
Go ahead.
You got a pen?
You sure you don't mind?
So then we went to dinner.
- Who paid?
- We split it.
Split it. Pretty good.
- Did you talk about game six?
- No. I gotta wait until it's the right time.
- Yeah?
- It's Elaine.
Come on up.
So then what?
Nothing. Then he took me home.
Shake his hand?
Yeah.
What kind of a shake does he have?
Good shake. Perfect shake.
Single pump, not too hard.
Didn't have to prove anything,
but firm enough to know he was there.
So...
...you're gonna see him again?
He asked me if I was doing anything
Friday night.
The weekend!
So then, as I was getting out
of the car...
- Hi!
- Oh, hi, Elaine.
Hi, Elaine.
So how was your date?
What date? It's a guy.
So you know... He called me.
- Already?
- Keith called you?
This guy really gets around.
- Do you mind?
- No, I don't mind. Why should I mind?
What did he say?
He asked me out for Saturday night.
- You going?
- No.
- I told him I was busy.
- Oh, really?
So we're going out Friday.
- Friday?
- Yeah.
He's going out with you on Friday?
- Yeah?
- He's supposed to see me on Friday.
- I didn't know.
- We made plans!
- Well... I'll cancel it.
- No, don't cancel it.
Well, this is a little
awkward, isn't it?
Well, frankly, it is.
I've never seen you jealous before.
Well, you're not even a fan.
I was at game six.
You didn't even watch it.
Wait a second. Wait a minute.
Are you jealous of him
or are you jealous of me?
Any Hennigan's around here?
Vandalay Industries.
Kell Varnsen speaking.
May we help you?
Oh, hi, Keith.
No, I was just joking around.
No, no, I don't mind at all.
- No, no, no. I can cancel.
- Sure. We'll do something next week.
No, it's no problem at all.
Okay. Take it easy.
That was Keith.
We're gonna do something next week.
Hey, what are you doing
Friday night?
Friday night? Nothing. Now.
Want to come to see the baby?
Oh, fasten your seat belts.
We're going to see the baby.
If you don't see the baby now,
you're never gonna see her.
- All right, I'll go.
- All right. All right.
I'll get it.
Hello.
What-delay Industries?
- No!
- Vandalay!
Say Vandalay!
No, you're way, way, way off!
Yeah, that's the right number,
but this is an apartment.
- No, say...
- Vandalay! Say...
Vandalay Industries!
Yeah, no problem, no problem.
How did you know who they wanted?!
And you want to be
my latex salesman.
Just sign here, please.
I know who it was too.
It was the guy that interviewed me.
He was very threatened by me.
Why else wouldn't he hire me?
- I could sell latex like that.
- Just sign that.
- Who is this?
- It's my daughter.
This is your daughter?
My God!
I hope you don't mind my saying,
she is breathtaking.
You think so?
Would you take this picture away
from me? Just take it away.
Get it out of here.
Take it away, and put it away.
Let me just sign this and go.
You know...
...she doesn't even have a boyfriend.
Okay. Okay.
Who do you think you're talking to?
You trying to make a joke,
Mrs. Sokol? It's not funny.
I can tell you that.
I'm serious. She doesn't.
You know, it's one thing to not
give me the extension.
But to tease and
to torture me like this...
...there's no call for that.
Would you like her phone number?
Mrs. Sokol,
I don't know what to say.
- Where should I sign this thing?
- No, no, no, no. Don't worry about it.
Unemployment, it's a tough thing.
Even if you get a job after
you've been unemployed...
...they take unemployment out
of your check every week...
...and show it to you in that little box.
How good can it be for your
confidence that every paycheck...
...has the word "unemployment"
on it?
Can't get it out of your mind!
You just got the job!
They're already getting ready
for you to be laid off.
I have a friend who's unemployed.
He's collecting unemployment
insurance.
This guy has never worked this hard
in his life to keep this thing going.
He's down there every week waiting
on the lines and getting interviewed...
...and making up all these lies
about looking for jobs.
If they had any idea the effort
and energy that he is expending...
...to avoid work, I'm sure they'd give
him a raise. I'm sure of it.
The guy is doing a tremendous job...
...not working.
So tell me more
about this game six.
Well, there was two outs,
bottom of the tenth.
We're one out away
from losing the series.
Hello. How are you?
So, what do you think?
Do you love her?
Yes, I do love her.
You have a very nice place here.
So who do you think she looks like?
Lyndon Johnson.
What? Lyndon Johnson?
He's joking.
No, I'm not joking.
She looks like Lyndon Johnson.
Jerry, I can't believe it took you
so long to see the baby.
I kept saying to Michael, "When is
Jerry going to see the baby?"
I was saying the same thing.
Take a picture.
Michael, get the camera.
- You don't have to take a picture.
- I don't know where it is.
It's in the bottom drawer
of our dresser.
Hurry up!
He's such an idiot.
Jerry, you want to pick her up?
- I better not.
- I'll pick her up.
No!
Thank you for a wonderful time,
George.
Glad you enjoyed it.
I haven't had a Big Mac
in a long time.
Billions and billions.
Would you like to come up?
Would I like to come up?
I would love to come up.
I'm... l'm fighting not to.
Fighting.
Unfortunately, I...
...have to get an early start tomorrow.
Gotta get up and hit that pavement.
But it's Saturday.
All the offices are closed.
I got me an appointment
with a hardware store.
I'm not saying I want to do it
for the rest of my life...
...but hardware fascinates me.
Wouldn't you love to make a key?
Will you call me as soon
as you get home?
- Tonight?
- Yes.
Will I call you when I get home?
What do you think?
You kill me. You really kill me.
Well, good night.
It was an accident. Right, Jerry?
It was an accident.
Oh, she's gonna be all right.
Here, baby. Here.
Here, baby.
Baby, baby, baby.
Who's the baby?
I have a friend who's got a baby.
"Gotta see the baby.
You've got to come over
and see the baby."
Nobody ever wants you to come over
and see their grandfather, do they?
"You've got to see my grandfather.
You've got to see him.
He's so cute.
168 pounds, 4 ounces.
I love them when they're this age.
He's 1000 months.
You know, the mid-80s is such
a good time for the grand-people.
The mid-80s, you gotta see them.
He went to the bathroom
by himself today."
You know what's tough about seeing
people when they have a baby...
...is that you have to match
their level of enthusiasm.
You know what I mean?
They're always so excited.
"What do you think of him?"
I'd like to meet a couple that goes:
"You know, we're not that happy
with him, frankly.
I think we really made a big mistake.
We should have got an aquarium.
You want him? We don't even
want him. You want him?"
Thanks for a nice evening.
This was really fun.
Yeah, it was.
Gosh, should I kiss her good night?
Is he going to try and kiss me?
- I love Cajun cooking.
- Really?
You know, my mom's
one-quarter Cajun.
Oh, my father's half-drunk.
Maybe they should get together.
Go ahead. Kiss her.
I'm a baseball player, damn it.
What's he waiting for?
I thought he was a cool guy.
Come on. I won the MVP in '79.
I can do whatever I want to.
Well, this is getting awkward.
Well, good night.
Good night.
Who does this guy think he is?
I'm Keith Hernandez.
Who else?
Mookie. Mookie was there.
You know him?
Well, I don't know him.
I know who he is.
He's such a great guy.
You should meet him.
- He's the one who got that hit...
- I know. He got the hit in game six!
So then what happened?
Nothing. Then he took me home.
So did you two...
...have...?
What?
You know.
Milk?
- No.
- Cookies?
Did he kiss you good night?
I don't know.
What do you mean, you don't know?
All right. He kissed me, okay?
Well, what kind of a kiss?
Was it a peck? Was it a kiss?
Was it a long make-out thing?
Between a peck and a make-out.
So you like him.
I don't understand.
Before you were jealous of me.
Now you're jealous of him?
I'm jealous of everybody.
Hello.
Oh, hi. What's happening?
What?
Sure.
Yeah, okay.
Then... I'll see you then.
Yeah, yeah. Okay.
Bye.
- Who was that?
- That was Keith.
- What's going on?
- He wants me to help him move.
Help him move?
Move what?
You know, furniture.
So, what did you say?
I said, yes, but I don't feel right
about it.
I mean, I hardly know the guy.
That's a big step
in a male relationship.
The biggest.
That's like going all the way.
And you feel you're not
really ready for...
Well, we went out one time.
Don't you think that's coming on
a little too strong?
Hey.
What's going on?
Keith Hernandez just asked me
to help him move.
What?
Well, you hardly know the guy.
What a nerve!
You see? Wasn't I right
about this guy? Didn't I tell you?
Oh, you're not gonna do it, are you?
- I said, yes.
- You said yes?!
Don't you have any pride
or self-respect?
I mean, how can you prostitute
yourself like this?
Are you gonna start driving him
to the airport?
I'm not driving him to the airport.
Oh, boy. I don't know.
- Kramer, do me a favor, would you?
- What?
Don't mention it to anybody.
I wish you never mentioned it to me.
I had a great time tonight, Carrie.
And I will call you
as soon as I get home.
Don't bother.
Bother? What kind of bother?
I would prefer it if you didn't.
- Why? Is anything wrong?
- It's over, buddy. Done.
Finished. So long. Goodbye.
Adios. Sayonara.
- Why?
- I've been thinking about it.
You got no job.
You got no prospects.
You're like Biff Loman.
I went to the hardware store
interview.
You think I'm going to spend my life
with somebody...
...because he can get me a deal
on a box of nails?
I thought we were a team.
If I ever need a drill bit, I'll call you.
Carrie, could you do me a favor?
Could you not mention this
to your mother?
You know, I hate to brag...
...but I did win 11 straight
Gold Gloves.
I wouldn't have brought it up,
but since you mentioned it.
I didn't mention it.
Well, I won them anyway.
Well, so what? I mean...
...you played first base.
I mean, they always put
the worst player at first base.
That's where they put me,
and I stunk.
Elaine, you don't know the first thing
about first base.
Well, I know something
about getting to first base...
...and I know you'll never be there.
The way I figure it,
I've already been there.
And I plan on rounding second
tonight at around 11:00.
Well, I'd watch the third-base coach
if I were you...
...because I don't think
he's waving you in.
You know, I hate to say this...
...but I really think that
we're hitting it off.
- Get it? Get it?
- Clever.
- What are you doing?
- What's that?
- You smoke?
- Yeah.
I didn't know you smoked.
Is that a problem?
She likes him.
I mean, she really likes him.
- How do you know?
- Who wouldn't like him?
I like him, and I'm a guy.
I suppose he's an attractive man.
Forget that. He's a ballplayer.
MVP, 1979.
I'm making wisecracks in some
nightclub. This guy was in game six.
They're a perfect match.
They go together.
Like one of these brother and sister
couples that look alike.
I hate those couples. I could never be
one of those couples.
There are no bald women around,
you know.
I know this sounds a little arrogant,
but I never thought she'd find...
...someone she liked better
than me. But, you know...
...I guess I had my chance.
And that's that.
You know what I'd like to do?
I'd really like to have sex
with a tall woman.
I mean really tall, like a giant.
Like 6'5".
Really?
What was the tallest woman
you ever slept with?
I don't know, 6'3".
Wow! God!
See, this is all I think about:
sleeping with a giant.
It's my life's ambition.
So I guess it's fair to say you've set
different goals for yourself than...
...say, Thomas Edison, Magellan,
these type of people.
Magellan? You like Magellan?
Oh, yeah. My favorite explorer.
Around the world. Come on.
- Who do you like?
- I like de Soto.
- De Soto? What did he do?
- Discovered the Mississippi.
Oh, like they wouldn't have found
that anyway.
All right. I gotta go down
to the unemployment office.
- You want to take a walk?
- No, I got some stuff to do.
I gotta meet Keith at my apartment
at 3. I'm helping him move.
What?
The guy asked you to help him move?
Wow!
- I know. Isn't that something?
- Why doesn't he just pay a mover?
He's got some valuable antiques.
He's worried they'll break something.
Soon he'll have you driving him
to the airport.
I'm not driving him to the airport!
I gave. I gave everything I could,
Mrs. Sokol.
- Nothing was good enough for her.
- Sign here, please.
I don't know who she's looking for.
I don't know.
I'll tell you, she's very particular,
your daughter. Very particular.
Is she looking for some
big hotshot businessman?
Well, I've got my pride too.
I'm not gonna beg her.
All right. Just sign it.
People are waiting.
You like baseball?
That was autographed
by the '86 Mets.
I saw every inning that year.
It's funny, because I happen to be
very good friends with...
...Keith Hernandez.
You know Keith Hernandez.
Know him?
Would you... like to meet him?
Oh, come on. Come on.
I can produce Keith Hernandez,
right here...
...within the hour.
All right.
You got one hour.
All right, Mrs. S.
I and my good pal
Keith Hernandez...
...will be right back.
129 West 81 st Street, and hurry.
Or not.
You better bring your gloves.
It's freezing out there.
It shouldn't take too long.
I'd say maybe, oh, four hours.
Really, Jerry, there's not that much.
First, we got the bedroom.
We got two dressers and the bed.
- Is there a box spring?
- What's that?
- A box spring?
- Yeah, there's a box spring.
But it's attached to the headboard,
and we'll have to take that apart.
Then we got the couch.
- Is that a sectional?
- Yeah, 12 pieces.
- A marble coffee table.
- Is that a thick marble?
Three inches thick.
Got it in Italy.
But the big problem is gonna be
the convertible sofa.
When you move it,
it tends to open up...
...so it's going to be difficult
getting it downstairs.
Stairs?
- There's no elevator?
- No, it's a brownstone. Three floors.
- I'm sorry, I can't do this.
- What?
I can't do it! I can't!
It's too soon.
I don't know you.
I can't help you move, I'm sorry.
I can't! I just can't.
- Hello.
Oh, you don't remember me.
- No. Should I?
- Yeah, yeah, you should...
...because I certainly remember you.
Let me refresh your memory.
June 14th, 1987.
Mets-Phillies. You made a big error.
Cost the Mets the game.
Then you're coming up
the parking lot ramp.
You said, "Nice game, pretty boy."
- You remember.
- And then you spit on us.
- Hey, I didn't spit at you.
- Yeah, right.
- No, no. Then who was it?
- Look, the way I remember it...
...I was walking up the ramp.
I was upset about the game.
That's when you called me
"pretty boy."
Hey, that tick ed me off.
I was turning to say something...
...and as I turned around...
...I saw Roger McDowell
behind the bushes...
...over by that gravelly road.
Anyway, he was talking to someone,
and they were pointing at you.
I tried to scream out,
but it was too late.
It was already on its way.
I told you.
- It was McDowell.
- But why? Why McDowell?
Maybe because we were sitting
in the right-field stands...
...cursing at him in the bullpen
all game.
He must have caught a glimpse of us
when I poured that beer on his head.
- It was McDowell.
- Oh, boy.
- Look, Keith, we're sorry.
- Yeah, I couldn't be sorrier.
Guys, don't worry about it.
- Well, I guess I better get going.
- What are you doing?
- I gotta move.
- You want any help?
- I'd love some. You sure?
- I'd love to help you.
Yeah, me too!
Okay, guys. We got to be careful
of one thing.
Some of the stuff is very fragile
We'll have to handle it like a baby.
Hey, no sweat.
Hello.
Oh, hi, Elaine. What's going on?
No, he just left.
You broke up with him?
Me too!
What happened?
Oh, smoking. You know, you're like
going out with C. Everett Koop.
Me? No.
I couldn't go through with it.
I just didn't feel ready.
So, what are you doing now?
Oh, great idea. Okay.
I'll meet you there in, like,
30 minutes.
Okay, bye.
Keith! Keith!
- What happened? Where's Keith?
- You just missed him. He just left.
What do you need him for?
Keith! Keith! Up here!
Look, could you do me a favor?
I need you to go to the
unemployment office with me!
l... I'm Jerry's friend!
The guy from the locker room!
I'm the chucker!
lt'll take five minutes!
Wait! Wait!
Well, Biff...
...what's next?
I don't know.
Excuse me.
I was walking behind you, and you...
...dropped your wallet.
When you're moving,
your whole world becomes boxes.
That's all you think about,
is boxes. Where are there boxes?
You just wander down the street,
going in and out of stores.
"Are there boxes here?
Have you seen any boxes?"
I mean, you can't even talk to people
because you can't concentrate.
"Shut up! I'm looking for boxes!"
So after a while, you become
really into it. You can smell them.
You walk into a store:
"There's boxes here.
Don't tell me you don't have boxes.
Damn it! I can smell them!"
You become, like, obsessed.
"I love the smell of cardboard
in the morning."
At a funeral, everyone's crying around.
You're looking at the casket:
"That's a nice box.
Does anybody know where
that guy got that box?
When he's done with it,
you think I could get that?
It's got some nice handles on it."
And that's what death is, really.
It's the last big move of your life.
The hearse is like the van.
The pallbearers are close friends.
The only ones you could really ask
to help you with a big move like that.
And the casket is that great,
perfect box...
...you've been looking for
your whole life.
The only problem is
once you find it, you're in it.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group