They got us trained
to use the cash machine.
We're chickens in an experiment...
...waiting for that pellet
to come down the shoot.
You see people at the cash machine.
They're just there.
Waiting for the sound.
You're waiting for the sound.
That's what we're trained to hear.
The here-comes-the-money sound,
you know?
It's exciting. Don't you get excited?
"It's coming. It's coming.
They're giving me money."
Hey, I gotta get some cash.
I'm gonna run down to the ATM.
- Yeah, I gotta grab some too.
- I'll get it for you.
Just give me your card.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, just tell me your code.
My code?
- So why didn't you tell her the code?
- No way.
George, you're gonna
marry this woman, most likely.
It says very clearly,
"For your protection...
...do not give your secret code
to anyone."
So you're taking relationship advice
from Chemical Bank now?
Why does everything have to be "us"?
Is there no "me" left?
Why can't there be some things
just for me? Is that so selfish?
Actually, that's the definition
of selfish.
Have you given your code
to anyone?
No one's ever asked. Do you want it?
It's Jor-EI.
- Superman's father on Krypton.
- Of course.
Come on, Georgie,
you know you wanna tell me.
It's eating you up inside.
Sing it, sister.
No. No, I am not giving my code
to anyone for any reason.
What if my life depended on it?
If you're in some situation where
fast cash will save your life...
...l'll give you the code.
- What's the matter with your leg?
- My foot fell asleep.
- How did your foot fall asleep?
- I crossed my legs.
I forgot to alternate.
- Hey, Jerry, George.
- Hey, Fred.
- Hey, Freddie.
- Foot fell asleep.
You're lucky. At least you got
something to do.
- Hey, Fred, do you know Elaine?
- No.
Nice to meet you. Well, I'm out of here.
See you, guys.
- All right, Fred.
- See you.
Did you hear that?
He said, "Nice to meet you."
- So?
- So we've met before.
At Katie Ash's party.
We talked for, like, 10 minutes.
And he didn't remember you?
- Where are you going?
- I gotta go talk to him.
Excuse me. Excuse me, Fred.
- Yeah.
- Hi.
You just said, "Nice to meet you,"
but actually we've met before.
- We have?
- Yeah. Yeah, at Katie Ash's party.
What was your name again?
Elaine. You don't remember
our conversation?
I talked about how
my uncle worked...
...in the book depository building
with Lee Harvey Oswald.
Not ringing a bell.
When my uncle said to him,
"The president's been shot"...
...Oswald winked at him and said,
"I'm gonna go catch a movie."
- No.
- Right when we were in front of...
...the bathroom door.
- The bathroom door.
I remember someone had played
tic-tac-toe on it and the X's won.
They went diagonally from
the top left to the bottom right.
Sounds great. I'd love to do
some TV commercials.
That should really be fun.
Okay. All right, bye.
How do you like that?
I'm gonna do TV spots
for Leapin' Larry's Appliance Store.
That was Leapin' Larry himself.
I'm gonna meet him tomorrow.
Leapin' Larry.
That's where I bought this.
- What is that?
- It's an emergency-band scanner.
It picks up everything:
fires, harbour patrol, even the police.
I'm watching the watchers, Jerry.
We got a big fire on 115th.
I tell you, if I could do it over again,
I'd give it all up to be a fireman.
Yeah, those civil servants who
risk their lives really got it made.
Yeah. When I was a kid,
all I ever dreamed of...
...was steering the back
of that big hook-and-ladder.
You're lucky they let you drive a car.
No, no, no. They're taking
the West Side Highway.
At this time of day? That's insane.
They're heading
straight into gridlock.
Oh, those fools.
What was that? All right.
So get a load of this.
This guy, Fred Yerkes...
...remembers every little thing
about that night except me.
Really? I'm surprised.
He doesn't meet that many women.
So, what are you saying?
What's to be said.
He didn't remember you.
Yeah, but why? I mean...
...you know.
I know.
- You know?
- Yeah, I know.
- You got the new catalogue.
- Yeah. Good piece...
...on the Himalayan Walking Shoe.
- Too good. Peterman was so pleased...
...now he wants to take me
out to dinner tomorrow.
- Maybe you wanna come.
- Why would I wanna do that?
Please, Jerry.
Please, please, please.
I can't sit with him.
He tells these stories.
It's gonna be awful.
Yeah, sounds like fun.
I want you to tell me, George.
Why? Why is my code
so important?
Because it's part of our relationship.
It's an indication of trust.
We're not supposed to
keep secrets from one another.
I'm sure you have secrets from me.
I don't know anything
about your cycles.
- My cycles?
- I never know what's going on there.
Well, from now on,
I'll keep you apprised of my cycles.
- Please.
- Anything else?
We're out of Bosco.
How about this?
"Come on down to Leapin' Larry's.
If you beat our prices,
we'll give you the store."
You know, I've always liked
your comedy.
- You don't take cheap shots.
- No, I don't.
I'm sorry for keeping you so long.
Again, I apologize for the mess.
This renovation is killing me.
My foot's asleep again.
When I lost my leg
in the boating accident last year...
...I got so depressed
about this damn prosthetic...
...I thought I was gonna have to
give up the business.
But now, I'm rejuvenated.
Let me show you around the store.
You know what,
I'll be with you in a minute.
That is a great impression.
Larry, wait, you don't understand.
I just came from Leapin' Larry's.
What, making fun of crippled people?
Is that what you've sunk to?
No, I didn't do it on purpose.
My foot fell asleep.
Oh, your foot fell asleep.
You know, the guy has one leg and
he still calls himself Leapin' Larry.
You'd think he'd have
a sense of humour.
You just joked yourself out of that
commercial, didn't you, munjamba?
Yeah.
Oh, boy. Look at that.
See, that's that fire
I was listening to yesterday.
The whole building burned down.
They just don't know
what street to take.
Remember I got us to Yankee Stadium
in rush hour in 15 minutes?
- Of course.
- It's all up here, Jerry.
All up here. It's innate.
The amazing thing is
you never have any place to go.
Where are we gonna eat?
We're gonna meet Elaine and
Peterman at the Chinese place.
Nobody mentioned
anything about Peterman.
If I did, would you have gone?
- No way.
- There you go.
I don't even know Peterman.
Now how am I gonna relax?
I'm gonna have to be on all night.
I don't like being on, Jerry.
I'd much rather be off.
Trust me, you're off.
Oh, hi, Fred.
Hello.
- It's Elaine.
- Oh, yeah. Right.
- Yeah. How you doing?
- I'm depressed.
I got this new shirt.
The button fell off.
Once the button falls off, that's it.
I'll never fix it.
- Yeah, that's too bad.
- Yeah, I'm gonna get some vitamins.
- I feel depleted.
- I never take them.
They make you nauseous, right?
Yeah. Yeah, that's right.
You remembered.
Do you wanna have dinner tonight?
- Tonight?
- What, you have other plans?
No, no, no. None that I can...
...remember.
All right. You're locked up in a prison
in Turkey. I have your wallet.
The only way I can bribe the guards
to get you out...
...is for you to give me
your ATM code.
- Call the embassy.
- They're closed.
- Why?
- Bomb threat.
- We're in Turkey?
- Midnight Express, my friend.
My card won't work.
They're not on the PLUS system.
You must be Jerry Seinfeld.
Yes. Hi, Mr. Peterman.
This is George Costanza.
J. Peterman.
J. Crew.
So is Elaine here?
Oh, Elaine just called.
She won't be joining us.
But not to worry. I'll tell the maître d'
it'll just be the three bulls.
What? He still wants to have dinner
with us?
- Without Elaine? What for?
- What is he, crazy?
Oh, we gotta get out of here.
Come on, weave your web,
liar-man.
- I got nothing. l... I'm blank.
- Come on, George...
...what's the matter with you?
- I'm choking.
Oh, Fong has been
most accommodating.
- Shall we?
- Actually, I just remembered...
...I promised this comedy club
that I'd do a set tonight.
- I'm terribly sorry.
- I understand. No hard feelings.
George and I
will miss your company.
Fong, it will just
be two this evening.
Well, George...
...we dine.
I can't believe this.
This guy's standing me up?
And there, tucked into the river's bend,
was the object of my search...
...the Guangia River Market.
Fabrics and spices
traded under a starlit sky.
It was there that I discovered
the Pamplona Beret.
Sizes seven and a half through
eight and three quarters. Price, $35.
What about sports?
You follow sports?
It's fourth and inches and
the Giants are going for it.
You've gotta love sports.
You know, this is very nice,
but I really could take a cab, really...
Nonsense, George.
Besides, it gives me a chance to
tell you about my trip to Burma.
I discovered a very unusual
corduroy.
Peterman here.
What? Oh, no.
All right. I'll be right there.
It's my mother.
She's at death's door.
- What?
- I just pray to God...
...we can make it there in time.
I can't believe you blew us off.
We did you a fav our.
Well, Fred asked me out.
- Fred?
- Yeah, and then he stood me up.
I don't get this guy.
You see what's going on here.
You're attracted to him because
he can't remember you.
I am? But that's so sick.
That's God's plan.
He doesn't really want anyone
to get together.
Anyway, so how was the dinner?
Well, when I heard
you weren't coming...
...I made an excuse and
got the hell out of there.
What about Georgie?
He didn't make it.
- Doctor, how is she?
- She's too weak to talk.
- She'll be happy to hear you.
- Mama, it's me, Jacobo.
I'm here for you, Mama.
I'm George Costanza.
I was having dinner with your son.
Shake off the dew, my friend.
Oh, man.
- What time is it?
- It's morning.
Thanks for seeing me
through the night.
I'll make us a pot of coffee, George.
Watch her, won't you?
- Who?
- Mama.
Just talk to her, George.
The doctor seems to think it helps.
Hi. You know, l... l...
I really should be getting back
to my fiancée. You know, we...
We had this big fight yesterday...
...and, well, she wants to know
my secret code.
I don't know. I can't tell her.
The funny thing is, you know,
I would really love to tell someone...
...because it's killing me.
You wanna know what it is?
It's Bosco.
You know, the chocolate syrup.
I love that stuff. I pour it in milk.
It's my favourite drink.
Boy, that is a relief.
Bosco.
- Bosco.
- Mama?
- Quiet, quiet. It's a secret.
- Bosco! Bosco!
- Shut up. It's a secret.
- Mama, what are you trying to say?
Bosco.
She's gone.
Bosco?
This never would have happened...
...if you hadn't bailed out on me.
- I did not bail out on you.
Why couldn't you include me
in your excuse?
Why didn't you
come up with your own?
I froze.
- I think I'm losing it.
- Oh, come on.
- Maybe you're just in a slump.
- No, no.
I reached down
and there was nothing there.
Now Peterman wants me
to go to the funeral.
Oh, come on, just tell me
your code already. What is it?
I am not giving you my code.
- I bet I can guess it.
- Yeah, right.
Oh, all right. Yeah.
Let's see.
Well, we can throw out birthdays
immediately. That's too obvious.
And no numbers for you.
You're a word man.
All right. Let's go deeper.
What kind of man are you?
Well, you're weak, spineless.
A man of temptations.
But what tempts you?
You're a portly fellow...
...a little long in the waistband.
So, what's your pleasure?
Is it the salty snacks you crave?
No, no, no.
Yours is a sweet tooth.
- Get out of here.
- Oh, you may stray...
...but you'll always return
to your dark master...
...the cocoa bean.
- I'm leaving.
- And only the purest syrup nectar...
...can satisfy you.
- I gotta go.
If you could,
you'd guzzle it by the gallon.
- Ovaltine, Hershey's, Nestlé's Quik.
- Shut up! Shut up!
- What was that?
- What?
You just checked your watch.
Are you thinking of bailing?
I got a date.
- Oh, Mr. Peterman.
- Oh, Elaine.
George.
When Mama said "Bosco"...
...she must have been
communicating something.
Her legacy. A dying wish, perhaps.
Mothers say things.
My mother goes babbling on and on
like a crazy person.
Mr. Peterman...
...you have my deepest sympathies.
Unfortunately, I've gotta get going.
- You do?
- Yes, actually we both do.
I have a personal commitment.
- Well, personal... I mean, we both...
- What is it?
I'm speaking at a
woman's rights conference.
Yes, and I'm speaking
at a men's conference.
I don't believe that for a minute.
- Elaine, it was good of you to stop by.
- My pleasure.
Fortunately, I still have George here
to help me through this.
You know, George, growing up
as a boy in Costa Rica...
...I heard a rumour that
Mama had taken a lover.
Perhaps Bosco was this man's name.
You wanna come to
the fire station with me?
- Fire station?
- Yeah, I made a map of my shortcuts.
I'm gonna rock their world.
I gotta go down to Leapin' Larry's.
- He took you back?
- Yeah, we straightened it out.
- All is forgiven.
- You know...
...the important thing is that
you learned something.
No, I didn't.
Well, Mr. Kramer, your list of shortcuts
is most impressive.
This is just
the Upper West Side.
Wait until I get to the Village.
Then you're gonna see a magic show.
Mr. Kramer, almost every week
some hothead like yourself...
...saunters in here
talking about faster routes...
...and snazzier colours for the truck.
- Well, l...
The fact is, we feel things are
fine the way they are.
Thanks for having me back and
sorry about the misunderstanding.
Water under the bridge.
Come on. I never did get a chance to
show you around the store.
Oh, sure.
Oh, again.
I'll be right there.
Attention, company 390.
Structure fire...
...at Leapin' Larry's
Appliance Warehouse.
Leapin' Larry's? Hey, that's uptown.
You gotta take Amsterdam.
- Stay out of this, Kramer.
- All right, men, let's move it.
Pull those doors.
Move. Move.
Giddyup.
Are you okay, cowboy?
- Where do you need to go?
- I drive the back of the truck.
You'd better take it easy.
All right, 48, let's go. Let's go!
Sorry about the other night.
My mother called.
She couldn't find her pills.
I had to go into Brooklyn...
...help her find the pills
and they were right in...
...the medicine cabinet.
Could you believe that?
The worst part is getting from
the subway station to the house.
There's no transportation.
What am I doing?
I'm on a date with this guy
because he didn't remember me?
He's demented. Listen to him.
I could take a cab, but if my mother
saw me in a cab, she would yell at me:
"Freddie, what are you taking
a cab for? It's so expensive."
She's out of her mind.
Eventually, you'll meet her.
Bosco.
There's a big fire down the street.
The whole block is going up in flames.
George.
We're gonna make a left
onto Broadway.
No, I would advise against that.
- Who is this?
- It's Kramer.
Kramer?
What are you doing back there?
Desota's down,
but Cosmo's got the caboose.
- How did this start?
- Beats me.
Where the hell is the fire department?
I'm gonna lose the whole store.
Kramer, get the hell out of there.
You're not trained to
operate this equipment.
- Hey, Kramer!
- Hey!
Pay attention, Kramer!
Hey, try the scanner.
See if you can pick up anything.
What are you doing, Kramer?
You're all over the road.
- Don't worry, cap, I can handle it.
- Kramer?
You're losing control.
Hard right! Hard right!
We're never gonna to mak e it!
That's a shame.
This fire's gonna eat up
this entire block.
George, look. There's a man in there.
Get out. You're in danger.
My sleeve, it's stuck in the machine.
It ate my card.
George, give me your ATM card.
I don't have my ATM card.
George, you're obviously lying.
Anyone can see that.
It's jammed.
I'll slide it under the door.
- Now give me your code.
- What? Why?
The machine won't open
without the code.
- George, give him your code.
- But l...
George, there's no time.
Tell him your code.
Shout out your code, man.
Code! The code!
Hi.
- Here's your cash, George.
- Thanks.
And here's your card back.
Anyone for Bosco?
Oh, my God.
- Look at this.
- What?
It's the new J. Peterman catalogue.
Look, look.
"The Rogue's Wallet.
It's where he kept his card,
his dirty little secret.
Short, devious, balding...
...his name was Costanza.
He killed my mother."