Human fascination with water
is amazing.
We're constantly going
to beaches, pools, lakes, rivers.
We're swimming, we're snorkeling,
we're scuba-diving.
We bathe in it.
Our bodies are mostly made of water.
Everyone's carrying around
these bottles of water.
We can't get enough water.
Unless it rains...
...then we're like,
''Oh, look, l'm soaked.
l am literally drenched.''
For some reason, we have a huge
problem with small, flying water.
lt'll just stop us right in our tracks.
''l felt a drop.
We're gonna get caught in it!
Everyone cover
your water bottles. Run!''
Get off at the next exit.
Kramer, l've driven
to East Hampton many times.
l know the exit.
l hear it's a great house.
Pool, sun deck.
Yeah, l'll be there.
You sure we're making
the right move?
We gotta see the new baby. At least
we'll get a weekend in the Hamptons.
-Didn't they just have a baby?
-That was two years ago.
Remember?
''Jerry, you gotta see the baby.
You gotta see the baby.''
ls it possible they're just having
babies to get people to visit them?
Hey, Jerry, you ever
wear silk underwear?
-No.
-Put that on the top of your list.
No, not for me.
A little too delightful.
George and Jane
should be almost there.
lsn't it weird that they
haven't had sex...
...but they're spending
a weekend together?
George is pleased.
lt's like she signed a letter of intent.
-When's Rachel coming out?
-The 3:00 train.
Her father is so religious.
l'm amazed he's letting you
see her again...
...after that Schindler's List
make-out session.
l brought him some kishke.
-What's that?
-lt's a stuffed meat thing.
lsraeli soldiers carry it in case
they're captured behind enemy lines.
They eat it and it kills them.
l never tasted a cough medicine
l didn't love.
Me too. l love cough medicine.
You see? We were made
for each other.
It's amazing. If I reach out
and touch her breast right now...
...she'd scream and throw me
out of the car.
But at this time tomorrow,
I could touch it all I want.
-What's your favorite?
-Pertussin.
-Ever try it with club soda?
-No.
Oh, very refreshing.
Sex is like joining a private club.
I'll be the same me tomorrow...
...but suddenly the ''no trespassing''
sign will be gone.
-Are we almost there?
-Yeah, about 1 0, 1 5 minutes.
But l have to stop
at a vegetable stand.
-What for?
-My mother loves Hampton tomatoes.
She's nuts for Hampton tomatoes.
Can you buy them later?
l really wanna get some sun.
Hey, Jerry, rub some lotion
on my back.
Who are you, Mrs. Robinson?
Come on. l'll rub some on you.
-That's not sweetening the deal.
-Oh, come on.
No.
You know, when l was a kid...
...l once found $ 1 .50 in change
at the bottom of a pool.
-You must have been excited.
-Yeah.
l gotta go get those tomatoes.
You wanna go?
-l don't think so.
-Okay. l'll see you later.
-Anybody want some tomatoes?
-No, thanks.
l'm gonna take a dip.
And then there's Maude.
Look at my face.
Look at it.
-Do you see any lines?
-No lines.
You know why?
One word: shade.
So when are we gonna see this baby?
When is this momentous event?
He's taking a nap or something.
l'm gonna go see if there are
any girls on the beach.
-Elaine, you wanna come?
-No, thanks.
l got plenty of girlfriends.
Well, this is interesting.
What?
Jane's topless.
Yo-Yo Ma.
Boutros Boutros-Golly.
Nice rack.
Come on, you guys.
You can come and see the baby now.
-Oh, in a minute, Carol.
-Yeah, we're gonna be right up.
This is weird, wild stuff.
George hasn't even seen her yet.
Why do you think we're getting
the sneak preview?
Maybe she's trying to create a buzz.
-What?
-Get some good word of mouth going.
Oh, here she comes.
l'm thirsty. Anyone want a drink?
No, thanks.
l'm good.
All right. Show's over.
l'm going to the beach.
Adam, Jerry and Elaine are here.
Where is the cute little
snuggly baby?
-lsn't he gorgeous?
-Oh, he's--
ls he gorgeous.
Gorgeous, yes.
So very gorgeous.
Michael, shut the door.
You're letting bugs in.
ls it me or was that the ugliest baby
you have ever seen?
l couldn't look.
lt was like a Pekingese.
Boy, a little too much chlorine
in that gene pool.
The thing is, they'll never know.
No one's ever gonna tell them.
-You have to lie.
-Oh, it's a must-lie situation.
Yes. lt's a must-lie situation.
You know, l don't think we should
tell George we saw Jane topless.
No. l don't think so.
Remind me to tell Kramer too.
Lobster.
-Well, this ointment should do it.
-How are you feeling, Adam?
Elaine. This is our pediatrician,
Ben Pfeffer.
Hi.
Look at him, Elaine.
How gorgeous is he, l ask you?
How gorgeous?
Pretty gorgeous.
-Elaine, do you have children?
-Me? No, but l'd love to have a baby.
l mean, l can't wait to have a baby.
l'm just dying to have a baby.
A beautiful woman like you should.
You're quite breathtaking.
Breathtaking?
l'm breathtaking?
And he's very particular.
Ben, you're staying
over tonight, right?
Sure.
l....
l'm gonna go pick up Rachel
at the station.
-Yeah, see you.
-Okay.
Oh, just look at him.
Yeah, he really is breathtaking.
The train was so crowded,
l had a seat facing the wrong way.
Oh, l like that.
lt's like going back in time.
-Hey, Rachel.
-Hi.
-l'm gonna go in and get changed.
-Okay.
What kind of a greeting was that?
-She's got greeting problems.
-Yeah.
Boy, l love these Hampton tomatoes.
You know, you can eat them
like apples.
lt's funny. The tomato never really
took off as a hand fruit.
Well, the tomato's an anomaly.
So successful with the ketchup
and the sauce...
...but you can't find a good one.
Look at what l got!
The K-man!
You got lobster for everybody?
Yeah, and they're fresh.
Right out of the ocean!
This is fantastic.
Man, what a weekend!
Swimming, lobster for dinner.
l know. lt's great.
l saw Jane topless.
You saw who what?
Yeah, l saw Jane topless.
Well, we all saw her.
All right.
You saw Jane topless?
Well, when you went for the
tomatoes, she lied out topless.
Oh, you mean facedown
on her chest.
No.
-Faceup on her back?
-Yeah.
-Well, why'd she do that?
-Well, l guess she was hot.
You mean she just
lay there topless?
No, no. She got up,
she walked around.
Walked around?
-And you looked?
-Of course.
She's got a great body, buddy.
All right, l'm gonna go upstairs.
l'll be right back.
l can't believe that you saw her
before me!
Think of me as a doctor.
-Well, how good a look did you get?
-What do you mean?
Well, if she was a criminal...
...and you had to describe her
to a police sketch artist...?
They'd pick her up
in about 1 0 minutes.
Great. Great.
So any time you want,
you can just visualize her naked.
l guess that's true.
Stop it. Stop it.
This is not fair! lt's not fair.
l don't like this.
l don't like it one bit.
What do you want me to do?
You wanna see Rachel naked?
Yes! Yes!
-Yeah, right.
-The punishment should fit the crime.
You could see me naked.
l could offer you that.
lt's like l'm Neil Armstrong.
l turn around for a sip of Tang
and you jump out first!
Nobody ever called me
breathtaking before.
l've never been called
breathtaking either.
l mean, if he thinks that
that baby is breathtaking...
...then who's not breathtaking?
Maybe he just said it
because the mother was in the room.
Yeah. Right.
That's a possibility.
l have to find out.
-How you gonna do that?
-l can be very clever.
-l'm gonna take a swim.
-Oh, me too. l'll meet you down there.
Don't go in.
Rachel's getting undressed.
Oh, okay.
-Hey!
-Oh, sorry.
-Don't you knock?
-l'm sorry.
Not like l'll see something
l've never seen before.
-You might have.
-l didn't.
You won't.
What do you want anyway, George?
Yes, George. l'm kind of
wondering myself.
What is it that you want?
No, l was just wondering
if you guys had any gum.
So you were swimming
in the pool...
...and you wanted some gum.
Yes, because the water
was cold...
...and the chewing warms me up.
We don't have any gum.
Okay. Thanks anyway.
Strange man.
Wait till you get to know him.
-So where is this baby, anyway?
-Oh, check it out.
l guarantee you've never seen
anything quite so objectionable.
lt's down the hall,
third door on your left.
Oh, my God!
l'm sorry, l thought this was
the baby's room.
l'm really sorry.
l was in the pool!
Did she do it on purpose?
lt was my fault.
l told her the wrong door.
l was supposed to see her.
She wasn't supposed to see me.
So what?
Well, ordinarily l wouldn't mind.
But....
But what?
Well, l'd just got back
from swimming in the pool...
...and the water was cold.
-You mean shrinkage.
-Yes.
Significant shrinkage.
So you feel you were shortchanged?
Yes.
lf she thinks that's me, she's under
a complete misapprehension.
That was not me, Jerry.
That was not me.
Well, so, what's the difference?
-What if she discusses it with Jane?
-Oh, she's not gonna tell Jane.
-How do you know?
-Women aren't like us.
They're worse!
They're much worse than us.
They talk about everything.
Could you tell her about
the shrinkage factor?
No. l'm not gonna tell her
about your shrinkage.
Besides, l think women know
about shrinkage.
How do women know
about shrinkage?
lsn't it common knowledge?
-Elaine.
Elaine!
-What?
-Do women know about shrinkage?
What do you mean, like laundry?
No.
Like when a man goes swimming,
afterwards....
lt shrinks?
Like a frightened turtle.
-Why does it shrink?
-lt just does.
l don't know how you guys
walk around with those things.
-Excellent lobster, Kramer.
-Really good.
Rachel, aren't you gonna have any?
No, l can't.
l'm kosher. We don't eat shellfish.
You mean you've
never tasted lobster?
No.
You're so pious.
l really respect that.
You know, when you die...
...you're gonna get
some special attention.
The baby's crying.
l'll go get him, he can sit with us.
No, no. You don't want to do that.
-You'll be uncomfortable.
-Yeah. Finish eating.
The baby's not gonna have
any fun over here.
-We're not fun for a baby.
-Yeah.
The lobsters will scare him.
l'm gonna get him.
See? Look at this.
Rachel, my T-shirt shrunk.
lt used to be much bigger,
and now it shrunk.
See, that's what water does.
lt shrinks things.
Really? Tell us more, Mr. Science.
What are you doing?
What are you laughing at?
-lt's nothing, George.
-lt's very impolite to tell secrets.
-Are you talking about me?
-What is it with you?
Easy, big fella.
Kramer, where did you
get these lobsters?
-At MacLeish's Fish Market?
-No. l got them in the ocean.
The ocean? What do you mean?
Well, l found this rope
and l kept tugging on it...
...all these lobsters came up.
Those are commercial lobster traps.
You can't take lobsters from there.
-That's against the law.
-Hey, take it easy.
There are plenty of lobsters
in the ocean for everyone.
My father was a lobsterman.
He got up every morning at 4...
...and came home at night
stinking of brine.
He sent me through law school
with the lobsters he caught.
Here he is.
-Some night, huh?
-Yeah.
l wish l had my telescope.
-Some dinner, huh?
-Yeah.
Nothing like really
fresh-caught lobster.
Some house, huh?
lt was built by Mark Farbman.
He built a lot of these homes here.
Some ugly baby, huh?
-What did you say?
-l said...
...''some snuggly baby.''
He is something.
Well, to tell you the truth,
Dr. Pfeffer...
...l was surprised to hear you use
a word like ''breathtaking''...
...to describe a baby.
l mean, because you also
used it referring to me.
Well, you know, Elaine, sometimes
you say a thing like that just to be nice.
You told her?
-Yeah. What's the big deal?
-You don't understand this organ.
lt's very schizophrenic.
Anyway, what's the difference?
You're the ones who are
obsessed with this stuff, not us.
l'm sure it wouldn't matter to Jane.
You're going back
to New York now?
Yeah. l have some things
to do tomorrow.
l think you spoke to your little friend
Rachel, that's what l think.
So what if l did?
And she didn't say something to you
about a certain something?
l don't know what
you're talking about.
l think that you think...
...that a certain something
is not all that it could be...
...when, in fact, it is
all that it should be and more.
-l'm sure it is.
-Look, you don't understand.
There was shrinkage.
You looking for this?
Oh, Kramer. You startled me.
Well, l thought you might
wind up around here.
Yeah, well, l couldn't stop...
...thinking about the way everybody
was enjoying the lobster so much.
And, well, l thought a little taste
couldn't hurt.
-May l?
-No, l'm afraid l couldn't do that.
-Why not?
-Well, now, it wouldn't be kosher.
Come on, Kramer.
l really wanna try it.
No, l'm sorry, honey.
Not on my watch.
Come on, Kramer.
l just heard a car drive out.
What was that?
Oh, just Jane driving back
to New York in the middle of the night.
George, thanks so much
for making breakfast.
These are the best
scrambled eggs ever.
l didn't know you could cook.
Well, l'm just expressing my gratitude
to our gracious host.
Yes, George, the whole breakfast
is breathtaking.
-Good morning.
-Hey!
-Hey, morning.
-Morning.
Kramer, l wanna thank you
again for last night.
-You really saved me.
-What happened?
Well, l almost tried the lobster...
...but Kramer stopped me.
Well, l knew you'd regret it
for the rest of your life.
You're right. l would have.
Hey, look at this guy.
-A little breakfast?
-Yeah.
-And you eat eggs, don't you?
-Yes, l do.
-All right.
-Thank you.
Delicious. Where did you learn
to make eggs like this?
These are so good.
Enjoying them?
Oh, good.
You know, you might wanna try
eating it with one of these.
There's lobster in these eggs?
Not that much.
You know, they tend
to shrink in the water.
Well, l guess l gotta go too.
Well, this has turned out
to be one hell of a weekend.
Excuse me.
Sorry to bother you.
We're trying to track down
a lobster poacher...
...that cleaned out one of the traps.
l wonder what's going on.
Guess l should go up
and apologize.
-There he is, officer.
-Yeah.
Don't you ever knock?!
l don't know why Rachel had
to drive back with Michael and Carol.
Hey, if you saw me naked...
...l wouldn't wanna ride
in the same car with you either.
l still can't believe
Michael finked on Kramer.
How is he gonna pay off
a $ 1 000 fine?
They got some sort of program.
What?
Hey, there's a tomato stand.
Let's stop. l can get some more.
Hey, isn't that Michael's car?
-There's Rachel.
-Where?
Look at the work that people
will do to get to the ocean.
They'll fight traffic and the heat
and the parking and the hot sand...
...trying to get through the waves...
...and the ironic thing is...
...the ocean doesn't
even really want us in there.
That's what surfing is.
Surfing is the ocean
throwing us out of itself.
You see?
We keep trying to paddle in...
...and the ocean is saying,
''No, you don't.''
The ocean is like a nightclub...
...and the waves are bouncers
tossing us out.
The undertow is like
the really mean bouncer.
lnstead of throwing you out, they take
you in the back and rough you up.
''Oh, you wanna come in?
How about coming in like 25 miles?''